<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 04:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared CB Kristian Fulton, WR Jalen Royals, TE Jared Wiley, RB Elijah Mitchell, G Trey Smith, T Josh Simmons, and DE Malik Herring inactive for Week 8 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27de-dab4-a3fb-bffe04a60000</link>
      <description>The offensive linemen were ruled out earlier in the week, something that could expose quarterback Patrick Mahomes to unwanted pressure against a Commanders defense blitzing at the fifth highest frequency this season. Fulton remains sidelined while Mitchell continues to be the odd man out in the backfield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-27de-dab4-a3fb-bffe04a60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed WR Marquez Valdes-Scantling, formerly of the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2806-d5d8-a3ff-f96779730000</link>
      <description>Vadels-Scantling signs with the Steelers on an undisclosed contract following a successful visit earlier in the day. MVS was released from the 49ers after four appearances but previously played with Steelers quarterback Aaron Rodgers in Green Bay. It looks like a depth move for a team searching for consistent production from ancillary pieces behind alpha receiver DK Metcalf.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-2806-d5d8-a3ff-f96779730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Broncos CB Patrick Surtain (pectoral) is week-to-week with a strained pectoral.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-280a-deb1-a39b-290e3a760000</link>
      <description>Surtain was unable to finish the team’s Week 8 win over the Cowboys, leaving in the first half what is now known as a pectoral strain. He will miss multiple games with the ailment, likely leaving Kris Abrams-Draine to soak up additional work on the perimeter in the immediate future. Schefter adds that the team is likely to consider injured reserve for the reigning Defensive Player of the Year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-280a-deb1-a39b-290e3a760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marcus Mariota completed 21-of-30 passes for 213 yards, one touchdown, and two interceptions in the Commanders’ 28-7, Week 8 loss to the Chiefs, adding 28 yards on eight carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28c9-d245-adfb-bddfa2590000</link>
      <description>Mariota seemed to be doing enough to threaten an upset on the road, passing for 155 yards in the first half in what was a 7-7 game at the break. The wheels fell off the rest of the way with the Commanders failing to move the football with any sort of consistency in the second half. Two turnovers on downs and an interception in the red zone in the first half stalled any momentum, but the Washington defense kept the team in the game - at least enough to keep the team competitive through two frames. The Commanders drop their third straight contest and are now in need of a mid-season intervention, which could come in the form of a return to health of second-year quarterback Jayden Daniels for a difficult test at home against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28c9-d245-adfb-bddfa2590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacory Croskey-Merritt rushed nine times for 25 yards in the Commanders’ Week 8 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28cf-d245-adfb-bddf046d0000</link>
      <description>Croskey-Merritt was out-gained by quarterback Marcus Mariota on the ground while fellow running back Jeremy McNichols led the team in receiving. It was an all-around poor showing by the Commanders after taking a 7-7 game into the half. Croskey-Merritt faces another difficult challenge against the Seahawks in Week 9, where he can’t be counted on as more than a FLEX play by fantasy managers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28cf-d245-adfb-bddf046d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin caught 3-of-4 targets for 54 yards and a touchdown in the Commanders’ Week 8 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e0-d5d8-a3ff-f9e1d3540000</link>
      <description>McLaurin saw shadow coverage from opposing lockdown corner Trent McDuffie, something that helps explain his modest four targets on the evening. He did make two highlight reel grabs on the evening, the first a toe-dragging touchdown on the sideline in the end zone and the second a circus catch down the sideline, but failed to finish the game after apparently tweaking his injured quad early in the fourth quarter. Fantasy managers will want to monitor his practice status ahead of a difficult matchup with the Seahawks in Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e0-d5d8-a3ff-f9e1d3540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zach Ertz caught 4-of-6 targets for 16 yards in the Commanders’ Week 8 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e3-dab4-a3fb-bbf3b5380000</link>
      <description>Ertz committed two uncharacteristic drops and saw decreased involvement in the offense with the returns of Terry McLaurin and Deebo Samuel. McLaurin failed to finish the game after apparently tweaking the quad injury that forced him to miss time this season, so there could be room for Ertz to see another bump in targets when the Commanders host the Seahawks in Week 9. Treat Ertz as a low-upside TE2 for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e3-dab4-a3fb-bbf3b5380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deebo Samuel caught 3-of-6 targets for 11 yards in the Commanders’ Week 8 loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e6-d5d8-a3ff-f9e737be0000</link>
      <description>Samuel’s drop occurred in the red zone on the team’s first possession, with the pass going through his hands, off his face mask, and into the waiting arms of Kansas City defensive end Mike Danna. It was a forgettable performance from the veteran slot man, who also saw his usage cut into with the return of Terry McLaurin. That said, McLaurin failed to finish the game after tweaking his quad injury, something fantasy managers will want to track closely as the team prepares to host the Seahawks in Week 9. Another missed contest from McLaurin could leave Samuel as the team’s top pass-catcher yet again, a situation that could warrant WR2 potential in fantasy circles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28e6-d5d8-a3ff-f9e737be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 25-of-34 passes for 299 yards, three touchdowns, and two interceptions in the Chiefs’ 28-7, Week 8 win over the Commanders, adding 30 yards on four carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28ea-d5d8-a3ff-f9ebd0b70000</link>
      <description>Mahomes threw interceptions on consecutive drives for the first time in his career on the Chiefs’ first two possessions of the game, the first an undercut back shoulder through by Washington corner Marcus Lattimore and the second a ball off veteran tight end Travis Kelce’s hands over the middle of the field. The Chiefs would shut out the Commanders after the break, during which time Mahomes would lead three straight touchdown drives that culminated receiving touchdowns by Kareem Hunt, Travis Kelce, and Rashee Rice. The defense would do the rest as the Chiefs coasted to a comfortable win after the early miscues. Up next for the 5-3 Chiefs is a gauntlet of opponents that begins with the Bills on the road in Week 9 before facing the Broncos and Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28ea-d5d8-a3ff-f9ebd0b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco rushed 12 times for 58 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28ef-deb1-a39b-29ef4a420000</link>
      <description>The veteran ground-mover was not targeted through the air and also watched from the sideline as Kareem Hunt cashed in on two short yardage scores, the first from inside the one and the second a two-yard receiving touchdown. Pacheco also got his leg caught under him on a tackle to his knee in the fourth quarter. He would limp to the sidelines under his own power before jumping off the training table with a smile, likely indicating he avoided an injury that could cost him time. He could have his number called more frequently against the run-funnel Bills in Week 9, against whom he enters RB2 territory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-28ef-deb1-a39b-29ef4a420000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
