<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:01:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Keenan Allen caught 4-of-5 targets for 44 yards in the Chargers’ Week 8 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-143e-d245-adfb-957f3d420000</link>
      <description>It was a quiet day for Allen, and it’s disappointing on a day where Justin Herbert was able to find the end zone three times. Some of this has to do with the fact that the Chargers won by five scores, but it’s worth noting that Los Angeles may be in blowout territory again in Week 9 against the Titans. Still, Allen is a high-floor WR3 for that contest and going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-143e-d245-adfb-957f3d420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre Harris caught 2-of-2 targets for eight yards and a touchdown in the Chargers’ Week 8 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-143e-d245-adfb-957f43650000</link>
      <description>Harris has his first receiving touchdown of his career on a short completion from Justin Herbert. The second-round pick was a non-factor in the contest outside of that, in part because of Los Angeles going run-heavy in a blowout, and in larger part because Harris just isn’t a part of this Chargers’ offensive scheme. He’s off the radar for Week 9 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-143e-d245-adfb-957f43650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quentin Johnston didn’t receive a target in the Chargers’ Week 8 win over the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1444-deb1-a39b-354edfc10000</link>
      <description>Johnston’s lack of involvement could have something to do with the hamstring issue he had coming into Week 7, and also because the Chargers were running the ball an awful lot against the Minnesota front. Still, zero targets is beyond concerning; especially when you see “tight end” Oronde Gadsden so much more involved in this offense (5-77-1). Johnston is a very risky FLEX play for Week 9 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1444-deb1-a39b-354edfc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Jefferson caught 7-of-11 targets for 74 yards in the Vikings’ Week 8 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1446-deb1-a39b-354e5cac0000</link>
      <description>Jefferson was the best player for the Vikings, but that’s not saying a whole lot. Carson Wentz was under constant pressure — and wasn’t good even when he wasn’t — and the fact Jefferson was able to accrue this many yards is impressive with context. Jefferson will likely have J.J. McCarthy throwing him the football in Week 9 against the Lions. He’s a WR1 regardless, but it remains to be seen if that’s an upgrade or not.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1446-deb1-a39b-354e5cac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Addison caught 3-of-4 targets for 26 yards and a touchdown in the Vikings’ Week 8 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1451-d245-adfb-955f05010000</link>
      <description>Addison salvaged his fantasy day with a short scoring pass from Carson Wentz. It’s a disappointing effort, but an understandable one with Wentz struggling to stay upright and throwing ineffectively even when he did have time. Addison is a WR3 for the Week 9 contest against the Lions, but one who offers some upside even with some question marks as to who will be under center for Minnesota in that contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1451-d245-adfb-955f05010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught 2-of-3 targets for 26 yards in the Vikings’ Week 8 loss to the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1454-deb1-a39b-355eae3a0000</link>
      <description>Hockenson’s three targets are a season low, and unfortunately more inline to his disappointing first two contests when he had a combined 27 yards. The 28-year-old tight end is a decent bounceback candidate for Week 9 against his former team in the Lions, but it’s worth noting that J.J. McCarthy could be under center for that contest, and Hockenson and McCarthy didn’t appear to have much of a connection early on. Just something to keep in mind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1454-deb1-a39b-355eae3a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings HC Kevin O’Connell said “if J.J. [McCarthy] is healthy, J.J. will play” in Week 9 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1637-dab4-a3fb-9f7712b30000</link>
      <description>Speaking after a 37-10 loss to the Chargers on Thursday night, O’Connell stuck to the script regarding his second-year quarterbacks availability. McCarthy is nearly six full weeks removed from a high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 2 against the Falcons, but has been healthy enough to serve as the team’s emergency QB in back-to-back weeks. He also looked particularly nimble in Thursday’s loss when he leapt over Justin Jefferson who was barreling toward the sideline after making a catch. McCarthy has been listed as limited in every practice over the last two weeks and appears to be trending in the right direction toward a return. We’ll likely get a more definite answer from KOC once practice starts up next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1637-dab4-a3fb-9f7712b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports there is a “real possibility” Jayden Daniels (hamstring) is only out for Week 8 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-164f-d5d8-a3ff-ff6f778f0000</link>
      <description>According to Rapoport, Daniels is dealing with “a low-grade” hamstring injury that could only sideline him for one week. Head coach Dan Quinn didn’t waste any time ruling him out for Week 8 when he announced on Thursday that the Commanders would be without their QB1 for Monday Night Football against the Chiefs, so we’ll see if he gets a longer leash next week. The proof will be in the injury report, but a return to practice ahead of Week 9’s game would be an encouraging sign for the star QB after being sidelined all of this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-164f-d5d8-a3ff-ff6f778f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on Terron Armstead’s podcast ‘The Set,’ Tyreek Hill said whether or not he retires is “based upon how I feel.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1683-dab4-a3fb-9ff3e2be0000</link>
      <description>It was the first public interview given by Hill since suffering a season-ending knee injury in Week 4. The 31-year-old receiver said right now he’s happy being at home with his kids and with the career he has had before adding “I’m at the point now where I need to have a conversation [about retirement] with mom, family, everybody.” Laid up on his couch and recovering from surgery, Hill sounded more like a player who would prefer to retire than continue the NFL grind, but a lot could change between now and then. Hill will be 32 at the start of next season but remains under contract through 2026. He’ll have to undergo extensive rehab just to return to the field, and said in 2023 hewould retire after his current contract— the one he is on now — expires. Even if he does play in 2026, it’s clear Hill is on the back nine of his career, and could opt to call it quits at any time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1683-dab4-a3fb-9ff3e2be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on 105.3 The Fan, Cowboys owner Jerry Jones said Trevon Diggs (concussion) and Donovan Wilson (elbow/shoulder) are questionable for Week 8 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16a5-d5d8-a3ff-ffe552db0000</link>
      <description>Jones’ comments come before the the Cowboys third practice of the week gets underway. We will receive a more official word on both players’ statuses later in the day, but it’s worth pointing out that Diggs and Wilson were DNPs on Wednesday and Thursday. Jones calling them questionable is a fairly optimistic take given how they are trending based on those practices. We’ll check back in once the final injury report is released but both players will probably need a limited practice on Friday if they hope to suit up this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-16a5-d5d8-a3ff-ffe552db0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
