<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Trey Amos (fibula) will “miss some significant time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6a-d673-a39e-effb450a0000</link>
      <description>Considering how little is left of the NFL season and Washington’s placement in the standings, this is likely a season-ender. Amos had a 58.8 PFF coverage grade in 511 snaps during his first 10 games of the season, but looked rough the last two weeks as he allowed 138 yards and a touchdown while allowing 8-of-8 completions in coverage. He’ll likely head to IR in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6a-d673-a39e-effb450a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said he thinks Rashod Bateman will be “okay” after suffering an ankle injury in Week 10 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6a-d713-ad9e-6f7e88780000</link>
      <description>Bateman suffered an ankle sprain on what appeared to be an illegal hip-drop tackle in Sunday’s win. Harbaugh said the team will “see how serious it is going forward,” and was unable to say whether or not Bateman will play in Week 11 against the Browns. Bateman has caught 16 passes for 194 yards and two touchdowns this season and has managed just six catches in his last five games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6a-d713-ad9e-6f7e88780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said Harrison Mevis will again be the team’s kicker in Week 11 against Seattle.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f77-d45b-affe-7ff776880000</link>
      <description>Mevis, the “Thiccer Kicker,” did not attempt a field goal against the 49ers, settling for six made extra points. Seattle will probably force some more attempts this week against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f77-d45b-affe-7ff776880000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said Marlon Humphrey (finger) may need surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6f-d673-a39e-efff12140000</link>
      <description>According to Harbaugh, Humphrey would likely miss one or two games if he did need surgery. The team is still weighing that decision, but with games against the Browns and Jets on tap over the next two weeks, it’s safe to say the Ravens can afford to be without Humphrey if he does opt for surgery. Humphrey has struggled in coverage this season, allowing 32 receptions for 461 yards and two touchdowns on 45 targets, but did notch his first interception of the season in Week 10’s win over the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f6f-d673-a39e-efff12140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Isiah Pacheco (knee) “may take more time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f7f-d45b-affe-7fff92270000</link>
      <description>Don’t be surprised if we aren’t seeing Pacheco at practice this week, in other words. Coming off the bye, we were expecting to see Pacheco return to the lineup, but if that doesn’t happen, Kareem Hunt will be on the RB2/RB3 borderline against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f7f-d45b-affe-7fff92270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said MJ Stewart (quad) will be placed on season-ending injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f91-d673-a39e-ef9182e60000</link>
      <description>No surprise after Stewart was carted off. Myles Bryant replaced Stewart against the Jaguars in Week 10. It’s possible Jimmie Ward could eventually take the role after he recovers from foot surgery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f91-d673-a39e-ef9182e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles activated LB Nolan Smith ahead of Week 11’s game against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f79-d45b-affe-7fffb8f30000</link>
      <description>Smith suffered a triceps injury in Week 3’s win over the Rams and has been sidelined ever since. The third-year pro totaled 10 tackles and one forced fumble in the three games he appeared in this season, and totaled a career-high 6.5 tackles last season. He should immediately slot into his normal role on Monday night against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f79-d45b-affe-7fffb8f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Rich Cimini reports Garrett Wilson will miss 3-4 weeks with a knee sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb1-d673-a39e-efb152f30000</link>
      <description>Wilson’s return from injury was cut short when he re-aggravated the same knee injury that forced him to the sidelines in Week 6 against the Broncos. It’s a tough blow for one of the league’s worst offenses, which will now look to guys like Adonai Mitchell, John Metchie, and Josh Reynolds to lead a pass offense that has been grounded for much of the season. A four-week absence would mean Wilson could have a chance to suit up in Week 15 against the Jaguars. Given the current state of the Jets’ season, it will be interesting to see if the team opts to play him when healthy or sideline him for the rest of another lost season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb1-d673-a39e-efb152f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nick Wagoner believes “it’s clear the 49ers don’t intend to make [Brock] Purdy active again until he’s healthy enough to reclaim his starting job.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb4-d673-a39e-efb5f85d0000</link>
      <description>So here are the facts on the ground: After the Giants game last week, Kyle Shanahan “acknowledged that Purdy likely wouldn’t return to full health at any point this season as he deals with turf toe.” Shanahan later said “Our dilemma or what we’re trying not to do is put him out in the situation we did versus Jacksonville six weeks ago ... I do believe he’s closer and further along than what he was at that time. Hopefully he’ll have a chance this week.” What does it mean to be healthy enough? Purdy certainly didn’t play well against the Jaguars in Week 4. But if he’s never going to be fully healthy again this season, it doesn’t take an expert between-the-lines reader to see a scenario where Mac Jones simply keeps starting every week. Especially if the 49ers continue losing and fall out of playoff contention. We’re not saying that this is what is going to happen. But it shouldn’t be surprising if the 49ers continue to start Jones. As Wagoner puts it: “Purdy could, hypothetically, reach 90% health but is that better than Jones at full strength? It would be easy enough for the 49ers to continue riding with Jones given the possibility Purdy could struggle or, worse, reaggravate the toe injury again.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb4-d673-a39e-efb5f85d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills HC Sean McDermott said he will continue to stick with Joe Brady as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb9-d713-ad9e-6ffd91460000</link>
      <description>A 13-point performance against a bad Dolphins team is just the latest flop for a Bills team that has scored 20 or fewer points in its three losses this season. Brady replaced offensive coordinator Ken Dorsey during the 2023 season and helped fix an offense that was falling well short of what we’d expect from a Josh Allen-led attack. Now, it’s Brady’s offense that’s struggling to take advantage of Allen’s skillset, as the Bills currently rank 23rd in deep pass attempts and 24th in dropbacks through the first 10 weeks of the season. At some point, Brady should lean more into his MVP quarterback who ranks in the top six among his peers in both EPA per dropback and offensive success rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6fb9-d713-ad9e-6ffd91460000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
