<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:01:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers placed OG Chandler Zavala (knee) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a034-deb6-a7fd-f3ff0e950000</link>
      <description>Zavala will miss at least four games on IR after picking up the knee injury in Week 4 against the Patriots. It’s yet another blow to a Carolina offensive line graded by Pro Football Focus as the NFL’s 12th worst pass-blocking unit. Bryce Young could be under even more duress in the coming weeks with Zavala sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a034-deb6-a7fd-f3ff0e950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Jalen Coker (quad) is eligible for the active roster in Week 5.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a03c-dca3-a9fb-bdbd02550000</link>
      <description>Coker, according to head coach Dave Canales, is still considered week to week as he works his way back from a serious quad injury he sustained in late August, just after the team had committed to him as their full-time slot wideout. A fantasy folk hero of sorts due mostly to his last name, Coker last year had 32 catches for 478 yards and two touchdowns in Carolina. When Coker is able to return, he should instantly be the Panthers’ No. 2 receiver, though he should remain on 12-team league waiver wires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a03c-dca3-a9fb-bdbd02550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox Sports’ Greg Auman reports Bucky Irving (ankle) was seen Wednesday with crutches and a walking boot.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a040-dca3-a9fb-bdd9cfd60000</link>
      <description>This report along with a Tuesday report that Irving is “gathering medical opinions” on the ankle/foot injury he sustained in Week 4 against the Eagles suggest a potential long-term absence for Tampa’s No. 1 back. Unless Irving is able to shed the boot and practice Thursday or Friday, Rachaad White will likely step into the team’s RB1 role in Week 5 against the Seahawks. White would be a top-20 fantasy option in that role thanks largely to his pass-game involvement. Sean Tucker would serve as the Bucs’ RB2 and could take goal line touches from White if Irving is sidelined. Tucker should be rostered in deeper formats this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a040-dca3-a9fb-bdd9cfd60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) is “in question” for Week 5 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a057-dca3-a9fb-bddfeb270000</link>
      <description>Schefter added that the injury — sustained near the end of last Thursday’s loss to the Seahawks — “is not thought to be serious,” though it could limit him this week in practice and could cost him Week 5. Benson in Week 4 operated as the team’s lead back with James Conner (ankle) done for the season. He lost most pass-catching duties to Emari Demercado, however, who would slide in to Arizona’s RB1 role should Benson be sidelined this week. Demercado should be rostered in all leagues in case Benson sits. He would make for a solid flex option against a porous Tennessee defense allowing the seventh most rushing yards in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a057-dca3-a9fb-bddfeb270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bucky Irving’s foot sprain is not expected to be a long-term injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a07e-dca3-a9fb-bdff5d6b0000</link>
      <description>The sprain, per Schefter, is a “week to week” injury. It could keep Irving sidelined in Week 5 against Seattle after Tampa’s lead back was seen in a walking boot on Wednesday. Irving is reportedly seeking medical opinions this week. If he sits in Week 5, Rachaad White would serve as Tampa’s RB1 with Sean Tucker possibly taking a solid RB2 role behind White.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a07e-dca3-a9fb-bdff5d6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said RB Braelon Allen’s knee injury is “pretty serious.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a092-d6e9-af9d-aa92b92d0000</link>
      <description>Allen picked up the knee injury on a kick return in Week 4 against the Dolphins. Glenn said Allen is seeking secondary medical opinions on the injury before the team makes a decision on how much time he’ll miss. If it’s a season ending injury, Breece Hall should see a bump in weekly touches and perhaps goal line usage. Isaiah Davis, meanwhile, would likely operate as the Jets’ No. 2 back and should be rostered in 12-team leagues. Davis had five touches for 28 yards in Week 4 with Allen sidelined for much of the contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a092-d6e9-af9d-aa92b92d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Daniels (knee) was medically cleared to return to practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0a0-dca3-a9fb-bdb9aa0c0000</link>
      <description>Daniels is expected to log a full practice Wednesday after missing the past two weeks with a knee injury he picked up in Week 2. Barring any practice setbacks, Daniels should be under center for the Commanders in Week 5 against a tough Chargers defense. His return to the lineup will be welcome news for Deebo Samuel and Zach Ertz, who should remain in fantasy lineups in a potential back-and-forth affair.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0a0-dca3-a9fb-bdb9aa0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans opened the three-week practice window for Tyjae Spears (ankle).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0a3-dca3-a9fb-bdbb47260000</link>
      <description>Spears could return to game action as early as this week against the Cardinals if he’s able to practice in the coming days. His presence in the Titans backfield could be a hit to Tony Pollard’s weekly fantasy prospects. Pollard through four games has accounted for 68 of the Titans’ 73 running backs rushes while catching six of nine targets. It’s hard to get excited about anyone in a dumpster fire of a Tennessee offense, but Spears is a decent pick up in deeper leagues in case Pollard misses any time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-a0a3-dca3-a9fb-bdbb47260000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
