<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 22:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dawson Knox caught 1-of-2 targets for 10 yards in the Bills’ Week 16 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e0-dc7a-af9b-cfff56730000</link>
      <description>Knox’s most memorable play was the one he didn’t make. Facing a fourth-and-one on the Browns’ 11-yard line, Knox broke free in the end zone for what should have been an easy touchdown. Instead, the veteran tight end bobbled Josh Allen’s pass to squander any hopes the Bills had of scoring a touchdown in the second half. Knox can be left on fantasy benches in Week 17’s game against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e0-dc7a-af9b-cfff56730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Addison caught 2-of-3 targets for 26 yards in the Vikings’ Week 16 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42d8-dc7a-af9b-cfff6ba70000</link>
      <description>Addison notably dropped a deep touchdown from J.J. McCarthy in the first half. The throw was arguably short and forced Addison to tumble to the ground to make the catch, but it’s a grab any professional receiver should come down with. Normally a touchdown-scoring specialist, Addisionhasn’t found the end zone since Week 11. He has just three scores all year. Addison will be relegated to the WR4 ranks for Week 17 against the Lions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42d8-dc7a-af9b-cfff6ba70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Olave caught 10-of-16 targets for 148 yards and two touchdowns in the Saints’ Week 16 win against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e2-d35e-a1bf-47e2dbc40000</link>
      <description>Olave over the past two weeks has turned his air yards domination into actual fantasy production, which is nice. Tyler Shough, who had 308 yards on the day, targeted Olave relentlessly from start to finish against a Jets secondary that has been shredded in recent weeks. Olave caught one touchdown from Shough and one from 35-year-old gadget player Taysom Hill, who functioned as the centerpiece of the Saints offense for some reason. Olave’s domination of targets and air yards in the New Orleans offense gives him weekly top-10 upside. He’ll get the Titans in Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e2-d35e-a1bf-47e2dbc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chuba Hubbard rushed six times for 27 yards in the Panthers’ Week 16 win over the Buccaneers, adding one reception for seven yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42df-d087-addf-f3ff71060000</link>
      <description>Hubbard continues to play second fiddle to Rico Dowdle, seeing seven touches to Dowdle’s 13 touches. His first carry came in the red zone, where he rushed for a loss of two yards. With Dowdle also getting work in the two-minute drill and passing game, it is difficult to find a path to fantasy usage for Hubbard. He is a risky FLEX play for Week 17 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42df-d087-addf-f3ff71060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught 4-of-5 targets for 34 yards in the Bills’ Week 16 win over the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e4-da28-afbb-c6fd19e30000</link>
      <description>In a game that resulted in just 130 passing yards for the Bills, Shakir led the team in receptions, yards, and targets. His biggest gain of the day came on an 18-yard reception to help set up James Cook for an eventual touchdown, but this was easily one of Shakir’s most forgettable outings of the season. He’ll be hard to trust as anything more than a WR3 in Week 17’s game against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e4-da28-afbb-c6fd19e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raheim Sanders rushed 11 times for 42 yards in the Browns’ Week 16 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e6-d35e-a1bf-47e6d4040000</link>
      <description>Sanders saw most of his opportunities after Quinshon Judkins (leg/ankle) left in the second quarter. Sanders’ 11 carries wound up leading all Browns players on Sunday, but it was Trayveon Williams who served as the primary pass-catching back sans Judkins. Sanders saw eight of his 11 carries come on the Browns’ seventh possession of the game, and he felt a yard shy of a rushing touchdown that ended up being converted by Harold Fannin on the following play. Sanders could have some upside in Week 17 against the Steelers, but that will largely hinge on whether or not Dylan Sampson (hand) is able to get on the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e6-d35e-a1bf-47e6d4040000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught his only target for two yards in the Vikings’ Week 16 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e4-d35e-a1bf-47e69d540000</link>
      <description>Hockenson popped up for a usable fantasy outing last week, catching four balls for 66 yards. He came crashing back to Earth today with his worst outing of the year. Hockenson has been held under 20 yards in five of his past eight games. He can be left out of starting fantasy lineups heading into Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e4-d35e-a1bf-47e69d540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals ruled out CB Garrett Williams (Achilles) in Week 16 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42ab-dc7a-af9b-cfbff6310000</link>
      <description>Williams backpedaled in coverage, pivoted to his right and attempted to push off his left leg. Instead, the leg gave out. Williams looked behind him, seemingly investigating whether an opponent had made contact with his lower body. He then began hopping on his right leg, unable to put weight on his left leg. Sadly, this was a fairly straightforward Achilles tendon rupture. He was eventually carted away after the trainers met with him on the field. Williams recorded three pass breakups and one interception this season. Cardinals EDGE Josh Sweat (ankle) is questionable to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42ab-dc7a-af9b-cfbff6310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tetairoa McMillan caught 6-of-10 targets for 73 yards and a touchdown in the Panthers’ Week 16 win over the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e7-da28-afbb-c6ff330a0000</link>
      <description>After a few low-volume weeks, McMillan was back to double-digit target volume against the Buccaneers. He operated as the team’s lead wideout and saw multiple end zone targets. Bryce Young was able to find McMillan to convert on one of those end zone targets for a 22-yard score at the end of the first half. Coming off foot/ankle injuries from this past week, McMillan was not hampered by the issues and finishes with 73 receiving yards on his ten targets. He profiles as a fantasy WR2 for Week 17 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42e7-da28-afbb-c6ff330a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max Brosmer completed 7-of-9 passes for 52 yards in the Vikings’ 16-13, Week 16 win over the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42ea-da28-afbb-c6ffdabd0000</link>
      <description>Brosmer took over for J.J. McCarthy after halftime. The latter suffered a hand injury on his final snap of the first half and was quickly ruled out. Per The Minnesota Star Tribune’s Ben Goessling, McCarthy is not believed to have suffered any broken bones. He will undergo further testing on Monday. Brosmer will likely draw the start in Week 17, though McCarthy can’t be ruled out entirely just yet. Neither quarterback will be on the QB2 radar for the final week of the fantasy football season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-42ea-da28-afbb-c6ffdabd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
