<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 18:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers opened the 21-day practice window for WR Jalen Coker (quad).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4be-d94a-a79d-cdbf1e800000</link>
      <description>Coker will now have three weeks before the team must activate him to the game day roster. He could play as soon as Week 6 against the Cowboys, a good matchup against one of the league’s worst coverage units. Coker, who had 32 catches for 478 yards and two touchdowns in 2024, would immediately function as Carolina’s WR2 when he’s activated. He should be rostered in deeper leagues as a viable flex option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4be-d94a-a79d-cdbf1e800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Giants RB Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) is “good to go” for Week 6 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4c2-def2-abdb-dde30ac90000</link>
      <description>Tracy has missed the past three weeks with a shoulder injury but should return to action on Thursday night against the Eagles. Tracy could eat into Cam Skattebo’s workload and make him more of a top-20 option than the top-12 option he’s been over the past few games. Skattebo should continue working as the pass-catching back, however.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4c2-def2-abdb-dde30ac90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Joe Flacco will start in Week 6 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4c0-dd4c-afb9-e7c1e7c30000</link>
      <description>The Bengals pulled the plug on Jake Browning after three disastrous starts. They traded for Flacco earlier this week and the journeyman will make his debut on the road against a stout Green Bay defense. It’s a tough spot for a quarterback who just joined the team, but Flacco is no stranger to spot-starts. Flacco is only a low-end QB2 for his first game as a Bengal, but his addition should boost the floors of Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins. Both receivers were struggling to put up usable fantasy scores under Browning until they padded their box scores in garbage time last week. Flacco will look to get them going before the fourth quarter in Week 6.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4c0-dd4c-afb9-e7c1e7c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders coach Dan Quinn said Terry McLaurin (quad) will not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4ce-d94a-a79d-cdcf774b0000</link>
      <description>Quinn told reporters on Monday that he was optimistic about McLaurin playing in Week 6. While there is still a chance the veteran wideout returns to practice later this week and suits up on Sunday, that doesn’t look likely at this point. Barring a surprise, Deebo Samuel will continue to operate as the team’s top wideout. Samuel has 14 receptions for 168 yards and two scores over the past two weeks. He is working his way up the WR2 ranks heading into his Week 6 date with the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4ce-d94a-a79d-cdcf774b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields (knee) is practicing in full for Week 6 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4d5-d94a-a79d-cddd63cf0000</link>
      <description>A full practice means Fields isn’t at risk of missing Week 6, but it’s always notable when a quarterback is added to the injury report, especially one who relies on his legs as much as Fields does. Fields is currently the QB4 by points per game, though his fantasy success hasn’t translated to anything resembling success for the franchise. The Jets are currently the lone winless team in the NFL. Even if he is dealing with a slight knee issue, Fields will run plenty in Week 6 against the Broncos, keeping him near the top of the QB1 ranks despite a tough matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4d5-d94a-a79d-cddd63cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals placed TE Tip Reiman (leg) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4da-dd4c-afb9-e7dbdac30000</link>
      <description>Reiman went down with a gruesome leg injury in Week 5 against the Titans. He was immediately placed in an air cast and carted to the locker room. Reiman doesn’t do much that fantasy managers care about, but he is an integral part of Arizona’s offense as a blocker. He has played on 37 percent of the team’s offensive snaps this year and contributes on special teams. The Cardinals have Elijah Higgins and Travis Vokolek on the roster as potential replacements for Reiman. Vokolek profiles as a more similar player to Reiman than Higgins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4da-dd4c-afb9-e7dbdac30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor announced Joe Flacco as the team’s starting quarterback for Week 6 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4e1-d94a-a79d-cded297f0000</link>
      <description>Browning was doomed to a QB2 role once the Bengals traded for Joe Flacco earlier this week. He had eight interceptions in less than four full games this year. The Bengals were 0-3 with Browning at the helm. They were out-scored 37-113 in his three starts. Flacco has also struggled to start the year, but he should at least give the Bengals a higher weekly floor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4e1-d94a-a79d-cded297f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson (hamstring) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4e8-def2-abdb-dde956f40000</link>
      <description>Per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, Jackson is reportedly facing “an uphill battle” to play in Week 6. A DNP on Wednesday confirms that report and all but rules Jackson out for Sunday’s game. Barring a surprise, Cooper Rush should make his second start as a Raven, though Tyler Huntley is also an option for the team. Rush imploded in his first start, throwing for 179 yards and three interceptions in a blowout loss to the Texans. We don’t have high hopes for the offense no matter who draws the start versus the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4e8-def2-abdb-dde956f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Marlon Humphrey (calf) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4f0-dd4c-afb9-e7f167bd0000</link>
      <description>Linebacker Roquan Smith and fellow corner Chidobe Awuzie both missed Wednesday’s practice with hamstring injuries. With Lamar Jackson unlikely to play this week, the Ravens may ultimately choose to sit the bulk of their injured players for a likely loss to the Rams on Sunday. They then get their bye week, allowing them to return close to full strength for Week 8 versus the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4f0-dd4c-afb9-e7f167bd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Tavion Sanders (ankle) returned to practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4f6-db72-a199-feff541a0000</link>
      <description>It’s presumably a limited session for Sanders, but that’s still a step in the right direction as he works his way back from the high-ankle sprain he suffered in Week 3. Mitchell Evans and Tommy Tremble have combined for three touchdowns over the past two weeks. It’s possible all three see the field once Sanders is healthy. This is largely a situation to avoid for fantasy purposes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-c4f6-db72-a199-feff541a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
