<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 23:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ka’imi Fairbairn made 2-of-2 field goals in the Texans’ Week 13 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6eb-db57-afda-d6fb72730000</link>
      <description>Neither of his kicks were all that dramatic. It appeared to the naked eye that Fairbairn missed an extra point on Houston’s second touchdown, but the referee signaled that it was good and that isn’t a reviewable play. Colts fans were not happy. Fairbairn remains a solid K1 play on an offense that relies on his contributions since they have zero red zone game to speak of.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6eb-db57-afda-d6fb72730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Jeudy caught 3-of-4 targets for 26 yards in the Browns’ Week 13 loss against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ec-d82c-a79a-f7fc8a1e0000</link>
      <description>Jeudy was second on the team behind Harold Fannin in targets in another run-heavy game for the Browns. Jeudy was seen chastising QB Shedeur Sanders on the sideline following a miscommunication between the two in the second half, a sign of persistent frustration among Browns pass catchers trapped in an offense without a viable starting quarterback. Jeudy shouldn’t be started in 12-team leagues next week against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ec-d82c-a79a-f7fc8a1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Queen is questionable to return to Week 13 against the Bills with a hip injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ed-db57-afda-d6ff19af0000</link>
      <description>One play after Patrick Queen sparked a near-brawl in the second quarter with a questionable hit on Josh Allen, the linebacker went down after a carry by James Cook. He limped off the field and into the blue medical tent before going back into the locker room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ed-db57-afda-d6ff19af0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tony Pollard rushed 10 times for 60 yards and a fumble in the Titans’ Week 13 loss to the Jaguars, adding one reception for three yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6e8-db57-afda-d6fa7b520000</link>
      <description>In a blowout loss, Pollard saw one less snap than Tyjae Spears, though he still saw two more touches than Spears. Pollard began the game with three carries for 36 yards, picking up three first downs on the Titans’ opening drive. However, the Titans went down quickly and the run game was abandoned. To rub more salt into the wound, Pollard fumbled on a garbage time possession late in the fourth quarter. Volume in his lead back role keeps Pollard in the fantasy RB3 range for Week 14 against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6e8-db57-afda-d6fa7b520000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller caught 2-of-3 targets for 47 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 13 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ea-d6c4-abfb-d6eb52e40000</link>
      <description>Waller was responsible for the Dolphins’ biggest play of the game, a 34-yard strike down the sideline that set up a field goal in the second quarter. A few big plays are all you could ask for from Waller after coming off injured reserve over the weekend. He hadn’t played since Week 7 heading into today’s game. Waller’s role should increase over the next few weeks, but it wouldn’t be a surprise to see him continue to split reps with Greg Dulcich. Waller will be stuck in the TE2 ranks for for Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ea-d6c4-abfb-d6eb52e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 4-of-8 targets for 42 yards in the Bucs’ Week 13 win over the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ec-d90e-a9da-dfef92e10000</link>
      <description>This has somehow become Egbuka’s standard statline of late. He didn’t help himself today with a rough third down drop on the Bucs’ opening series. Baker Mayfield also missed on a potential long gain down the seam. Egbuka is still commanding an impressive target share and maintaining a strong floor. The spiked weeks have just been too few and far between of late. He does have a plus Week 14 matchup in the Saints. He still belongs in every 12-team league lineup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6ec-d90e-a9da-dfef92e10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cedric Tillman did not catch his only target in the Browns’ Week 13 loss against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6f4-db57-afda-d6f6620f0000</link>
      <description>Tillman ran a pass route on 23 of the Browns’ 29 drop backs in a game that saw the run-first Browns throw just 28 passes. Tillman now has seven receptions over his past four games as the WR3 for Cleveland. He should remain on waiver wires ahead of the Browns’ Week 14 game against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6f4-db57-afda-d6f6620f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyjae Spears rushed two times for a loss of a yard in the Titans’ Week 13 loss to the Jaguars, adding six receptions for 25 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6f4-d6c4-abfb-d6f731ed0000</link>
      <description>Spears was more involved with the Titans trailing for the majority of the game against the Jaguars. He out-snapped Tony Pollard by one total snap, catching all six of his targets in the passing game. Spears keeps a fantasy scoring floor due to his passing game usage, but his ceiling is capped with the lack of scoring from the anemic Titans offense. He is a touchdown-dependent FLEX play for Week 14 against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6f4-d6c4-abfb-d6f731ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Bond caught 1-of-2 targets for 18 yards in the Browns’ Week 13 loss against the 49ers, adding one rush for nine yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6f8-d90e-a9da-dfff25010000</link>
      <description>Bond followed up his impressive Week 12 performance — two catches for 58 yards — with something of a dud, though no one put up great numbers in the lifeless Cleveland offense. Bond ran a route on just 13 of the Browns’ 30 drop backs. He’ll be a deep league flex option in Week 14 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-d6f8-d90e-a9da-dfff25010000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
