<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 04:02:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Packers DL Micah Parsons (back) “is expected to play” in Week 1 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16f6-d332-a1fd-96f630720000</link>
      <description>Rapoport relayed his source’s info, saying, Parsons’ facet sprain is something he “needs to take some medicine for” and that an “epidural could potentially await him if he keeps having problems with it.” Shot or not, Parsons is all but guaranteed to be on the field when the Packers host the Lions on Sunday. The Packers face Parsons’ former Cowboys squad in Week 4, and play the Browns in Week 3. The Packers’ D/ST could be a high-scoring unit, racking up sacks aplenty both weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16f6-d332-a1fd-96f630720000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared QB Tanner McKee, EDGE Azeez Ojulari, EDGE Ogbo Okoronkwo, OL Drew Kendall, OT Cameron Williams, OL Kenyon Green and DT Ty Robinson inactive for Week 1 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fcae-d332-a1fd-febec9da0000</link>
      <description>McKee had been set to be Jalen Hurts’ backup before breaking his throwing thumb late in training camp. No. 2 duties now belong to Sam Howell. Beyond that, this is a mercifully quiet early-season injury list for the defending-champion Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fcae-d332-a1fd-febec9da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16fe-dbe3-a9bb-36ffdebe0000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez is highly unlikely to play at this point, having rehabbed this hamstring injury for more than a month. Raiders WR Jakobi Meyers’ day would be considerably easier if Gonzalez were unable to go. Patriots OT Will Campbell was also added to the injury report with an ankle injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-16fe-dbe3-a9bb-36ffdebe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian McCaffrey (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1717-db7b-a5dd-b71728c50000</link>
      <description>Teams often give veteran players, particularly older running backs, days off at the first sign of irritation or discomfort, so it is entirely possible this is simply the 49ers acting out of an abundance of caution. McCaffrey does have a history of calf and Achilles tendon issues dating back to Week 17, 2023, so managing his practice load is prudent. Tomorrow’s injury report should help clarify his Week 1 status. In the meantime, fantasy managers are advised to pickup Brian Robinson if he available in free agency. McCaffrey typically makes himself available to the media on Thursday, after practice, but the veteran running back was reportedly absent this afternoon. He could be undergoing treatment or even imaging. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1717-db7b-a5dd-b71728c50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams CB Ahkello Witherspoon (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-170a-dbe3-a9bb-375ba8180000</link>
      <description>Witherspoon is a new addition to the injury report today. The veteran cornerback is currently penciled in as a starter on the perimeter. Although the Texans will be without No. 2 WR Christian Kirk (hamstring), Rams cornerbacks still have the tall task of covering Nico Collins. Witherspoon’s absence could be consequential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-170a-dbe3-a9bb-375ba8180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1734-de13-afdd-57ff21e50000</link>
      <description>The 49ers are smartly easing Jennings back into action following an extended absence. Head coach Kyle Shanahan has already said he expects Jennings to play in Week 1 against the Seahawks, and the front office added $3 million in play-time incentives to Jennings’ contract yesterday. He’s a WR4 against Seattle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1734-de13-afdd-57ff21e50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Jordan James (finger) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1738-d332-a1fd-973eb2c20000</link>
      <description>James should be available for the 49ers at this point, if they need him against the Seahawks on Sunday. Christian McCaffrey notably appeared on the injury report with a calf injury today, and although there is no reason to panic, it’s good to be familiar with the 49ers’ RB depth chart. James currently sits fourth behind Brian Robinson and Isaac Guerendo. 49ers rookie WR Jordan Watkins (ankle) returned to practice in a limited capacity today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1738-d332-a1fd-973eb2c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (ankle) is practicing in full for Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1740-de13-afdd-57cb03c80000</link>
      <description>Horton’s preseason showing, operating as the Seahawks’ field-stretcher, made Marquez Valdes-Scantling irrelevant. The exciting rookie will be on the field for Seattle’s Week 1 game against the 49ers. Unfortunately, his role will probably be too unreliable to put him in fantasy lineups, but he’s a player worth keeping an eye on as the season progresses. He will likely be involved as a returner as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1740-de13-afdd-57cb03c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter was ejected from Thursday’s Week 1 game against the Cowboys for spitting on Dak Prescott.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-171e-dbe3-a9bb-375ffb860000</link>
      <description>Stupefying. As the players and refs milled about the field following an Eagles special teams injury on the opening kickoff, Carter began jawing with Prescott literally right in front of a ref. He then spit on the quarterback and was instantly ejected. Mortifying, foolish behavior from one of the Eagles’ most important players. The de facto one-game suspension means Carter is unlikely to face further discipline, but the Eagles’ coaching staff figures to be shaking its collective head for weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-171e-dbe3-a9bb-375ffb860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles FB Ben VanSumeren has been ruled out of Philadelphia’s Week 1 game against the Cowboys with a knee injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1757-dbe3-a9bb-37579d480000</link>
      <description>A lead blocker trying to get a toehold on special teams, VanSumeren appeared to blow out his right knee on the game’s opening kick. Not good. The 25-year-old managed just 22 snaps on offense last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1757-dbe3-a9bb-37579d480000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
