<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers waived QB Clayton Tune.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9523-dc7a-af9b-dfbf4e640000</link>
      <description>Over three seasons with the Cardinals and Packers, Tune is 21-of-38 for 112 scoreless yards, three interceptions, and has taken 12 sacks. On the bright side, he still has his youth. The Packers decided to add Desmond Ridder to the playoff roster over Tune. We don’t think anything we can say would be meaner than that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9523-dc7a-af9b-dfbf4e640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed LB Kyzir White off the Titans practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9525-d56e-afff-f7edc56d0000</link>
      <description>White gives the 49ers some emergency depth for the playoffs with Tatum Bethune hurt. The 49ers finished Week 18 with Eric Kendricks and Garret Wallow at linebacker and won’t get Fred Warner back until the NFC Championship, at earliest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9525-d56e-afff-f7edc56d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills signed K Matthew Wright to their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-952a-d35e-a1bf-d5ea1e220000</link>
      <description>Your latest Matt Prater potential replacement has arrived. Wright will kick against the Jaguars in the Wild Card round should Prater be unavailable. Wright is 5-for-5 on field goals and 4-of-4 on extra points between three teams this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-952a-d35e-a1bf-d5ea1e220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions fired OC John Morton.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-954d-d35e-a1bf-d5cfa4da0000</link>
      <description>Just five days ago, Morton said he wanted to say with the team even in a lesser role. Dan Campbell, who took over playcalling duties from Morton midseason, apparently did not agree to this arrangement. Morton will probably catch on elsewhere lower on the ladder in 2026, perhaps back in Denver with Sean Payton.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-954d-d35e-a1bf-d5cfa4da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants, Cardinals, and Raiders have all requested an interview with Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak for their head-coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-954f-d35e-a1bf-d5cff3850000</link>
      <description>These are in addition to a Falcons interview we heard about yesterday, making Kubiak one of the hottest head-coaching candidates of the offseason. Seattle’s 10th-ranked DVOA offense with Sam Darnold, as well as Kubiak’s ability to scheme so much of his offense around star wideout Jaxon Smith-Njigba, have apparently drawn plenty of attention. Kubiak, on bye, is also available to interview right away, which doesn’t hurt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-954f-d35e-a1bf-d5cff3850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens fired head coach John Harbaugh.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9562-dc7a-af9b-dfff2b3e0000</link>
      <description>To say that this year was a stunning fall from grace for the Ravens almost undersells it. They were consensus Super Bowl preseason favorites, and couldn’t even finish with enough wins to manage a playoff spot in a league where seven teams from each conference make the playoffs. And while a few of those losses came during Weeks 4-6 when essentially everyone important on the team was hurt, Harbaugh’s Ravens choked away leads left and right this season as well. They lost to the Bills in Week 1 when they entered the fourth quarter with a 34-19 lead. They allowed 15 fourth-quarter points to the Patriots to lose in Week 16. They lost twice to the Steelers in games they absolutely needed, even with Lamar Jackson finding Zay Flowers for a pair of 50-yard touchdown strikes in the fourth quarter of the finale. Harbaugh is an objectively great football coach, with a 180-113 career record and a Super Bowl win. He’ll instantly vault to the top of the coaching carousel. But the level of cursed that the Ravens felt this year meant that something, somewhere, was going to have to change. And in this case, the Ravens felt it should be the head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9562-dc7a-af9b-dfff2b3e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (knee) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9574-d968-a19b-ddf527860000</link>
      <description>It’s a walkthrough estimation, but we’re not overly concerned about a limited session from Moore. He played hurt several times this year through some nagging injuries, and a limited session on Tuesday suggests he’s well in line to play in Saturday’s Wild Card game against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9574-d968-a19b-ddf527860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) was limited in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9575-d56e-afff-f7fdaa2f0000</link>
      <description>Odunze practiced on Friday of last week, and while this is not a sure sign he’ll be ready for Saturday’s game against the Packers, it’s certainly a promising start of the week. This is an estimation, so we’ll probably get better confirmation later. It is worth noting that Caleb Williams addressed a question about Odunze’s return as if it was going to happen — he’d know better than we would, of course.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9575-d56e-afff-f7fdaa2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports a “key pressure point” in John Harbaugh’s firing was “his refusal to entertain” moving on from OC Todd Monken.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9582-d968-a19b-ddf3e53f0000</link>
      <description>In other words, ownership wanted to make some changes there. John Harbaugh wanted to run it back. It’s probably not the only reason that the Ravens moved on from the the 63-year-old Super Bowl champion, but it happened to be a big one. Monken had reportedly interviewed for the Michigan head coach job, among others, and is still regarded highly across the football landscape. Russini also reports that Kliff Kingsbury is “a name to watch” in Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9582-d968-a19b-ddf3e53f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
