<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 02:36:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Luke Musgrave caught 4-of-6 targets for 52 yards in the Packers’ Week 15 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fbc-d005-a9bf-dfbc5b1b0000</link>
      <description>The six targets Musgrave saw on Sunday set a new season high, as did his 52 receiving yards. Musgrave’s production saw a nice boost, thanks in part to a 26-yard reception on the Packers’ second drive of the game. Sunday’s game against the Broncos marked the first time this season that Musgrave has surpassed 34 receiving yards. He can be left on waivers for Week 16’s game against the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fbc-d005-a9bf-dfbc5b1b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audric Estime rushed three times for 11 yards in the Saints’ Week 15 win over the Panthers, adding three receptions for 39 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f9b-d77b-adfb-df9b81200000</link>
      <description>Saints RB Devin Neal exited with a hamstring injury, allowing Estime to get involved as a receiver while RB Evan Hull ran four times for 12 yards. Estime ran like a rhinoceros after the catch, churning his legs through contact after securing two screen passes and one checkdown target. Veteran RB Alvin Kamara (ankle/knee) has not yet resumed practicing. Estime could warrant RB3/FLEX consideration against the Jets in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f9b-d77b-adfb-df9b81200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matthew Golden caught 3-of-4 targets for 55 yards in the Packers’ Week 15 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fc0-d77b-adfb-dfc36a7f0000</link>
      <description>Golden tied with Jayden Reed for the team-high in receiving yards in Sunday’s loss, and drew a 25-yard DPI on Riley Moss in the third quarter to keep a drive alive. That drive ended with a 40-yard touchdown run by Josh Jacobs on the following play. Golden continues to show flashes in his rookie season but has yet to live up to the billing that made him the no. 23 overall pick in this year’s draft. Fantasy managers can avoid him in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fc0-d77b-adfb-dfc36a7f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Walker had nine rushes for 17 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 15 win against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fc3-d1bc-a3fb-9fe7b04e0000</link>
      <description>A week after posting just 29 yards on ten rushing attempts against the Falcons, Walker was ineffective once again against a middling Colts rush defense. Zach Charbonnet, meanwhile, had eight rushes for 31 yards and ran 16 pass routes to 14 routes for Walker. With one rushing touchdown since Week 4 and no path to consistent pass game usage in the balanced Seattle offense, Walker is barely usable in any fantasy format. The Seahawks backfield is perfectly formulated to destroy all potential fantasy value. They play the Rams in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fc3-d1bc-a3fb-9fe7b04e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo Doubs caught 2-of-3 targets for 36 yards in the Packers’ Week 15 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fc5-d77b-adfb-dfc720a30000</link>
      <description>Doubs only saw three targets in this one, but the fourth-year receiver could see a bigger workload in Week 16 if Christian Watson (chest) is unable to go. Earlier this season, when Watson was recovering from a knee injury, Doubs saw eight or more targets in three games and finished as a top-36 PPR receiver in four of those outings. He’s a highly volatile player, but may find himself on the radar as a FLEX play if Watson can’t go against the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fc5-d77b-adfb-dfc720a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Kupp caught 5-of-7 targets for 46 yards in the Seahawks’ Week 15 win against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fc9-d8cf-affb-bfeba7220000</link>
      <description>It was another low-volume outing for the Seahawks’ pass offense, and Kupp was an afterthought behind Jaxon Smith-Njigba, as usual. Kupp was third in receiving yards behind JSN and Rasheed Shahid, who had 74 yards. Kupp, who has more than 50 receiving yards in just three games this season, profiles as a desperation second flex option for Week 16 against the Rams, his former team. He had 23 yards on three receptions the last time Seattle played the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fc9-d8cf-affb-bfeba7220000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryce Young completed 15-of-24 passes for 163 yards and one touchdown in the Panthers’ 20-17, Week 15 loss to the Saints, rushing seven times for 49 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fbb-d1bc-a3fb-9fbf85050000</link>
      <description>Young was up-and-down as a passer. He threw a nifty sidearm completion to TE Tommy Tremble for eight yards to get around the Saints’ leaping DE Cam Jordan on the Panthers’ second drive. On the next drive, he connected with WR Jalen Coker on a 24-yard corner route before connecting with WR Tetairoa McMillan for 21 yards. He nearly connected with McMillan again for a long touchdown, but the pass was off the mark and Saints CB Quincy Riley batted it down. Riley showed up again on the Panthers’ fourth drive, dropping an easy interception in coverage against WR Xavier Legette. A few plays later, Young found Coker for a 32-yard touchdown down the right sideline, impressively releasing the ball before Coker had fully separated from Riley. Young also scrambled very effectively here, averaging 7.0 yards per carry. He is a QB2 against the Buccaneers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fbb-d1bc-a3fb-9fbf85050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs caught 3-of-5 targets for 13 yards and a touchdown in the Colts’ Week 15 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fd1-d77b-adfb-dfd35d6e0000</link>
      <description>Downs, a natural short-area target for the weak-armed Philip Rivers — who made his first start since 2020 in Week 15 — saw a bump in playing time against the Seahawks, running 26 routes on 31 Colts drop backs. He caught Rivers’ lone touchdown on the day, getting open in the back of the end zone. If Downs maintains this route participation he could be an interesting deep league option in Week 16 against the a Niners secondary that has been generous to opposing slot receivers all season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fd1-d77b-adfb-dfd35d6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alec Pierce caught his lone target for 16 yards in the Colts’ Week 15 loss against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fd5-d77b-adfb-dfd7d4480000</link>
      <description>Pierce was always going to be a loser of the Colts’ Philip Rivers experiment. Pierce generally operates as an intermediate and deep target, and he now has a 44-year-old quarterback who is physically unable to throw it more than 20 yards or so. Pierce’s lone grab in Week 15 came near the sideline; Pierce boxed out his defender and made a nice grab on a floater from the weak-armed Rivers. Pierce isn’t fantasy viable for as long as Rivers is under center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fd5-d77b-adfb-dfd7d4480000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen Coker caught 4-of-4 targets for 60 yards, one touchdown and one fumble lost in the Panthers’ Week 15 loss to the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fd8-d1bc-a3fb-9ffce2080000</link>
      <description>Coker had a great game. He showed up on the Panthers’ first drive with a toe-tapping 15-yard catch along the left sideline. He hauled in a 24-yard pass on a corner route on the Panthers’ third drive and caught a 32-yard touchdown via hitch-and-go on the Panthers’ fourth drive. Though Coker often lines up in the slot, he scored the touchdown lined up out wide on the right side. Coker is a WR3/FLEX against the Buccaneers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1fd8-d1bc-a3fb-9ffce2080000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
