<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:29:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>David Montgomery rushed eight times for 32 yards and one touchdown in the Lions’ Week 13 loss to the Packers, adding two receptions for 16 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c796-db57-afda-d7b6e33c0000</link>
      <description>The Lions deployed Montgomery in the wildcat near the goal line in this one. The first sequence resulted in a successful run to the right for a three-yard touchdown. The Lions tried it again later, this time asking Montgomery to throw a pass to TE Ross Dwelley, but the two were unable to connect. Regardless, Montgomery was able to return FLEX-worthy numbers on Thanksgiving. Be thankful. He is a decent FLEX option in what should be a high-scoring game against the Cowboys next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c796-db57-afda-d7b6e33c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens declared WR Tylan Wallace, QB Cooper Rush, G Ben Cleveland, T Carson Vinson, and OLB David Ojabo inactive for Week 13 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c770-d6c4-abfb-d7739df90000</link>
      <description>There are no real surprises here as the Ravens enter Week 13 as one of the healthier teams in the league. They hunt for their sixth consecutive victory against their division rivals on Thanksgiving as they continue their bid for a late-season push towards the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c770-d6c4-abfb-d7739df90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals WR Tee Higgins is inactive for Week 13 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c7bb-db57-afda-d7bbad450000</link>
      <description>This is purely a formality after Higgins was ruled out on Monday, although the team does get both quarterback Joe Burrow and wide receiver Ja’Marr Chase back. also inactive for the Bengals are QB Jake Browning, RB Tahj Brooks, WR Jermaine Burton, TE Cam Grandy, DE Trey Hendrickson, and DE Cam Sample.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c7bb-db57-afda-d7bbad450000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes completed 23-of-34 passes for 261 yards and four touchdowns in the Chiefs’ 31-28, Week 13 loss to the Cowboys, adding 30 yards on three carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c7f9-d90e-a9da-dfff5ec30000</link>
      <description>Mahomes and the Chiefs found themselves in another fourth quarter hole from which to dig themselves out of, this time unable to replicate the late magic they showed against the Colts last week. His four touchdown tosses matched a season high set back in Week 4 against the Ravens, but their defense was unable to contain a Dallas offense that amassed a robust 457 total yards of offense. The loss drops the Chiefs to 6-6 and on the outside looking in on the playoff picture in the AFC. Mahomes and the Chiefs turn their attention to a tough Texans team in Week 14 in desperate need of a win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c7f9-d90e-a9da-dfff5ec30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco rushed three times for 16 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys, adding 17 yards on two receptions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c7ff-d90e-a9da-dffffee10000</link>
      <description>Pacheco was used sparingly in his return to the lineup following a three-game absence but looked fully healthy and spry when his number was called, with his 6.6 yards per opportunity handily leading the Kansas City backfield. Fantasy managers will need to remain patient with the speedy veteran as he works his way back into full health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c7ff-d90e-a9da-dffffee10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed 14 times for 58 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys, adding 22 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c803-d90e-a9da-df0f27260000</link>
      <description>Hunt remained the clear lead back with the return of Isiah Pacheco to the game-day roster, out-touching the younger back 15-to-5 in the loss. That said, he remains one of the more touchdown-dependent backs in the league considering the the pass-first nature of the Kansas City offense. He might also be forced to overcome fewer opportunities in the coming games as Pacheco works his way back into game shape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c803-d90e-a9da-df0f27260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice caught 8-of-12 targets for 92 yards and two touchdowns in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c805-d82c-a79a-fb95369d0000</link>
      <description>Rice got the party started with a 29-yard grab on the team’s opening possession, tacking on an additional score on fourth-and-three at the start of the fourth quarter on a beautiful catch over a defender in the middle of the end zone. His 12 targets were double the next closest Kansas City skill position player as he continues to operate as the key cog of the offense. Rice will look to keep his torrid stretch going against a much stiffer opponent when the Chiefs take on the Texans in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c805-d82c-a79a-fb95369d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Kelce caught 5-of-6 targets for 45 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c808-d82c-a79a-fb9cf8270000</link>
      <description>Kelce found paint on the final play of the third quarter to send the Chiefs to a 14-7 lead, but things would stall out in the second quarter as they were held off the scoreboard on their final two possessions of the first half. He extended his franchise record for total touchdowns scored that he set two weeks ago, something he’ll look to replicate in a difficult matchup against the Texans in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c808-d82c-a79a-fb9cf8270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 4-of-6 targets for 61 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c80b-d90e-a9da-df0fe9310000</link>
      <description>Worthy’s six targets tied for second on the team with Travis Kelce but were half of Rashee Rice’s team-leading 12 on the evening, something fantasy managers have grown to accept since the talented third-year receiver’s return from a six-game suspension to start the season. He’ll likely have to overcome modest volume again when the Chiefs take on the Texans in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c80b-d90e-a9da-df0fe9310000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood Brown caught both targets for 20 yards and a touchdown in the Chiefs’ Week 13 loss to the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c80e-d82c-a79a-fb9e3e410000</link>
      <description>Brown’s fourth quarter touchdown was his first road score since the 2022 season while with the Cardinals. He continued to play well behind the top trio of Rashee Rice, Travis Kelce, and Xavier Worthy, keeping him heavily reliant on touchdowns to return usable fantasy weeks. That is unlikely to change ahead of a difficult matchup with the Texans in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c80e-d82c-a79a-fb9e3e410000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
