<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL insider Jordan Schultz reports Giants GM Joe Schoen won’t be fired at this time.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f02-d713-ad9e-6f560ac90000</link>
      <description>This news comes minutes after it was announced that the Giants had fired head coach Brian Daboll. Schoen was hired as the Giants’ GM in 2022 and has his fingerprints all over a roster that has opened the season with a 2-8 record for the third-straight year. While the win/loss record doesn’t look great, Schoen seems to have hit on a few important picks in recent years. Wide receiver Malik Nabers looks like the real deal, and rookies Jaxson Dart and Cam Skattebo have both shined in limited action this season. It’s too early to say that Schoen is safe beyond this season, but interim HC Mike Kafka will now have a chance to show what he can do with this roster, which could play a role in determining Schoen’s fate this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f02-d713-ad9e-6f560ac90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Joe Burrow (toe) will not play in Week 11 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f0d-d45b-affe-7f9f51140000</link>
      <description>This news doesn’t come as a surprise. The Bengals announced earlier today that they plan to open Burrow’s return window this week, but according to FOX Sports’ Jay Glazer,Burrow hopes to return “by Thanksgiving.” The Bengals play the Ravens on Thanksgiving night in Baltimore, which could carry playoff implications for at least one of those teams. Joe Flacco will get at least two more starts for the Bengals, but Burrow is clearly trending in the right direction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f0d-d45b-affe-7f9f51140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Trey Hendrickson (hip) is doubtful for Week 11 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f13-d713-ad9e-6f5756b70000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson re-aggravated his hip injury in Week 8’s loss to the Jets and hasn’t played a game since. Despite initially being called “day-to-day” by Taylor, Hendrickson appears to be on track to miss a second consecutive game with his injury. We’ll check back in on Hendrickson’s official status when the Bengals release their final injury report on Friday but it sounds like we can safely assume he will be out in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f13-d713-ad9e-6f5756b70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Vikings LB Jonathan Greenard (shoulder) may only miss one game due to his injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f1c-d1e7-a1fa-7ffee71d0000</link>
      <description>Greenard exited Sunday’s game against the Ravens and did not return to the game. His injury didn’t appear too serious when it first happened, and according to Rapoport, it “is believed to be a minor injury that may just cost him a week.” Greenard has totaled 18 tackles and two sacks for the Vikings, who play the Bears in Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f1c-d1e7-a1fa-7ffee71d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars designated TE Brenton Strange (hip) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f2a-d673-a39e-efbb14c30000</link>
      <description>His 21-day window will open this week. Strange had a 20/204/0 line in four full games and an abbreviated stint in Kansas City. He’ll be a low-end TE1 when he returns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f2a-d673-a39e-efbb14c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns coach Kevin Stefanski said “I’m not sure if that’s what we’re doing” when asked about activated Deshaun Watson (Achilles) off the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f2f-d1e7-a1fa-7fef64360000</link>
      <description>You know Watson was woeful for the Browns when, even staring into the Dillon Gabriel void, all Stefanski can do is say he’s not sure if activating Watson is a good idea or not. We continue to doubt that Watson will play this season after rupturing his Achilles twice, once off the field, in the past 13 months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f2f-d1e7-a1fa-7fef64360000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos LB Alex Singleton said he had surgery for testicular cancer and will return “in the coming weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f37-d673-a39e-efb711760000</link>
      <description>Apparently Singleton caught the cancer early, which is great news. Singleton has been more-or-less an every-down starter for the Broncos this year, playing 659 defensive snaps in 10 weeks. They’ll turn to their depth and hope to get Singleton back for the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f37-d673-a39e-efb711760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Giants announced Joe Schoen will lead the search for their next head coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f3c-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe2e4e0000</link>
      <description>“We feel like Joe has assembled a good young nucleus of talent, and we look forward to it’s development,” was the direct quote from owner John Mara. Do not link him to the 2022 or 2023 Giants draft classes. That would be mean. It does appear that hitting on Malik Nabers, Abdul Carter, Jaxson Dart, and Cam Skattebo has bought Schoen more time than we would have expected from the outside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f3c-d1e7-a1fa-7ffe2e4e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOX Sports’ Jordan Schultz reports Dalton Kincaid (hamstring) is “considered week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f52-d1e7-a1fa-7ffa5d050000</link>
      <description>Players that are “week to week” usually wind up missing their next game, and since the Bills are on Thursday night in Week 12, Kincaid could wind up missing multiple games. It’s a volume upgrade for players like Keon Coleman and Khalil Shakir as the Bills try to get their passing game on track in Week 11 against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f52-d1e7-a1fa-7ffa5d050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens HC John Harbaugh said he wants to get Keaton Mitchell more involved in the offense.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f4a-d673-a39e-efdbf9790000</link>
      <description>Mitchell continues to look like one of the most explosive backs in the league whenever he touches the ball. The third-year back is averaging a blistering 6.2 YPC on 15 carries this season and has seen three of his attempts go for 12-plus yards. Mitchell won’t be taking over for Derrick Henry any time soon, but it’s hard to ignore the impact he can make on a game when given the opportunity to do so. Fantasy managers shouldn’t use this as excuse to add and start Mitchell in Week 11 against the Browns, but he’s turning into an interesting stash as a potential handcuff to Henry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-6f4a-d673-a39e-efdbf9790000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
