<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 22:01:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dawson Knox caught 1-of-3 targets for 23 yards in a Week 11 win over the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea2-d45b-affe-dfb6fbcf0000</link>
      <description>The one catch was a big one in the fourth quarter, getting the Bills to the three-yard line and setting up a Josh Allen touchdown. Still, Knox doesn’t need to be started in fantasy leagues while Dalton Kincaid is out with a hamstring injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea2-d45b-affe-dfb6fbcf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nico Collins caught 9-of-10 targets for 92 yards and a touchdown in Houston’s Week 11 win over the Titans</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea2-d1e7-a1fa-deeadd4a0000</link>
      <description>He drifted in the back of the end zone against zone coverage to catch the team’s lone touchdown, a short one on second-and-goal from the 3. His longest (and biggest) catch was a toe-tapper on third-and-long to keep Houston in possession of the ball ahead of a potential overtime. Say what you will about Davis Mills, but he knows who to throw the ball to here: Collins has 36 targets in the three games that Mills has played the majority of from Weeks 9-11. He’ll be on the WR2 line against the Bills in Week 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea2-d1e7-a1fa-deeadd4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Schultz caught 6-of-9 targets for 51 yards in Houston’s Week 11 win over the Titans</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea5-d1e7-a1fa-deefa6570000</link>
      <description>Schultz has earned 28 targets with Davis Mills in control of the offense for most of the last three weeks, creating lines of 6/77/0, 6/51/0, and 7/53/1. He won’t be an exciting TE1 start against the Bills on Thursday night, but he does offer a high floor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea5-d1e7-a1fa-deefa6570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 5-of-9 targets for 40 yards in a Week 11 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea4-d673-a39e-aeb5d6d80000</link>
      <description>That’s now four times in the last five games that Egbuka has been held under 60 yards and out of the end zone. He did have one bag drop in this game, but much of the dip in production can be tied to injuries to Chris Godwin, Bucky Irving, and Mike Evans. There are simply not enough weapons in Tampa Bay to take defensive attention away from the rookie Egbuka. We’d still keep the faith and keep him in lineups, especially if Irving and Godwin are able to return soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea4-d673-a39e-aeb5d6d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Hockenson caught 3-of-6 targets for 39 yards in the Vikings’ Week 11 loss against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea6-d713-ad9e-eef6d65b0000</link>
      <description>Hockenson had two crucial drops in this one, doing no favors for his struggling young quarterback, who completed just 48 percent of his throws. With six total receptions over his past three outings, Hockenson’s meager Week 11 stat line is one of his best of the 2025 season. The veteran is a distance third or fourth option in the low-volume Minnesota passing offense and probably should not be started in 12-team leagues next week against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea6-d713-ad9e-eef6d65b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sterling Shepard caught 4-of-5 targets for 54 yards in a Week 11 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea7-d673-a39e-aeb791a90000</link>
      <description>Shepard was tied for second on the team in targets and led the team in receiving yards. Much of his work was done on third-and-long, where he was able to find soft spots in the Bills’ overly soft zone defense. Shepard has stepped into a bigger role with Mike Evans and Chris Godwin injured, but it hasn’t led to much fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea7-d673-a39e-aeb791a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Higgins caught 4-of-7 targets for 55 yards in Houston’s Week 11 win over the Titans</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea7-d45b-affe-dfb761460000</link>
      <description>He was down at the one on his longest catch, a 23-yarder, and Higgins looked like he could have beaten up on Tennessee’s cornerbacks outside all day if they’d wanted to test that. Higgins finished second amongst Texans wideouts with 47 snaps of the team’s 70. He’s been a key cog in the red zone offense. We wouldn’t recommend him as a FLEX against the Bills, but he’s definitely working his way into the conversation with 22 targets in three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ea7-d45b-affe-dfb761460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tez Johnson caught 1-of-3 passes for six yards in a Week 11 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8eab-d1e7-a1fa-deeb89d90000</link>
      <description>He also rushed three times for zero yards. Johnson has been a nice story as a seventh-round rookie, but he has never topped 60 yards receiving in a game, so his fantasy value is excessively tied to touchdown value. That makes him really difficult to trust, especially next week against the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8eab-d1e7-a1fa-deeb89d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cade Otton caught 2-of-5 targets for 28 yards in a Week 11 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ead-d1e7-a1fa-deefc23f0000</link>
      <description>The Bucs still don’t have a single passing touchdown to a tight end this season. Otton was tied for second on the team in targets in this one, but was unable to do much of anything. He could still be considered a low-end TE2 next week if Chris Godwin remains out, but it’s not a high upside play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-8ead-d1e7-a1fa-deefc23f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
