<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:01:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Isaiah Bond will play in preseason Week 3 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd98-d332-a1fd-dfbec9420000</link>
      <description>Bond has practiced three times since the Browns signed him on Monday. He needs all the reps he can get, and the Browns are in need of playmakers. He presumably has a long way to go before he is even moderately familiar with the playbook and is not a recommended re-draft bench stash. He could be worth a waiver wire add later in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd98-d332-a1fd-dfbec9420000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-rays of Lamar Jackson’s foot showed “no damage.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda8-db7b-a5dd-edac012e0000</link>
      <description>Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said Jackson’s foot is “a little sore today,” but deemed the star quarterback “fine” after holding him out of Thursday’s practice. We can breathe a sigh of relief. Following his recovery will be worthwhile but fantasy managers can continue drafting Jackson as an elite QB1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda8-db7b-a5dd-edac012e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Ja’Lynn Polk (shoulder) will undergo season-ending surgery.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda5-de13-afdc-cfefe8730000</link>
      <description>It’s a brutal development for the second-year wide receiver. Polk was reportedly not a lock to make the Patriots’ roster after being outplayed by his teammates in spring practices. Hopefully, he can resume training individually before long. On 15 preseason snaps, Polk earned zero targets and rushed once for one yard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cda5-de13-afdc-cfefe8730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns head coach Kevin Stefanski said the starters will play 20-25 snaps in preseason Week 3 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd94-dbe3-a9bb-fdd763c40000</link>
      <description>Joe Flacco will be backed up by Dillon Gabriel in the QB2 role while Shedeur Sanders serves as the QB3. Kenny Pickett (hamstring) will not play. Fantasy managers should pay attention to both the Browns’ first-team running back and tight end usage. Rookies, RB Dylan Sampson and TE Harold Fannin Jr., are on the late-round radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cd94-dbe3-a9bb-fdd763c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars WR/CB Travis Hunter (upper body) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdb6-dbe3-a9bb-fdf73e120000</link>
      <description>The Jaguars eased Hunter into action via limited participation on Tuesday and Wednesday, with the goal of having him practice against the Dolphins in today’s joint practice. Jaguars head coach Liam Coen “considered” allowing Hunter to participate today, but “wanted to avoid any chance that Hunter could aggravate the injury.” Plans change, and no setbacks have been reported. Coen adds that if Thursday’s practice were a game, Hunter “probably” would have played. None of the starters will play in the Jaguars’ preseason Week 3 game against the Dolphins. Fantasy managers are advised to continue drafting Hunter as a WR3 with upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdb6-dbe3-a9bb-fdf73e120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay said Matthew Stafford (back) is practicing in full this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cde7-db7b-a5dd-ede7373a0000</link>
      <description>McVay feels “good” about Stafford’s current participation level. Hopefully, Stafford can remain setback-free as he shakes off rust and develops rapport with his pass catchers. He makes for a shaky QB2 in fantasy. Unsurprisingly, Stafford will not participate in the Rams’ preseason Week 3 game against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cde7-db7b-a5dd-ede7373a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins resumed practicing after briefly having his left ankle examined by Bengals trainers on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdde-dbe3-a9bb-fddf5a9d0000</link>
      <description>Higgins appears to be just fine. Typically, brief visits with trainers end up being afterthoughts and there is no reason to think this situation will end differently. Higgins has a lengthy lower-body injury history, particularly with regard to his hamstrings, so we’re noting this for posterity’s sake. Higgins’ third-round ADP in PPR formats is reasonable, though his WR12 ranking is perhaps a tad high. Still, he remains a reliable producer when on the field.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdde-dbe3-a9bb-fddf5a9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn indicated Chris Rodriguez Jr. is “likely” to handle short-yardage and goal-line rushing duties.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdf7-dbe3-a9bb-fdf7dce20000</link>
      <description>Beat reporter Ben Standig thankfully posed the question with fantasy managers in mind. Quinn complimented Rodriguez’s short-area tackle-breaking ability because it suits the Commanders’ “untraditional” tactic of not using a lead blocker in short-yardage situations. Jacory Croskey-Merritt is still in the hunt for lead back duties but if Rodriguez is set to assume short-yardage duties while Austin Ekeler plays on passing downs, the starter could be left with empty calorie touches between the 20s. Croskey-Merritt is a talented, young player but keep in mind, a wide range of outcomes is in play. Rodriguez makes for a worthwhile bench stash given Quinn’s comments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-cdf7-dbe3-a9bb-fdf7dce20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh declined to address whether Najee Harris (eye) could begin the regular season on the reserve/non-football injury list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce16-de13-afdc-cedf06f40000</link>
      <description>When asked about Harris’ potential placement on the reserve/NFI list, Harbaugh danced his way around the answer by saying, “when Najee is ready to play, Najee will be ready to play.” He then told reporters that speculation regarding Harris’ status beyond “today” goes “over the legal limit of what-ifs.” This is not reassuring. If Harris begins the year on the reserve/NFI list, he will be required to sit out at least four games. Omarion Hampton is an RB2 with RB1 upside. Fantasy managers can treat rookie RB Raheim Sanders as a late-round bench stash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce16-de13-afdc-cedf06f40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Tre’ Harris is expected to miss Thursday’s practice after leaving Wednesday’s practice early due to “tightness.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce25-dbe3-a9bb-fe77d0fc0000</link>
      <description>Chargers head coach Jim Harbaugh is being his typical, tight-lipped self on this one. Missing time is unideal for Harris, who has failed to secure the team’s X-receiver role. Harris will be afforded plenty more opportunities to secure a starting role, given his second-round draft capital. He should only be considered a dart throw in re-draft at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ce25-dbe3-a9bb-fe77d0fc0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
