<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:01:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Jets LG Alijah Vera-Tucker “suffered a potentially serious [arm] injury and could miss significant time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0fd0-d332-a1fd-9ff6b2f80000</link>
      <description>Vera-Tucker’s 2025 season could be over before it begins after sustaining an arm injury days before the Jets’ Week 1 opener against the Steelers. Vera-Tucker missed much of the 2022 and 2023 seasons due to injuries before returning and playing 15 games for the Jets in 2024. The Athletic’s Zack Rosenblatt said Vera-Tucker “was a standout in camp, dominant in the run game and appeared to be finally fully healthy” headed into the regular season. His injury is a massive blow to the Jets offense, expected to be predicated on the run. Pro Football Focus graded Vera-Tucker as the 33rd best run blocking offensive lineman in the NFL last season out of 148 qualifying players. This news is certainly a blow to Breece Hall and Braelon Allen, and perhaps the whole New York offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0fd0-d332-a1fd-9ff6b2f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Vic Tarfur suggested the “hype” surrounding WR Ricky Pearsall this offseason was “premature.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1001-d332-a1fd-9637b0d60000</link>
      <description>This comes as unpleasant news to the Pearsall truthers who months ago crowned the second-year wideout as the Niners’ unquestioned No. 1 receiver. Jauan Jennings’ return to action, 49ers beat writers have said, should take the shine off Pearsall. “He was out there at practice every day and did look good, but — sorry, fantasy football people — it sure seemed like the hype and jump to No. 1 receiver status was premature,” Tarfur said. “Pearsall is very quick and will still catch a fair number of passes, but physical corners will have some success against him, and Jennings’ return allows the 49ers to not put too much on Pearsall’s plate after all.” Pearsall should still see a good number of looks in Week 1 against the Seahawks, and certainly has top-30 in his range of fantasy outcomes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1001-d332-a1fd-9637b0d60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin said Jaylen Warren will be the team’s “featured runner” to start the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1012-de13-afdd-56db07ab0000</link>
      <description>Tomlin’s comments come after Warren on Tuesday signed a two-year contract extension with the Steelers. “His progress has been very evident and he’s to be congratulated,” Tomlin said of Warren, who in 2024 had 821 total yards and one touchdown, sharing the backfield with Najee Harris. “Certainly he’ll be our featured runner. Certainly you’ll see [Kaleb Johnson/Kenneth Gainwell], but at what time and at what degree [will depend week-to-week].” Warren is listed as the team’s RB1 on their Week 1 depth chart. Gainwell is listed as RB2, and Johnson as RB3. Warren could see a solid workload both as a rusher and a pass catcher in Week 1 against the Jets. He’s flex worthy in all fantasy formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1012-de13-afdd-56db07ab0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RB Jerome Ford is listed as the starter on the team’s Week 1 depth chart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1028-dbe3-a9bb-307b81400000</link>
      <description>The veteran will get the nod as the top back on the Cleveland depth chart for Week 1 against the Bengals. That might mean Ford will simply play the team’s first offensive drive, or it could mean he’ll operate as a workhorse over rookie RB Dylan Sampson. Ford over the past two seasons has 81 catchers for 544 yards and could suffice as a PPR flex option with check-down artist Joe Flacco under center for the Browns. The team’s backfield will be throwing into further chaos if Quinshon Judkins signs with the team in the coming days or weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1028-dbe3-a9bb-307b81400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir (ankle) was limited during Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1062-de13-afdd-56eb29120000</link>
      <description>Shakir appears on schedule to play Week 1 against the Ravens after sitting out for nearly a month with a severe high ankle sprain. He resumed practicing last week, and team is sure to be careful with their de facto No. 1 wideout ahead of the season opener. Shakir proved to be a reliable middle-of-the-field target commander in 2024, catching 76 passes for 821 yards and four touchdowns as Josh Allen’s main slot receiver. He’ll be a top-36 PPR option in Week 1 against Baltimore barring any setbacks to his ankle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1062-de13-afdd-56eb29120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers head coach Matt Lafleur said he’s “hopeful” Micah Parsons (back) can play in Week 1 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-106f-dbe3-a9bb-307f5fbc0000</link>
      <description>Parsons, according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter, is “uncertain” to suit up for the Packers after being traded from the Cowboys last week. “We’ll see,” LaFleur said when asked if Parsons will be ready for opening day. “He’s doing everything in his power. Got to get through a couple practices to see how he responds, but certainly hopeful.” The injury doesn’t sound like one that will keep the star EDGE rusher sidelined for very long, even if he does miss Week 1. Parsons is set to join a Packers front seven that pressured the quarterback at the league’s 13th highest rate in 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-106f-dbe3-a9bb-307f5fbc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jets LG Alijah Vera-Tucker suffered a torn tricep in Tuesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1093-dbe3-a9bb-30d3aa920000</link>
      <description>Per Schefter, AVT is getting a second opinion to confirm that season-ending surgery is necessary. Barring a surprise, Vera-Tucker appears to be done for the year. He should be placed on injured reserve later this week. Vera-Tucker was set to be an integral part of a Jets offensive line built for pounding the rock. Now they will be down a starting offensive lineman and a standout from training camp just days before the start of the season. Vera-Tucker was set to play on his fifth-year option in 2025, meaning he will be an unrestricted free agent next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-1093-dbe3-a9bb-30d3aa920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10a4-db7b-a5dd-b0a4ace80000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez has been dealing with the hamstring issue for well over a month and has yet to return to practice. A DNP to open the week suggests the young corner will be sidelined for New England’s 2025 opener versus the Raiders. Gonzalez was one of the few bright spots on an otherwise poor Patriots defense last year. Even after making several notable additions in the offseaosn, losing him for Week 1 will be a big blow to the Pats. It will also give Geno Smith a boost in the rankings for his first game as a Raider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10a4-db7b-a5dd-b0a4ace80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Jaire Alexander (knee) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10aa-db7b-a5dd-b0ae89fd0000</link>
      <description>As ESPN’s Jamison Hensley notes, it’s likely a limited session for Alexander. It’s his first time practicing since the beginning of August, so the Ravens are understandably taking it easy to start the week. Alexander likely needs to get upgraded to a full practice before the end of the week to suit up on Sunday, but this is a step in the right direction. The former Packer will start opposite Marlon Humphrey in a crucial matchup versus Buffalo if he’s ready to go for the first Sunday Night Football action of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10aa-db7b-a5dd-b0ae89fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10b6-d332-a1fd-96b61dc40000</link>
      <description>Ekwonu underwent the procedure just over a week ago. Head coach Dave Canales called him “day to day” on Monday, though he appears to be on the wrong side of questionable to start the week. Yosh Nijman looks like Bryce Young’s starting left tackle for Carolina’s Week 1 matchup with the Jaguars. Fellow backup Brady Christensen is also an option for the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-10b6-d332-a1fd-96b61dc40000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
