<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Darius Slayton caught 1-of-2 targets for eight yards in the Giants’ Week 16 loss to the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-430c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfa6a50000</link>
      <description>Slayton saw 10 targets last week and went for 53 yards on four grabs. He failed to repeat the solid performance and instead committed yet another drop. His hands have been a liability all year and his latest drop could result in less playing time next week. He isn’t on the fantasy radar heading into Week 17.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-430c-dc7a-af9b-cfbfa6a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachaad White rushed five times for 45 yards in the Buccaneers’ Week 16 loss to the Panthers, adding two catches for 15 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4309-d087-addf-f3f912900000</link>
      <description>White continues to get a mixture of carries and passing-down usage behind Bucky Irving, running 11 routes on 25 snaps. He had a 39-yard rush to open the second quarter, the second-longest rush of his career and the Bucs’ second-longest run of the season. White also eclipsed 4,000 scrimmage yards for his career with 60 total yards in this game. The Bucs’ usage of their backs is frustrating for fantasy purposes. White has the No. 2 role and rotates in for pure passing situations, making him a risky FLEX play for Week 17 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4309-d087-addf-f3f912900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kareem Hunt rushed three times for two yards in the Chiefs’ Week 16 loss to the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4313-dc7a-af9b-cfbf784d0000</link>
      <description>With the Chiefs’ offense on a doomed mission with “Chris Oladokun” replacing Gardner Minshew in the second quarter, Isiah Pacheco dominated work in the backfield. Even without the latest quarterback injury, we expected Pacheco to get more work down the stretch. These are rare meaningless games for the Chiefs, and it’s not like they need to evaluate Hunt. He will be fully off the FLEX radar for Thursday night’s game against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4313-dc7a-af9b-cfbf784d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Davis had three rushes for eight yards in the Jets’ Week 16 loss against the Saints, adding four catches for 52 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-430f-d35e-a1bf-47cf19120000</link>
      <description>Davis once again operated as the team’s RB2 behind Breece Hall, though it was Davis tho was Brady Cook’s preferred pass-catching option out of the backfield. Davis reeled in four of his five targets; AD Mitchell was the only Jets pass catchers with more targets on the day (6). Davis logged 17 pass routes to 22 routes for Hall, who managed one reception. Despite the decent usage, Davis won’t be a fantasy play in Week 17 against the Patriots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-430f-d35e-a1bf-47cf19120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean Tucker rushed four times for three yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 16 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4312-d35e-a1bf-47d252e30000</link>
      <description>Tucker had almost exclusively a red zone role for the Bucs in Week 16. He saw just five snaps, but got four carries. Tucker ran a few times at the goal line, punching one of them in for a one-yard score. The Buccaneers’ running back rotation currently sees Bucky Irving as the primary back, White in for some passing-down usage, and Tucker as the red zone back, making things frustrating for fantasy managers. Tucker is a touchdown-dependent FLEX play for Week 17 against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4312-d35e-a1bf-47d252e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audric Estime had five rushes for 19 yards in the Saints’ Week 16 win against the Jets, adding three catches for 17 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4317-dc7a-af9b-cfbf27780000</link>
      <description>Estime was widely believed to be the Saints’ No. 1 back headed into Week 16 with Devin Neal and Alvin Kamara sidelined with injuries. But it was gadget player Taysom Hill who easily led the New Orleans backfield with 12 rushes for 42 yards, including all of the goal line work. Estime had sold pass game usage, running a pass route on 34 of the Saints’ 55 drop backs on the day. RB Evan Hull ran ten routes and was not targeted. Estime should be considered a deep league flex play in Week 17 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4317-dc7a-af9b-cfbf27780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Hull had five rushes for three yards in the Saints’ Week 16 win against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-431c-d35e-a1bf-47de795c0000</link>
      <description>Taysom Hill, naturally, led the New Orleans backfield with 12 rushing attempts while Audrice Estime had five carries. Hull ran just 10 routes on the day and was not targeted while Estime ran 34 routes and had three grabs on four targets from Tyler Shough. Hull won’t be fantasy viable in Week 17 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-431c-d35e-a1bf-47de795c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Evans caught 5-of-9 targets for 31 yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ Week 16 loss to the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4317-dc7a-af9b-cfbf77350000</link>
      <description>Evans continues to be the Buccaneers’ WR1 since returning from his collarbone injury. It was an inefficient 31 yards on nine targets, a product of a struggling Bucs offense that has failed to take advantage of opportunities. Evans scored the Bucs’ first touchdown of the game on a goal-line fade from the one-yard line in the first quarter. He was targeted in the end zone twice from the one-yard line again in the third quarter, drawing a defensive pass interference before a Sean Tucker rushing score. He still needs 697 yards over the next two games to keep his 1,000-yard streak alive. Evans is a fantasy WR2 for Week 17 against the Dolpins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4317-dc7a-af9b-cfbf77350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xavier Worthy caught 2-of-3 targets for 41 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 16 loss to the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4317-d35e-a1bf-47d7cf410000</link>
      <description>Worthy “added” a zero-yard rush. Worthy actually tied for the team lead in receiving yards, which tells you all you need to know about how the Chiefs fared without Patrick Mahomes. That’s because they were also faring without Gardner Minshew following a first half knee injury. Minshew is now expected to miss Thursday evening’s game against the Broncos, leaving “Chris Oladokun” to sling the ball to Worthy and company. With or without Rashee Rice (concussion) back in the lineup, that basically makes Worthy a no-go as a WR4 vs. Denver’s elite pass defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-4317-d35e-a1bf-47d7cf410000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
