<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:06:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles completed an interview with Texans QB coach Jerrod Johnson for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b82-dead-af9e-6f874aaf0000</link>
      <description>Johnson interviewed for the role in-person today, having advanced to the second round of interviews earlier this week. He was previously linked to the Dolphins’ offensive coordinator vacancy as well. Johnson has served in his current role with the Texans since 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b82-dead-af9e-6f874aaf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers completed an interview with former Falcons head coach Raheem Morris for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bcd-d355-a5bd-8fdd6fd10000</link>
      <description>Morris spent the last two seasons serving as the Falcons’ head coach. Before that, he served as defensive coordinator for the 49ers’ division-rival Rams from 2021-2023. He held myriad roles with the Falcons from 2015-2020, coaching on both sides of the ball, including wide receivers and defensive backs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bcd-d355-a5bd-8fdd6fd10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers completed an interview with Raiders pass game coordinator and DB coach Joe Woods for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bcd-dead-af9e-6fcfd6cc0000</link>
      <description>This is Woods’ first reported interview in 2026. He has been in his current roles with the Raiders for just one season, and served as the Saints’ defensive coordinator from 2023-2024. Aside from the Saints, Woods has also served as defensive coordinator with the Browns (2020-2022) and Broncos (2017-2018).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bcd-dead-af9e-6fcfd6cc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers hired James Campen as their new offensive line coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bd7-dead-af9e-6fd7f4760000</link>
      <description>Campen previously coached the Packers’ offensive line under head coach Mike McCarthy and notably served as his run game coordinator for one season as well. Campen has been out of football for the past two seasons, most recently having coached the Panthers’ offensive line from 2022-2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bd7-dead-af9e-6fd7f4760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles hired Sean Mannion as their new offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bdf-dfd7-a5dc-0fff43cf0000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero believes “a schematic shift coming to Philly,” noting that Mannion played under Rams head coach Sean McVay and Vikings head coach Kevin O’Connell before serving as quarterbacks coach for the Packers under head coach Matt LaFleur. All three coaches use play action, shifts and motion far more than the Eagles did under former OC Kevin Patullo. Mannion will reportedly call plays for the offense. Pelissero’s belief is reasonable and bodes positively for a more fantasy-friendly environment in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bdf-dfd7-a5dc-0fff43cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs requested an interview with Raiders RB coach Deland McCullough for their running backs coach vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b8e-d355-a5bd-8fdec05a0000</link>
      <description>Prior to taking his job with the Raiders last offseason, McCullough coached in the college ranks for four years. Before that, he coached Chiefs running backs from 2018-2020. Chiefs head coach Andy Reid is evidently hoping to recapture some of his old rushing attack’s magic. The Chiefs ranked 12th in yards per carry (4.5) during McCullough’s final regular season with the team. They averaged 4.2 this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0b8e-d355-a5bd-8fdec05a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons completed and interview with Texans assistant general manager James Liipfert for the general manager vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bf8-d042-afbc-7ffa25ac0000</link>
      <description>Liipfert is reportedly a finalist, alongside Bears assistant general manager Ian Cunningham. Both candidates completed second-round, in-person interviews today. Liipfert operates as the director of college scouting within his current role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bf8-d042-afbc-7ffa25ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Dan Graziano reports that the Dolphins are hiring Nathaniel Hackett as their new quarterbacks coach.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bfb-dead-af9e-6fffe6500000</link>
      <description>The move reunites Hackett with new Dolphins head coach Jeff Hafley. Hackett served as a Packers defensive analyst under Hafley, then the defensive coordinator, last year. Hackett also notably served as the Packers’ offensive coordinator from 2019-2021 before taking the Broncos’ head-coaching role in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0bfb-dead-af9e-6fffe6500000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers signed WR A.T. Perry, formerly of the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c0b-d355-a5bd-8f5f6d3c0000</link>
      <description>This move makes sense for the Steelers, who fielded a very thin wide receiver corps in 2025. Perry, 26, last played regular season snaps with the Saints in 2023, catching 12-of-18 targets for 246 yards and four touchdowns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c0b-d355-a5bd-8f5f6d3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos completed an interview with Bills QB coach Ronald Curry for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c24-d042-afbc-7df655d20000</link>
      <description>9NEWS’ Mike Klis notes that Broncos head coach Sean Payton was interested in hiring Curry as his offensive coordinator back in 2023. It did not work out. Curry was reportedly one of Payton’s “top” offensive assistants with the Saints from 2016-21.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-0c24-d042-afbc-7df655d20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
