<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Free agent LB Anthony Walker Jr. is visiting with the Colts on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec7b-de13-afdc-eefbf6640000</link>
      <description>He played with the team until 2020 and the team has a gaping hole at middle linebacker with Jaylon Carlies heading to injured reserve, so it’s certainly a pairing that makes a lot of sense. The Colts currently have Joe Bachie and Cameron McGrone as inside linebacker possibilities next to Zaire Franklin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec7b-de13-afdc-eefbf6640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans re-signed TE Harrison Bryant.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec7f-db7b-a5dd-ec7fc94f0000</link>
      <description>He didn’t survive last cuts, but the Texans now will have three tight ends on the active roster again. Bryant is likely third in the pecking order behind Dalton Schultz and Cole Stover, which means he doesn’t need to specifically be rostered in fantasy leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec7f-db7b-a5dd-ec7fc94f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans claimed CB Jalyn Armour-Davis off waivers from the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec85-d332-a1fd-feb7fdcd0000</link>
      <description>The Titans have been lacking this particular brand of body outside, so there’s a chance that Armour-Davis slides right into being their top backup behind L’Jarius Sneed, Amani Hooker, and Jarvis Brownlee. The Titans also claimed DB Samuel Womack from the Colts, OL Clay Webb from the Broncos, and LB Dorian Mausi from the Vikings on waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec85-d332-a1fd-feb7fdcd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts GM Chris Ballard said the team won’t trade Anthony Richardson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec8b-dbe3-a9bb-fcdbb3f90000</link>
      <description>There’s probably not a huge market out there for quarterbacks who can’t hit 50 percent of their throws — maybe the Colts could have found the Trey Lance fourth-rounder — but this statement seems to say that the Colts will remain married to Richardson as their backup in 2025. Ballard said that he doesn’t feel Richardson is done in Indianapolis. Which, well, good luck with that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec8b-dbe3-a9bb-fcdbb3f90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins claimed CB JuJu Brents off waivers from the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec8d-d332-a1fd-febfb5fa0000</link>
      <description>It’s unclear if Brents, who missed time this offseason with a hamstring injury, is currently ready to play a big role in an NFL scheme. He posted a woeful 28.5 PFF coverage grade in a small sample of preseason snaps. His size and speed are hard to find and the Dolphins have a rough cornerback room, so we could see a big role for him in 2025, but he sure wouldn’t appear to be deserving of it being handed to him based on his first two seasons in the pros.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec8d-d332-a1fd-febfb5fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers claimed CB Damarri Mathis off waivers from the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec89-db7b-a5dd-ec8d9f0a0000</link>
      <description>An 11-game starter as a rookie, Mathis saw his playing time reduced severely in 2024 as Riley Moss took over as Denver’s outside CB2 next to Patrick Surtain. He’s previously played for Panthers DC Ejiro Evero and could compete for playing time in Carolina. The Panthers also claimed WR Dalevon Campbell off waivers from the Chargers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec89-db7b-a5dd-ec8d9f0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts claimed LB Chad Muma off waivers from the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec99-dbe3-a9bb-fcdbbdf00000</link>
      <description>Muma started just seven games in three years in Jacksonville, never really establishing himself as one of their best two inside linebackers. The Colts have a gaping hole at the position next to Zaire Franklin, though, and Muma could get a chance to secure that role in the final year of his rookie contract.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec99-dbe3-a9bb-fcdbbdf00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles claimed C Willie Lampkin off waivers from the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec9b-de13-afdc-eedbc6370000</link>
      <description>Lampkin, who went undrafted, had terrific tape in Week 1’s preseason game against the Cowboys and went Reddit-viral for pancaking three different Cowboys en route to a 94.1 PFF grade with the backups. He’s a particularly short center at a list 5-foot-11, 290 pounds, which explains why he went undrafted despite an 85.6 PFF grade at North Carolina in his senior season. The Eagles seem to think the Rams were on to something here — perhaps Lampkin can crack their interior line at some point.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec9b-de13-afdc-eedbc6370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns claimed RB Raheim Sanders off waivers from the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec9e-dbe3-a9bb-fcdf5e4c0000</link>
      <description>He’ll slot in as the third back behind Dylan Sampson and Jerome Ford for the time being. The rookie 23-year-old had a 79.2 PFF pass block grade in 59 total snaps in the preseason and could eventually replace Ford as the third-down back — he was a strong possibility for the Chargers practice squad had he made it unclaimed. The Browns also claimed CB Jarrick Bernard-Converse off waivers from the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-ec9e-dbe3-a9bb-fcdf5e4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints claimed WR Trey Palmer off waivers from the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eca1-db7b-a5dd-eca5c2840000</link>
      <description>Palmer isn’t an immediate threat for a big role in New Orleans, but given how banged up Rashid Shaheed and Chris Olave have been in recent years, it’s not impossible that he eventually becomes fantasy-interesting. For the time being, Palmer likely won’t make the three-wide behind those two and Devaughn Vele. The Saints also claimed OL Xavier Truss off waivers from the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-eca1-db7b-a5dd-eca5c2840000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
