<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 18:01:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Derrick Harmon (knee) is active for Week 3 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cec-d1b3-a5dd-6dfd55bc0000</link>
      <description>The No. 21 overall pick will make his NFL debut today after missing the first two weeks of the season with a knee issue. Running back Kaleb Johnson is active despite making a catastrophic blunder on a kickoff last week that resulted in a Seahawks touchdown. He won’t return kicks but could still be in the backfield mix for a few snaps. Inactive for the Steelers are CB Joey Porter Jr., S DeShon Elliott, OLB Alex Highsmith, G Andrus Peat, and DT Esezi Otomewo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cec-d1b3-a5dd-6dfd55bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared CB DeCamerion Richardson, RB Raheem Mostert, DE Charles Snowden, OT Charles Grant, OG Caleb Rogers, and DT J.J. Pegues inactive for Week 3 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cee-dfde-a1bd-7eef55730000</link>
      <description>Nothing to see here. The biggest question mark throughout the week was Brock Bowers, who was removed from the team’s final injury report on Friday. The Raiders will look to get back on track in Week 3 against a banged-up Commanders team that allowed 124 receiving yards to Tucker Kraft in Week 2, which could signal a productive day for Bowers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cee-dfde-a1bd-7eef55730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Charvarius Ward (concussion) is active for Week 3 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cee-d93f-ad9d-7eef3e860000</link>
      <description>Ward missed Week 2 after going down in the opener but is thankfully ready to return after a one-game absence. He has a DB’s dream matchup in the Titans’ struggling passing attack. Inactive for the Colts are QB Riley Leonard, TE Will Mallory, LB Chad Muma, OT Luke Tenuta and EDGE JT Tuimoloau.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cee-d93f-ad9d-7eef3e860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared RB Dameon Pierce, DE Darrell Taylor, QB Graham Mertz, WR Braxton Berrios, RB British Brooks, TE Brenden Bates, and T Blake Fisher inactive for Houston’s Week 3 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eede17e0000</link>
      <description>Pierce has been officially passed by Woody Marks and is a drop in 12-team leagues. With Jaylin Smith hitting IR before the game, this entire list is full of healthy scratches. Christian Kirk will officially be active and make his Texans debut. Berrios, who also was healthy for the first time all season, apparently has not cracked the rotation at wideout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eede17e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared WR Xavier Legette (hamstring) inactive for Week 3 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eed874f0000</link>
      <description>Legette was limited in practice with a hamstring issue all week, but the Panthers make the choice to keep him inactive against the Falcons. The 24-year-old infamously has 15 targets for eight total yards so far this season, so this may also be a reset for him. For fantasy managers, Legette is droppable until we see any kind of production. David Moore will start in his place on the perimeter. Also inactive for the Panthers in Week 3 are WR Jimmy Horn Jr., C Nick Samac, TE James Mitchell, OLB Patrick Jones Jr., and DT Tershawn Wharton.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eed874f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams declared OLB Nick Hampton, QB Stetson Bennett, TE Terrance Ferguson, OT DJ Humphries and LG Steve Avila active for Week 3’s game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eedd50c0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson is inactive with the Rams getting Parkinson back from a shoulder injury. Braden Fiske is also active after being considered questionable with an oblique issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eedd50c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brock Purdy (toe/shoulder) will not play in Week 3 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d2a-dfde-a1bd-7faf8f080000</link>
      <description>The 49ers also ruled out Jauan Jennings with ankle and shoulder injuries. Both players were reported to be out for Week 3 earlier today, so this isn’t exactly breaking news. Still, the 49ers aren’t even giving themselves the chance to do anything funny with their inactives. Mac Jones will start for the 49ers with Ricky Pearsall operating as his No. 1 receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d2a-dfde-a1bd-7faf8f080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lane Johnson is questionable to return against the Rams in Week 3 with a neck injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d53-d1b3-a5dd-6d73824e0000</link>
      <description>Johnson is being worked on in the medical tent. The 35-year-old future Hall of Famer has been replaced on the right side by Matt Pryor. This would be a massive loss for the Eagles if Johnson was to miss significant time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d53-d1b3-a5dd-6d73824e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley (rib) left Houston’s Week 3 game against the Jaguars and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d63-d6a5-adff-ffe754800000</link>
      <description>He’s been playing through some sort of injury for most of the season. Stingley’s absence should help the Jags passing attack today. Stingley had been in the blue medical tent for some of the first few drives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d63-d6a5-adff-ffe754800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders TE Michael Mayer (head) exited in the first quarter of Week 3’s game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d64-dfde-a1bd-7fedfb300000</link>
      <description>Mayer took a hard shot to the head late in the first quarter while playing on the punt coverage unit and remained down for several minutes. The third-year tight end waved off the cart and walked to the sideline with assistance from trainers, but it wouldn’t be surprising if his day was done.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6d64-dfde-a1bd-7fedfb300000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
