<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka (hip/groin) was seen practicing on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6240-d1b3-a5dd-6371dd840000</link>
      <description>We’ll await official word from the team before drawing any conclusions on Egbuka’s Week 3 status, but the fact that he was able to get on the field Friday is a good sign. The team will release its injury report later in the day, which will give us a better sense of where things stand, but it wouldn’t be surprising if he was listed as questionable heading into the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6240-d1b3-a5dd-6371dd840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden Daniels (knee) was not spotted at the media portion of Friday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6288-d1b3-a5dd-63f9fdcd0000</link>
      <description>As head coach Dan Quinn pointed out earlier in the week,Daniels would need to practiceif he hopes to play in Week 3 against the Raiders. Barring an unexpected turn of events, the second-year quarterback is looking like a DNP for the third-straight day, further putting his availability in doubt. We’ll see where things stand when the Commanders release their final injury report later in the day, but it’s growing increasingly more likely that Marcus Mariota will be under center against his former team on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6288-d1b3-a5dd-63f9fdcd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said CB Jason Marshall is likely week-to-week with a hamstring injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6291-d1b3-a5dd-63f1c5200000</link>
      <description>The rookie fifth-rounder played on 60 defensive snaps through the first two weeks of the season, but exited early in Thursday night’s contest against the Bills and did not return to the field. Playing almost exclusively as a slot corner, Marshall has allowed seven receptions on seven targets for 88 yards and a touchdown, with most of that coming in Week 3’s loss to the Bills. We’ll likely know more about his Week 4 availability later next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6291-d1b3-a5dd-63f1c5200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Glenn declined to answer whether Justin Fields (concussion) could lose his QB1 role while injured.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-629b-d1b3-a5dd-63fbdeac0000</link>
      <description>Jets beat writer Rich Cimini wrote on social media that Glenn declined to answer “when asked his philosophy on whether a player can lose his job while injured — a reference to Justin Fields, of course.” The Jets are 0-2, and Fields’ Week 2 performance against the Bills through nearly four full quarters of football was bad enough to warrant questions about his job security if Tyrod Taylor plays well and leads the Jets to a victory in Week 3 against the Buccaneers. Glenn’s refusal to answer could just be the result of a frustrated coach not wanting to play into the media’s hands three weeks into the season, but it goes without saying that Taylor turning out a strong performance could lead to calls for a change at the position from a base that’s desperate for competent quarterback play from anybody who can provide it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-629b-d1b3-a5dd-63fbdeac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets ruled out LB Jermaine Johnson (ankle) for Week 3 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-629a-d6a5-adff-f6df796f0000</link>
      <description>Johnson suffered an ankle injury in Week 2’s loss to the Bills and was a DNP all week. His absence shouldn’t come as a surprise, given his inactivity on Wednesday and Thursday. Now, the fourth-year pass rusher will hope to return in Week 4 for a Monday night matchup against the Dolphins. In addition to Johnson, the Jets also ruled out Josh Reynolds (hamstring), Kene Nwangwu (hamstring), and Jay Tufele (illness) for Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-629a-d6a5-adff-f6df796f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins HC Mike McDaniel said he expects Darren Waller (hip) to play in Week 4 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62b3-dfde-a1bd-7ebf34ce0000</link>
      <description>Speaking on Friday, McDaniel said Waller was close to playing in Thursday night’s loss to the Bills. We haven’t heard much from the veteran tight end since he announced his return to football earlier this offseason and was traded to the Dolphins, but it sounds like we may finally get our first look at the 33-year-old next Monday against the Jets. Waller was a limited participant in practice all of last week, so he’s clearly trending in the direction of returning. Fantasy managers shouldn’t rush to put Waller in their lineups until we see how the veteran tight end looks and how the Fins involve him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62b3-dfde-a1bd-7ebf34ce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers HC Matt LaFleur said Tucker Kraft (knee) won’t practice on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62bf-dfde-a1bd-7ebf04910000</link>
      <description>LaFleur said he doesn’t expect Kraft to go on injured reserve, but did say he was uncertain about the tight end’s Week 3 availability. Kraft suffered a knee injury in Thursday’s practice, and while the injury isn’t thought to be long-term, a return to action three days later could prove to be a hill too steep to climb. A DNP on Friday isn’t great for Kraft’s outlook, but it was expected after yesterday’s injury. If he’s not ruled out before the weekend, fantasy managers will want to treat him as a true game-day decision and have a backup option in place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62bf-dfde-a1bd-7ebf04910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders HC Dan Quinn ruled Jayden Daniels (knee) out for Week 3 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62cd-dfde-a1bd-7ecd65280000</link>
      <description>This was to be expected after Daniels missed all of practice this week due to a knee sprain he suffered in Week 2 against the Packers. The Commanders will instead start Marcus Mariota under center in hopes that Daniels can get right in time for the team’s Week 4 matchup against the Falcons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62cd-dfde-a1bd-7ecd65280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marcus Mariota will start in the Commanders’ Week 3 game against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62ce-dfde-a1bd-7ecf1afb0000</link>
      <description>Mariota will make his first start for the Commanders since joining the team last offseason, but has played well in the three appearances he made in relief of Jayden Daniels last season. Mariota threw for 364-4-0 on 44 pass attempts last season, and will now have a chance to start against his former team, the Raiders, on Sunday. Given his strong performances last season, Mariota could prove to be a serviceable option in 2QB/superflex leagues, and may even provide a slight boost to a passing game that has struggled through the first two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62ce-dfde-a1bd-7ecf1afb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said Joe Burrow underwent a successful surgery on his toe Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62df-d1b3-a5dd-63ffc3390000</link>
      <description>Taylor declined to place a timeline on when Burrow could return to action, but the prevailing belief is that the Bengals’ QB1 will be out for at least the next three months. Whether or not Burrow returns to the field will likely depend on where the Bengals sit in the standings at the time he’s well enough to play. If the Bengals are out of playoff contention, it wouldn’t be surprising if Burrow were shut down for the season, but we’ll have to see how things play out in the coming months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-62df-d1b3-a5dd-63ffc3390000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
