<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 19:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins CB Storm Duck is questionable to return to Week 1 against the Colts with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-255d-db7b-a5dd-a55d8ad80000</link>
      <description>Duck was at the bottom of a pile while making a tackle in the second quarter. He was able to hobble off the field before the cart took him the rest of the way into the locker room. The Dolphins’ secondary is incredibly banged up, so Duck was acting as one of their top corners. With him off the field, Rasul Douglas, who has only been with the team for a week, will step in as a boundary cornerback. This is positive news for the Colts’ pass-catchers; although, they’re already up three scores, so who knows how much more passing they’ll need to do.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-255d-db7b-a5dd-a55d8ad80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf) is active for Week 1 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2572-de13-afdd-67fb4e0c0000</link>
      <description>This morning’s reports indicate McCaffrey is a “full go” for Week 1. Players managing soft tissue injuries are not without re-injury risk, but McCaffrey is likely locked in for an RB1-level workload in the 49ers’ efficient offense and logic dictates that the team would shut him down if the injury was more than a mild strain. No. 2 RB Brian Robinson is still absorbing the 49ers’ playbook, which makes his rotational workload difficult to project. He’s a low-floor FLEX. The 49ers declared WR Jordan Watkins (ankle), RB Jordan James (finger), OL Drew Moss, OL Austen Pleasants, DT Jordan Jefferson, DE Robert Beal Jr., LB Nick Martin inactive for Week 1 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2572-de13-afdd-67fb4e0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared RB Jaleel McLaughlin, OLB Que Robinson, DE Sai’von Jones, TE Nate Adkins, LB Dre Greenlaw, T Frank Crum, and QB Sam Ehlinger inactive for Week 1 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2577-dbe3-a9bb-3577eadd0000</link>
      <description>It’s the first time McLaughlin has been a healthy scratch in his three-year Broncos career. It will be RJ Harvey and JK Dobbins functioning as the main backs in the Denver backfield in Week 1, and likely going forward. Look for Dobbins to lead the team in carries while Harvey is deployed in a pass-catching role. Both Denver backs could be solid fantasy options against what should be a bad Titans defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2577-dbe3-a9bb-3577eadd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins OG James Daniels is out for the remainder of Week 1 with a pectoral injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2578-de13-afdd-67fbf8670000</link>
      <description>Daniels was questionable heading into this game with an ankle injury, but then suffered a pectoral injury at the end of the first quarter. The Dolphins have not been able to open up many holes in the running game for DeVon Achane, and losing a starting lineman certainly won’t help that in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2578-de13-afdd-67fbf8670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports X-rays on Giants LB Micah McFadden (foot) came back negative.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2561-db7b-a5dd-a565a7180000</link>
      <description>This is good news for McFadden, who was carted off the field while sporting an air cast in the first quarter of Sunday’s game. The fourth-year linebacker was spotted in a boot later in the day, but his X-rays coming back negative suggests he may have avoided the worst. We’ll likely get a full update on McFadden’s status early in the week, but his absence could be shorter than initially expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2561-db7b-a5dd-a565a7180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans declared DL Shy Tuttle, CB Jalyn Armour-Davis, S Kevin Winston, CB Samuel Womack, OL Jackson Slater, OL Brandon Crenshaw-Dickson, and DL CJ Ravenell inactive for Week 1 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-257d-dbe3-a9bb-357ffc6e0000</link>
      <description>La’Jarius Sneed, struggling with a knee issue, will suit up for the Titans for Cam Ward’s first NFL regular season game. Even with Sneed healthy and active, the Titans defense should struggle to stop Bo Nix and the Denver offense. It could be a running theme in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-257d-dbe3-a9bb-357ffc6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals LB Cody Simon (concussion) exited Week 1 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2553-d332-a1fd-b777b5c00000</link>
      <description>Simon collided with teammate Joey Blount while defending a kickoff return against the Saints towards the end of the first half in Week 1. Both Simon and Blount walked off the field and headed to the locker room after the play. Per the broadcast, both players were diagnosed with concussions and ruled out for the game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2553-d332-a1fd-b777b5c00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Jake Bobo (concussion) is inactive for Week 1 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-256b-de13-afdd-67ebcf570000</link>
      <description>Bobo was unable to graduate past limited participation this week, as he works his way through the NFL’s concussion protocol. Backup WR Dareke Young (hamstring) is also inactive, which gives rookie WR Tory Horton an opportunity to hog No. 3 WR duties. Seahawks LB Uchenna Nwosu (knee) likewise remained limited all week, which hurts the Seahawks’ pass rush. The Seahawks also declared LB Jared Ivey, LB Connor O’Toole, OL Mason Richman and TE Nick Kallerup inactive for Week 1 against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-256b-de13-afdd-67ebcf570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RT Jack Conklin (eye) is questionable to return in Week 1 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2566-dbe3-a9bb-35773d580000</link>
      <description>Conklin left late in the first half with the eye issue before being listed as questionable to return. He didn’t return for the start of the second half, suggesting his day is done. Cornelius Lucas is in at right tackle for him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2566-dbe3-a9bb-35773d580000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers EDGE Micah Parsons (back) is active for Week 1 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2586-dbe3-a9bb-35d7782d0000</link>
      <description>This was always the expectation for Parsons, though NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reported this morning that he will likely be on a pitch count. Parsons is a game-changer even on limited snaps, so that shouldn’t be much of a concern for Packers fans. Inactive for the Packers are CB Nate Hobbs, S Zayne Anderson, OL Donovan Jennings, TE Ben Sims, DL Warren Brinson, and DL Barryn Sorrell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2586-dbe3-a9bb-35d7782d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
