<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Zavier Scott caught 6-of-8 passes for 43 yards and a touchdown in the Vikings’ Week 4 loss to the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a6-d6e9-af9d-9bb6ce750000</link>
      <description>Scott is the Vikings’ backup running back with Aaron Jones on injured reserve, but he was used in a hybrid role versus Pittsburgh. Scott, who played wide receiver at UConn, ran routes from the backfield, slot, and out wide in this game. He only saw two carries and rushed for just one yard. Carson Wentz attempted 46 passes, juicing the counting stats for his receivers, but a 17 percent target share is also impressive from Scott. He will hit the RB4 radar for Minnesota’s Week 4 date with the Browns in London.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a6-d6e9-af9d-9bb6ce750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the “initial belief” is that LT Joe Alt (ankle) has a high-ankle sprain.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91b1-dca3-a9fb-bdb925d10000</link>
      <description>Alt left Week 4’s game against the Giants and was carted off, but it appears he’s avoided a season-ending injury at this time. Austin Deculus replaced Alt as Justin Herbert’s blindside protector and may be starting for the short-term future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91b1-dca3-a9fb-bdb925d10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB D’Andre Swift (hip) is active for Week 4 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8802-d95b-addb-e8469f700000</link>
      <description>For the second straight week, Swift will suit up on game day after a trio of limited practice sessions. The Bears’ starting running back totaled 13 carries and three targets despite playing through a quad injury last week. He’s caught three passes in every game this season. Fantasy managers should expect 15 or so touches for him against the Raiders today. He’s a back-end RB2. The Bears declared CB Kyler Gordon, DT Grady Jarrett, LB TJ Edwards, RT Darnell Wright, TE Colston Loveland, DT Chris Williams and QB Case Keenum inactive for Week 4 against the Raiders. Loveland’s absence does not alter TE Cole Kmet’s projected workload enough to put Kmet on the TE1 radar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8802-d95b-addb-e8469f700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints OG Cesar Ruiz is questionable to return to Week 4 against the Bills with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91bb-dca3-a9fb-bdbb6eee0000</link>
      <description>The Saints finally had their starting offensive line healthy, but that didn’t last two quarters as Ruiz got injured in the second. He was able to limp off the field, but then was taken into the locker room on a cart. It appears unlikely that he’ll return this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91bb-dca3-a9fb-bdbb6eee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (hamstring) is questionable to return in the Falcons’ Week 4 game against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91bf-dca3-a9fb-bdbfa6270000</link>
      <description>Mooney was injured late in the first half and has been stuck on the sideline for all of the second half. The sixth-year receiver is without his helmet and, per the CBS Sports broadcast, had his tape removed from his cleats — an indicator that he may not be heading back to the field. If his day is over, he ends the week with one reception for 15 yards on one target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91bf-dca3-a9fb-bdbfa6270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs CB Jamel Dean (groin) was ruled out in Week 4 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91c2-dca3-a9fb-bddbfc850000</link>
      <description>Dean sustained the injury in the first half and could not return to game action in the second half. Members of the Tampa secondary have been dinged up throughout this Week 4 affair, creating good scoring conditions for Jalen Hurts and the high-powered Eagles offense. Dean would be a big loss for the Bucs if he misses time beyond Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91c2-dca3-a9fb-bddbfc850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared TE Michael Mayer, RB Zamir White, CB Decamerion Richardson, OT Charles Grant, OG Caleb Rogers and DL Leki Fotu inactive for Week 4 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87ef-d6e9-af9d-8fffbce40000</link>
      <description>Mayer’s absence reduces TE Brock Bowers’ positional target competition. Bowers logged a season-high 55 offensive snaps last week, after Mayer exited in the first quarter. Bowers is an elite TE1 against a Bears defense missing starting slot CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) and LB T.J. Edwards (hamstring). Through three games, the unit ties for a league-high 24 receptions allowed to opposing tight ends. The Raiders are also notably keeping RB Raheem Mostert active for the first time this season, while rendering White inactive. Mostert is unlikely to be fantasy-relevant, but he could run efficiently on a handful of carries in a change-of-pace role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-87ef-d6e9-af9d-8fffbce40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared TE Colston Loveland (hip) inactive in Week 4 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a3-deb6-a7fd-d3ff64ac0000</link>
      <description>Unfortunately, Loveland’s absence isn’t much of a needle-mover. The rookie tight end has just six targets in two games. Incumbent veteran TE Cole Kmet (groin) is active today, though he can only be viewed as a TE2 dart throw. Loveland can be expected to make strides as the season progresses, but he is unfortunately functioning as a roster-clogger on most fantasy benches at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91a3-deb6-a7fd-d3ff64ac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely (foot) is active for Week 4 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91e1-d6e9-af9d-9bf1a6610000</link>
      <description>Likely will make his season debut after missing the first three weeks of the regular season with a foot injury. He could see a limited role in his return, likely leaving Mark Andrews as the team’s No. 1 tight end. Likely should only be played in deeper formats. Ravens declared CB Jaire Alexander, S Reuben Lowery, RB Keaton Mitchell, FB Patrick Ricard, LB Kyle Van Noy, OT Carson Vinson, and DL Travis Jones inactive against Kansas City. With Van Noy sidelined, the Chiefs could find some success with their otherwise sleepy rushing attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91e1-d6e9-af9d-9bf1a6610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C.J. Stroud completed 22-of-28 passes for 233 yards and two touchdowns in Houston’s 26-0, Week 4 win over the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91e7-dca3-a9fb-bdffd43e0000</link>
      <description>It was 6-0 at halftime and Stroud had missed a wide-open Dalton Schultz in the end zone, but things picked up for the better in the second half as some easy completions were buttressed by a 37-yard sideline strike to Nico Collins to erase second-and-33 and a 24-yard touchdown to Jayden Higgins to put the game entirely out of reach. Stroud hit a few big throws in this game, but the overall shape of this offense still looks rough and we wouldn’t be excited to start him against the Ravens in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-91e7-dca3-a9fb-bdffd43e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
