<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:01:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Jeremy McNichols (hamstring) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ea8-d6a5-adff-feed44090000</link>
      <description>McNichols will likely get a chance to replace Austin Ekeler (Achilles) as the Commanders’ passing game specialist. He was terribly inefficient as a receiver last season, averaging just 0.20 yards per route run. He can be stashed in PPR leagues by those willing to roll the dice on a likely low-ceiling player.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ea8-d6a5-adff-feed44090000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eb1-d93f-ad9d-5ef75de80000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw practiced in full yesterday, but The Athletic’s Alec Lewis reported earlier this week that Darrisaw is not guaranteed to play in Week 3 against the Bengals. We think today is likely just a rest day in his long-running rehab program. Vikings C Ryan Kelly (concussion) remains sidelined, as does backup LT Justin Skule (concussion).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eb1-d93f-ad9d-5ef75de80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles TE Dallas Goedert (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eb5-d6a5-adff-fef5ae600000</link>
      <description>Goedert is clearly still bothered by the knee injury but his continued limited participation puts him on track to play in Week 3 against the Rams. The two talented offenses could produce a pass-heavy game environment. If active, Goedert can be started as a TE1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eb5-d6a5-adff-fef5ae600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Will Shipley (oblique) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ece-d1b3-a5dd-5fff7e860000</link>
      <description>Shipley still seems like a long shot to play in Week 3 against the Rams, but his return to practice is certainly positive. The Eagles traded for Tank Bigsby after Shipley was injured, so although Shipley may ultimately return to the No. 2 running back role, but things are a bit more crowded than when he left. He can be speculatively stashed on benches in 12-team leagues, though rostering him should not be considered necessary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ece-d1b3-a5dd-5fff7e860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Ladd McConkey (biceps) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e8d-d1b3-a5dd-5ffd56850000</link>
      <description>McConkey could be seen sporting a wrap on his upper biceps/shoulder area at practice today. His full participation is a great sign. The Chargers’ No. 1 wide receiver will be on the field for his team’s Week 3 matchup against the division-rival Broncos. The target-magnet is perhaps best viewed as a borderline WR1/2 this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5e8d-d1b3-a5dd-5ffd56850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles DT Jalen Carter (shoulder) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ed4-d1b3-a5dd-5ff545fb0000</link>
      <description>The Rams’ offensive line health is improving but LG Steve Avila remains sidelined by an ankle injury. His absence could be costly with Carter’s health improving. The Week 3 matchup between the Eagles and Rams might be a pass-heavy affair, which would bode positively for Carter’s sack productivity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ed4-d1b3-a5dd-5ff545fb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that Packers TE Tucker Kraft is believed to be “all good” after undergoing tests today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ee4-d6a5-adff-fee5f5cd0000</link>
      <description>One source tells Schefter that Kraft had “a little scare” today, while another adds that they “think he will be OK.” It sounds like Kraft is not expected to miss an extended period of time, but these positive, yet ambiguous, remarks leave room for interpretation. Fantasy managers should still make backup plans for Week 3 at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ee4-d6a5-adff-fee5f5cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) said that he will play in Week 3 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eda-d6a5-adff-fedf76800000</link>
      <description>The Dolphins are 12.0-point road underdogs, signaling a likely pass-heavy game script for Miami. Although we would prefer that the Dolphins score touchdowns in bunches, a tilted game script that features their speedy pass catchers will suffice. Waddle is a borderline WR2/3 for this week’s Thursday Night Football game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5eda-d6a5-adff-fedf76800000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins declared TE Darren Waller, QB Quinn Ewers, S Ifeatu Melifonwu, CB Juju Brents, CB Storm Duck, DT Zeek Biggers and WR Tahj Washington inactive for Week 3 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f00-dfde-a1bd-5f8d0f3b0000</link>
      <description>The 33-year-old tight end will try again next week. He remained limited through all three practices this week, which seemingly gives him decent odds of suiting up against the Jets in Week 4. The Dolphins’ injury-depleted secondary should allow the Bills to throw the ball efficiently, albeit in a likely run-heavy game script.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f00-dfde-a1bd-5f8d0f3b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills declared DT Ed Oliver, LB Matt Milano, DB Jordan Hancock, CB Ja’Marcus Ingram, WR Curtis Samuel, DE Landon Jackson and OL Chase Lundt inactive for Week 3 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f06-d6a5-adff-ffc774550000</link>
      <description>Oliver is nursing an ankle injury and Milano is rehabbing a pectoral injury. Their absences thin out the Bills’ interior defense, and Dolphins RB De’Von Achane fared well against this unit last year. He’s primed for another big game here. The Bills’ passing offense will survive Samuel’s absence. He has not yet suited up on game day this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5f06-d6a5-adff-ffc774550000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
