<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (shoulder) is not on Atlanta’s final injury report for Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f19-da67-a99f-fffda5560000</link>
      <description>London shrugged off the shoulder injury that sidelined him for the final stages of Atlanta’s Week 1 loss. He’ll be in line for a WR1 workload against a much tougher opponent in Week 2 — Minnesota’s defense held Caleb Williams down pretty spectacularly after their first drive in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f19-da67-a99f-fffda5560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Darnell Mooney (shoulder) will play in Atlanta’s Week 2 game against Minnesota.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f1c-da67-a99f-fffde5470000</link>
      <description>He’s off the final injury report after a few limited sessions on Wednesday and Thursday. He doesn’t make for an especially exciting play against a tough Vikings defense, but on volume he should probably remain somewhere on the WR2/WR3 line. It will be Mooney’s first game of the season after the Falcons opted to sit him as a game-time decision in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f1c-da67-a99f-fffde5470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs head coach Andy Reid said WR Xavier Worthy (shoulder) has “slim” odds of playing in Week 2 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f1e-dc44-a9d9-3f7e96fa0000</link>
      <description>Reid’s comments put Worthy on the wrong side of questionable, though the Chiefs’ head coach did say that Worthy is “doing very well.” Worthy “did a little bit of team work” on Friday after logging a limited session on Thursday. His Week 2 practice participation is at least promising for his Week 3 availability, but fantasy managers should expect Worthy to be unavailable this week. If he is somehow active, he would make for a very unreliable start in fantasy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f1e-dc44-a9d9-3f7e96fa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams LG Steve Avila (ankle) and TE Colby Parkinson (shoulder) are doubtful for Week 2’s game against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f1f-dc44-a9d9-3f7fd1910000</link>
      <description>The Rams will get one of their guards back after Kevin Dotson (also ankle) was cleared off the injury report for Week 2. Beaux Limmer figures to get Avila’s snaps at guard. Parkinson’s absence doesn’t majorly impact the Rams passing tree since it mostly condensed into Davante Adams and Puka Nacua in Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f1f-dc44-a9d9-3f7fd1910000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants LT Andrew Thomas (foot) is doubtful for Week 2 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f33-d294-a19b-fff3a2300000</link>
      <description>It’s the last thing the Giants need right now as their offensive line lacks impact players, but Thomas’ recovery is coming along slower than expected. He did get a practice session in this week, but it was only limited. It looks like another week of James Hudson’s play at left tackle for Big Blue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f33-d294-a19b-fff3a2300000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Wan’Dale Robinson (ankle) is questionable for New York’s Week 2 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f35-da67-a99f-fff551c90000</link>
      <description>He practiced on a limited basis both Thursday and Friday, so he’s probably on the optimistic side of questionable. If he plays, the Cowboys secondary is beat up and missing DaRon Bland. Robinson would have a pretty fine matchup to continue his PPR scam so long as he’s active for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f35-da67-a99f-fff551c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills RB James Cook (hamstring) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b19-da67-a99f-fffd8b970000</link>
      <description>Cook was present for all three practices this week, getting in one limited session on Wednesday before participating in full on Thursday and Friday. Cook can be expected to handle his typical workload, operating as the Bills’ starting running back. He’s a high-end RB2 with RB1 upside against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3b19-da67-a99f-fffd8b970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Darius Slayton (groin) is not on New York’s final injury report ahead of Week 2.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f37-d294-a19b-fff7e4f70000</link>
      <description>He’ll play against the Cowboys. If he can catch hold of a Russell Wilson moonball or two, the fantasy narrative about Slayton could shift in a hurry. But the Giants were so disorganized in Week 1 that it’s hard to see Slayton as more than a WR5 at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f37-d294-a19b-fff7e4f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills TE Dawson Knox (hip) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f38-da67-a99f-fffd204c0000</link>
      <description>Knox logged two limited sessions to open the week before practicing in full on Friday. The veteran tight end functions more so as a route-blocker to receiving TE Dalton Kincaid than he does as a true receiving weapon. Knox earned two targets in Week 1, and earned more than three targets in a game just once last year. Kincaid remains a viable TE1 in fantasy but Knox’s presence makes high-end outcomes just a tad more difficult to come by.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f38-da67-a99f-fffd204c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Taron Johnson (quad) is questionable to play in Week 2 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f3d-dc44-a9d9-3f7fdf590000</link>
      <description>The Bills’ talented slot cornerback suffered a quad injury in Week 1. He logged just two limited sessions in practice this week. The Bills have also listed CB Tre’Davious White (groin), backup S Jordan Hancock and LB Shaq Thompson (hamstring/hand) as questionable for Week 2. Star DT Ed Oliver is expected to miss multiple weeks after injuring his ankle in practice this week. The Jets’ capable skill position players are primed for a solid outing in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3f3d-dc44-a9d9-3f7fdf590000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
