<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:02:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Keon Coleman caught 8-of-11 targets for 112 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 1 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2774-d332-a1fd-b776339c0000</link>
      <description>Coleman and the rest of the Buffalo offense had a relatively quiet first half but scored 16 points in the final four minutes to steal the victory from the Ravens. Coleman’s touchdown went down as the first points in that span, which came on fourth down on a tipped pass off of tight end Dawson Knox’s hands. The incredible comeback win sends the Bills to a 1-0 record ahead of a road meeting with the Jets in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2774-d332-a1fd-b776339c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Khalil Shakir caught 6-of-9 targets for 64 yards in the Bills’ Week 1 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2778-d332-a1fd-b77e603f0000</link>
      <description>Shakir tied for second on the team in targets with Joshua Palmer behind Keon Coleman but failed to catch either of quarterback Josh Allen’s passing scores, leaving him with relatively modest fantasy returns on a night Allen attempted 46 passes. Ten different pass-catchers were targeted by Allen, something fantasy managers have grown accustomed to during the previous two seasons in Buffalo. Shakir should have brighter fantasy days ahead as one of Allen’s most trusted pass-catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2778-d332-a1fd-b77e603f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Palmer caught 5-of-9 targets for 61 yards in the Bills’ Week 1 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-277b-db7b-a5dd-a77f70d90000</link>
      <description>Palmer tied for second on the team in targets behind second-year receiver Keon Coleman, making his mark on a crucial catch down the left sideline with under a minute to play and the Bills down by two points. His catch-and-run reception went for 32 yards and put the Bills in field goal position to win the game, which they would do as time expired after trailing by 15 points twice in the fourth quarter. Palmer will be difficult to trust in managed leagues but appears set to return usable weeks in best ball for fantasy managers that targeted him in the middle rounds this offseason. Next up for Palmer and the Bills are the Jets on the road in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-277b-db7b-a5dd-a77f70d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid caught all four targets for 48 yards and a touchdown in the Bills’ Week 1 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-277e-db7b-a5dd-a77ea8250000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Josh Allen connected with Kincaid on the team’s first possession for a 15-yard touchdown for the team’s first points of the 2025 season. He would take a back seat to Keon Coleman, Josh Palmer, and Khalil Shakir the rest of the way as the Bills played from behind from the start of the second quarter until the final kick of the game, walking it off with a Matt Prater field goal as time expired. Kincaid could be difficult to trust in managed leagues considering his modest four targets on 46 Allen pass attempts in negative game script. He’ll look to find paint for the second time in Week 2 when the Bills hit the road to face the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-277e-db7b-a5dd-a77ea8250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson completed 14-of-19 passes for 209 yards and two touchdowns in the Ravens’ 41-40, Week 1 loss to the Bills, adding 70 yards and a touchdown on six carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2782-d332-a1fd-b7b62f350000</link>
      <description>The Ravens were in complete control of the game from the start of the second quarter through the middle of the fourth, leading by 15 twice in the final frame. An ill-timed fumble by Derrick Henry and two three-and-outs on their final three possessions allowed Josh Allen and the Bills to score 16 unanswered points in the final four minutes to steal victory from the Ravens, who fall to 0-1 ahead of a home meeting with the Browns in Week 2. Jackson looked the part of a two-time MVP while making multiple difficult throws throughout the game, the most beautiful of which was a dime to veteran wide receiver DeAndre Hopkins in the fourth quarter. Jackson remains an elite fantasy quarterback and appears primed to make another push towards league MVP in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2782-d332-a1fd-b7b62f350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Derrick Henry rushed 18 times for 169 yards and two touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills, adding 13 yards on one reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2787-db7b-a5dd-a787027f0000</link>
      <description>The Ravens completely controlled the game on the legs of Henry and quarterback Lamar Jackson, with Henry amassing a ridiculous 123 yards and a score on nine first half carries. Henry also managed 86 yards after contact on the team’s first three possessions alone in what appeared to be a convincing road victory. Things sputtered in the second half for the Ravens even though Henry added another score from 46 yards out, punctuated by a fumble while nursing an eight point lead with just over three minutes remaining. Even with the disappointing loss, Henry reminded us all that Father Time has yet to catch up to his massive frame. He started his 2025 season on track to challenge 2,000 yards yet again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2787-db7b-a5dd-a787027f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 7-of-9 targets for 143 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills, adding eight yards on two carries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-278c-de13-afdd-67cf0f9a0000</link>
      <description>After a quiet first half that was dominated by Derrick Henry and Lamar Jackson, Flowers erupted for catches of 39 yards, 23 yards, and 36 yards to set a new career high in receiving with 143 yards. His touchdown came on his 23-yard grab in the third quarter that pushed Baltimore’s lead to 14 points. The nine targets also accounted for a robust 47.4 percent team target market share on just 19 Jackson pass attempts, with no other pass-catcher on the team seeing more than a modest four looks. Flowers and the Ravens draw another difficult matchup against the Jets on the road in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-278c-de13-afdd-67cf0f9a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught his only target for four yards in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-278f-d332-a1fd-b7bffdc90000</link>
      <description>Quarterback Lamar Jackson attempted only 19 passes in a game the team controlled until the final kick, losing in spectacular fashion via a Matt Prater walk-off field goal after leading by 15 points twice in the fourth quarter. The fantasy returns from the veteran tight end were particularly disappointing considering fellow tight end Isaiah Likely was unable to suit up. Andrews is never overly likely to see immense target volume considering his advanced age and the run-focused nature of the offense, gaining most of his value from his robust red zone role. It was veteran wide receiver DeAndre Hopkins that cashed in on a touchdown from just outside the red zone in this one, but it is worth noting that only one of the team’s five touchdowns came from within 20 yards. We should see better fantasy days ahead for Andrews, with managers hoping that start in Week 2 on the road against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-278f-d332-a1fd-b7bffdc90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeAndre Hopkins caught both targets for 35 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2795-dbe3-a9bb-37d746bc0000</link>
      <description>Hopkins made a spectacular, one-handed grab through two defenders for a touchdown in the third quarter, giving the Ravens their second 15-point lead of the final frame. Two three-and-outs and a Derrick Henry fumble allowed the Bills to score 16 unanswered points in the final four minutes to snatch the victory away. Hopkins was not in a route enough to return consistent fantasy production, something likely to remain the case throughout the season as the aging veteran adapts to a reduced role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2795-dbe3-a9bb-37d746bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman caught 2-of-4 targets for 10 yards in the Ravens’ Week 1 loss to the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2798-db7b-a5dd-a79c80210000</link>
      <description>Bateman was an afterthought in the offensive game plan as the Ravens played with a lead for most of the game. His four targets ranked second on the team behind only Zay Flowers, but were not enough to return any fantasy value on just 19 Lamar Jackson pass attempts. Bateman remains a touchdown-dependent fantasy asset on a run-heavy offense in Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-2798-db7b-a5dd-a79c80210000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
