<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 18:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Titans have requested permission to interview Texans DBs coach Dino Vasso for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f289-d35e-a1bf-f7cb6ecb0000</link>
      <description>Texans DC Matt Burke is reportedly pushing for Vasso to get the promotion. It’s unclear if Vasso would actually get to call plays under defensive-minded head coach Robert Saleh, but it would inarguably be a promotion. 38-year-old Vasso has been bouncing around NFL coaching staffs since 2013, starting under Andy Reid in Kansas City.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f289-d35e-a1bf-f7cb6ecb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Browns interviewed Commanders run game coordinator and Anthony Lynn for their head coaching vacancy on Saturday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f53b-dc7a-af9b-ffbfb7020000</link>
      <description>Lynn met with the Cleveland brass on Saturday night in Florida. He spoke with the Bills about their head coaching vacancy earlier in the day. Lynn spent four years as the Chargers’ head coach, going 33-31 with one playoff victory. He worked in Detroit as their OC for a year after that. Lynn is respected in league circles but doesn’t fit the archetype of the young offensive wunerdkind that most teams are looking for these days. Still, he could get a second chance at leading a team, particularly in Cleveland, where several candidates have already pulled out of the running.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f53b-dc7a-af9b-ffbfb7020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans requested an interview with Falcons defensive pass-game coordinator Mike Rutenberg for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f546-dc7a-af9b-ffff66b10000</link>
      <description>Rutenberg worked under new Titans boss Robert Saleh in New York as the team’s linebackers coach. He had previously worked with him in San Francisco before Saleh brought him to the Jets. The Falcons finished 13th in EPA per dropback allowed and 12th in passing yards per game allowed. The solid season in Atlanta and his ties to Saleh make Rutenberg the favorite to land Tennessee’s DC gig.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f546-dc7a-af9b-ffff66b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bo Nix (ankle) “is expected to be sidelined 12 weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f562-d56e-afff-f7ea3c550000</link>
      <description>Nix’s broken ankle was devastating news for the Broncos as they came out of the Divisional Round. The silver lining is that he should be ready for the team’s offseason program and the injury is not expected to be a long-term issue. According to Schefter, “The recovery, not the surgery, is thought to be the most challenging part of this injury.” Nix will not be able to put weight on his ankle for a month, putting to bed any notion of a Super Bowl miracle. Jarrett Stidham will draw the start in the AFC Championship game versus the Patriots. He will also start in the Super Bowl if the Broncos win today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f562-d56e-afff-f7ea3c550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers hired former Cardinals head coach Jonathan Gannon as defensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f57f-dc7a-af9b-ffffecce0000</link>
      <description>Gannon lasted three years as the Cardinals’ head coach before the team fired him at the end of the 2025 season. Gannon’s defenses finished 31st, 15th, and 29th in points allowed. While the Cardinals undoubtedly lacked talent on Gannon’s side of the ball, his inability to string two decent seasons together on defense was one of the many reasons Arizona showed him the door. Gannon is replacing Jeff Hafley, who was hired as the Dolphins’ head coach. The hope is that with a full cupboard on defense, headlined by Micah Parsons, Gannon will get better results in Green Bay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f57f-dc7a-af9b-ffffecce0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants interviewed Dolphins wide receivers coach Robert Prince for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f5b6-dc7a-af9b-ffbf820f0000</link>
      <description>Prince has held the position of wide receivers coach across three teams since 2021. He has bounced between the college and pro ranks for over 30 years. Prince has received multiple offensive coordinator interviews over the years but has never filled that role for an NFL team. As USA Today’s Art Stapleton notes, Prince could be hired by the Giants in another role, even if they go in a different direction at OC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f5b6-dc7a-af9b-ffbf820f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports “multiple league sources consider Seahawks OC Klint Kubiak a prime candidate” for the Raiders’ head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f5c5-d56e-afff-f7ed802c0000</link>
      <description>Fowler also named Broncos pass-game coordinator Davis Webb as a “viable option,” according to his sources. With a handful of names already off the board for this hiring cycle, Kubiak is widely considered the top candidate left standing. He is the play-caller for the No. 3 offense in scoring and has experience under Kyle Shanahan, plus his father Gary Kubiak. Webb has only been coaching for three years and has held his current role for one season. He will likely need to gain some experience as an offensive coordinator before a team takes a chance on him as a head coach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f5c5-d56e-afff-f7ed802c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports George Holani and Cam Akers “are expected to be used in backup roles, with some work expected for each player.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f5f2-d968-a19b-fdf34ba90000</link>
      <description>With Zach Charbonnet out for the remainder of the postseason because of a torn ACL, the Seahawks are considerably thin at RB2. Holani was just activated off injured reserve and Akers didn’t join the team until the middle of the season. Akers does not have a carry with Seattle this year and Holani has just 22 attempts. Though we do buy that both backs will see the field today, it’s hard to imagine Seattle doing anything other than leaning on Kenneth Walker. Walker gashed the 49ers for 116 yards and three scores on 19 carries last week. He remains the top fantasy option at running back for the Conference Championship slate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f5f2-d968-a19b-fdf34ba90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports the Commanders are interviewing Vikings defensive pass game coordinator Daronte Jones for their defensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f608-dc7a-af9b-ffbfb47d0000</link>
      <description>Jones has had several DC interviews since the season ended, though some of those openings have since been filled. The Vikings ranked seventh in points per game allowed this year and led the league in passing yards per game allowed. Jones has primarily coached in Minnesota since joining the professional ranks, but does have stints with the Dolphins and Bengals. Having learned from Brian Flores in Minnesota for a few seasons, Jones should land a DC job sooner rather than later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f608-dc7a-af9b-ffbfb47d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys blocked the Eagles’ requests to interview offensive coordinator Klayton Adams for their offensive coordinator vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f636-d56e-afff-f6fe1a850000</link>
      <description>It would be a lateral move for Adams, so the Cowboys are allowed to block the interview and keep him in Dallas. Adams joined the Cowboys in 2025 after spending a few years as the Cardinals’ offensive line coach. Dallas erupted this year, finishing seventh in points per game and second in yards per game. Javonte Williams and George Pickens both had career years while Dak Prescott bounced back after a down 2024 campaign. Adams will be back with the team next year, though another elite showing from the offense could get him head coaching interviews next offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-f636-d56e-afff-f6fe1a850000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
