<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:01:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The San Francisco Standard’s Tim Kawakami reports, Jauan Jennings’ “lingering calf injury and long contractual stalemate with the 49ers could combine to send him to the injured reserve list this week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dece-de13-afdc-decf483b0000</link>
      <description>Kawakami outlines multiple scenarios that could take place between now and Week 1, with frustration growing on both the 49ers’ and Jennings’ sides. Jennings is reportedly set to make $1.5 million guaranteed, and up to $3.5 million in performance incentives this year. Kawakami suggests the idea of an IR stint “could be a tacit threat to the Jennings camp.” Should they opt to make the move, it could also serve as “a nervous compromise and delay tactic for this increasingly tense situation.” This scenario is bad for all involved, though, as it limits their ability to bring back other players who are also injured. It’s entirely “possible nothing dramatic happens this week,” Jennings shows up for Week 1 with a healthy calf and all of this fades into the background. Still, the tense situation in San Francisco is worth noting. Regardless, for fantasy leagues with an injured reserve spot, Jennings looks like a sharp pick at his PPR WR46 ADP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-dece-de13-afdc-decf483b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans Insider Aaron Wilson reports RB Joe Mixon has had a “tough and complicated rehab.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e183-d332-a1fd-f7b7c2aa0000</link>
      <description>Speaking in a video on YouTube, Texans Insider Aaron Wilson said running back Joe Mixon had “multiple injections and electromagnetic therapy to remove scar tissue” in the early stages of a “tough and complicated rehab.” Wilson adds that Mixon’s recovery started off well before “sort of hitting a plateau,” before Mixon sought alternative treatment. Wilson ends by saying, “I just don’t think he’s ready. My hunch is that it may take more time.” It certainly sounds like those closest to the organization are not expecting Mixon on the field to start the season, backing up previous reports that he is a candidate for the PUP list to start the season. Nick Chubb was held out of Saturday’s preseason game and is likely the Week 1 favorite for early-down carries in Houston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e183-d332-a1fd-f7b7c2aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins released CB Mike Hilton.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e1a4-db7b-a5dd-e1a4eda60000</link>
      <description>Hilton joined the Dolphins in late July but ultimately came up short of making the final 53. He played his previous four seasons with the Bengals, starting 23 games during the 2023 and 2024 seasons. The veteran has ample experience on both the perimeter and at nickel. It’s possible the Dolphins are engaging in roster shenanigans and will re-sign Hilton after final cuts, but Hilton should catch on somewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e1a4-db7b-a5dd-e1a4eda60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts released LB Solomon DeShields.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e1d4-d332-a1fd-f7f66c200000</link>
      <description>DeShields went undrafted after spending four years at Pittsburgh and one year with Texas A&amp;M. The Colts brought him in for training camp, but he didn’t do enough to crack the opening 53-man roster. We’ll see if DeShields catches on with another team or if the Colts try to bring him back on the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e1d4-d332-a1fd-f7f66c200000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allen Lazard will practice Monday and is on track to play in Week 1 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e1dd-dbe3-a9bb-f1df43c90000</link>
      <description>Lazard has been dealing with a shoulder injury for a few weeks, but is back at practice and on track to be available for Week 1’s game against the Steelers. Lazard lost the WR2 competition to Josh Reynolds in camp and isn’t fantasy-relevant at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e1dd-dbe3-a9bb-f1df43c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports WR Terry McLaurin has agreed to a three-year extension worth over $96M with the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e1e1-d332-a1fd-f7f712cf0000</link>
      <description>That wasn’t so hard, was it? McLaurin has essentially missed all of the offseason with a hold-in as he was in pursuit of a new contract. Now the receiver who turns 30 years old next month will be back on the field with a new contract when the Commanders take on the Giants in Week 1. McLaurin’s average salary is now $32 million, which is the same as A.J. Brown and less than only Ja’Marr Chase, Justin Jefferson, Ceedee Lamb, D.K. Metcalf and Garrett Wilson among receivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e1e1-d332-a1fd-f7f712cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sauce Gardner (calf) was not seen practicing on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-deeb-de13-afdc-deeb71c90000</link>
      <description>Gardner has been dealing with this injury for at least 10 days. His absence could simply be precautionary, but his status is worth following for matchup purposes. The Jets host the Steelers in Week 1. ESPN’s Rich Cimini notes QB Tyrod Taylor (knee) and G John Simpson (presumably back) are also absent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-deeb-de13-afdc-deeb71c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Football’s Nick Underhill reports that the “Saints have not yet picked a starter for Week 1.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e212-db7b-a5dd-e21630570000</link>
      <description>The team obviously hoped that Tyler Shough, their second-round rookie, would handily win the job. He failed to separate from Spencer Rattler, who fared fairly well in practice and preseason play. Shough can be expected to take regular season snaps at some point, but he may have to wait until Rattler throws one too many interceptions in September. Neither player needs to be drafted in re-draft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e212-db7b-a5dd-e21630570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Zenitz of CBS Sports reports the Eagles waived G Kenyon Green.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e21d-de13-afdc-e6dfc84c0000</link>
      <description>Green is a former first-round pick (15th overall in 2022) of the Texans and was acquired by the Eagles in a March trade that sent S C.J. Gardner-Johnson to the Texans. The 24-year-old guard has 23 starts to his name, but the Eagles are cutting this experiment short before the regular season after he missed time in camp with a shoulder injury. We’ll see if Green’s draft capital and experience will be enough for him to catch on with another organization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e21d-de13-afdc-e6dfc84c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers released LB Anthony Walker Jr.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e220-d332-a1fd-f63698a10000</link>
      <description>Walker was reportedly sidelined throughout training camp, and the team chose not to place him on the reserve/non-football injury list. This ostensibly benefits Walker. Any player placed on the reserve/non-football injury list is required to miss at least four games and the team is not required to pay him during that span. Although Walker has remained on the physically unable to perform list this month, ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that Walker is now “healthy and ready to go.” He totaled 43 tackles, one interception, six quarterback pressures and one sack with the Dolphins last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-e220-d332-a1fd-f63698a10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
