<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 20:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens LB Kyle Van Noy (hamstring) won’t return in Week 2’s game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4996-d86f-abdd-4dbfe6760000</link>
      <description>Van Noy pulled up on a play in the second quarter of Sunday’s contest against the Browns and immediately went to the sideline. It was announced early in the third quarter that Van Noy would not return, as his day ends with just one tackle on the ledger.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4996-d86f-abdd-4dbfe6760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared WR Xavier Worthy, WR Jalen Royals, TE Jared Wiley, RB Elijah Mitchell, OL Hunter Nourzad, and DE Malik Herring inactive for Kansas City’s Week 2 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-499c-d294-a19b-edfc88a90000</link>
      <description>No surprises here as Worthy and Royals were ruled out on Friday. Everyone else listed is a healthy scratch. Worthy reportedly is “looking good to play in Week 3,” but we’ll undoubtedly be blurbing him on the injury report. It should be one of the major storylines ahead of Week 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-499c-d294-a19b-edfc88a90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers FB Kyle Juszczyk is week to week with a concussion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49aa-d86f-abdd-4dbfd1840000</link>
      <description>The 49ers’ lead blocker and occasional gadget man suffered the injury early in San Francisco’s Week 2 contest against the Lions. Less involved in the offense than he used to be, Juszczyk’s absence shouldn’t really reverberate across fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49aa-d86f-abdd-4dbfd1840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields left the Week 2 game against the Bills and is being evaluated for a concussion.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b1-da67-a99f-cdf53fa50000</link>
      <description>Fields’ head slammed into the turf when Joey Bosa tackled him to the turf in the fourth quarter. The 26-year-old is struggling tremendously, along with the entire Jets offense, so the team may not try to bring him back into this game even if he does clear protocol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b1-da67-a99f-cdf53fa50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants LB Darius Muasau (concussion) left New York’s Week 2 game against the Cowboys and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b2-d294-a19b-edf2882b0000</link>
      <description>Muasau was taking over for Micah McFadden, who looks to be lost for most of the season. While the rookie is out, Chris Board has taken over at linebacker for the Giants. Muasau had only one tackle before leaving in the third quarter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b2-d294-a19b-edf2882b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Burrow (toe) will not return to the Bengals’ Week 2 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b2-da67-a99f-cdf7f2b50000</link>
      <description>Burrow went down with a toe injury in the first half and was eventually listed as questionable to return. His fate was sealed when Jake Browning took the first snap of the second half, even if it took the Bengals a while longer to rule him out. Burrow was spotted riding a scooter to keep weight off his foot after going into the locker room for an MRI. Jake Browning will close out Week 2 under center and could be the Bengals’ starter beyond today’s game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b2-da67-a99f-cdf7f2b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers LG Ben Bartch was forced from San Francisco’s Week 2 game against the Saints with an ankle injury and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b6-dc44-a9d9-4ff6a9a10000</link>
      <description>Bartch was deemed “questionable” before the break but never returned. A fill-in for an already banged up offense line, Bartch’s loss further thins San Francisco’s shaky depth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b6-dc44-a9d9-4ff6a9a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR KaVontae Turpin (neck) left Dallas’ Week 2 game against the Giants and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b5-d86f-abdd-4dbda8e20000</link>
      <description>His neck bent awkwardly on a kick return. Turpin caught 4-of-4 targets for 47 yards and a touchdown before leaving. He played only 14 offensive snaps and probably won’t return enough value to start in fantasy leagues while George Pickens is available, but Turpin looks explosive when the Cowboys feed him on offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49b5-d86f-abdd-4dbda8e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Jaylon Johnson aggravated his groin injury in Week 2 against the Lions and will not return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49ba-dc44-a9d9-4ffe339b0000</link>
      <description>Not good. The Bears’ top corner could now be looking at a multi-week absence. Chicago is hosting CeeDee Lamb’s Cowboys for Week 3, so Johnson’s health is of paramount concern.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-49ba-dc44-a9d9-4ffe339b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Walker had 13 rushes for 105 yards and a touchdown in the Seahawks’ Week 2 win against the Steelers, adding one catch for 13 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-499b-d86f-abdd-4dbf401f0000</link>
      <description>Walker saw 13 carries while Zach Charbonnet handled 15 rushing attempts for the run-heavy Seattle offense. Walker made the most of his chances, averaging 8.1 yards per carry and scoring a short touchdown in the fourth quarter to put the game away against a sleepy Pittsburgh defense. Walker ran tough throughout, bouncing off would-be tacklers and carrying defenders on a few first half carries. Walker logged six pass routes on the day to 14 for Charbonnet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-499b-d86f-abdd-4dbf401f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
