<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said WRs Terry McLaurin (quad) and Deebo Samuel (heel) will practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1208-dab4-a3fb-9b78a94b0000</link>
      <description>On Monday, Quinn told reporters that “the plan” was for McLaurin and Samuel to have a “full” week of practice this week. The “full” phrasing seemingly suggests he expects both players to practice in full three times. The injury report issued later today will confirm both players’ statuses, though McLaurin and Samuel are tentatively on track to suit up on Monday night against the Chiefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1208-dab4-a3fb-9b78a94b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings RB Aaron Jones (hamstring) is expected to play in Week 8 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-120b-d5d8-a3ff-fb6b4fe60000</link>
      <description>This is a bit surprising. Jones has logged just two limited practice sessions since the team activated him from injured reserve on Tuesday. Although limiting snaps when players return from injury may be optimal, NFL coaches frequently allow them to play their normal allotment once they retake the field. Consider Jones a volatile RB2 against the Chargers this evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-120b-d5d8-a3ff-fb6b4fe60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said WR Deebo Samuel (heel) will practice today.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1224-deb1-a39b-332ee7440000</link>
      <description>On Monday, Quinn said “the plan” is for Samuel and WR Terry McLaurin (quad) to have a “full” week of practice this week, seemingly indicating that both players are expected to practice in full from Thursday through Saturday. If so, they can be expected to suit up on Monday night against the Chiefs. The official injury report will reveal Samuel’s participation level later today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1224-deb1-a39b-332ee7440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec reports that Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is practicing on Thursday and “seemed to be working at a similar rate as yesterday.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1228-d5d8-a3ff-fb691a610000</link>
      <description>Jackson practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday, so if he really is taking a similar number of reps, he likely remains in the questionable to play category. Jackson has been out since straining his hamstring in Week 4, and one assumes that the coaching staff would like to see Jackson practice in full before allowing him to resume playing. If he can upgrade to full participation tomorrow, he should be good to go for Sunday. He will be a QB1 if active. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1228-d5d8-a3ff-fb691a610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR DeAndre Hopkins (undisclosed) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1237-d5d8-a3ff-fb7787540000</link>
      <description>The Ravens occasionally give veterans the day off on Thursdays, though the practice is certainly not the norm. Hopkins’ status is not contributing reliably enough to warrant weekly FLEX consideration, though having him on the field would certainly help Lamar Jackson’s (hamstring) scoring outlook if the quarterback can return this week. Hopkins’ practice participation is worth following.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1237-d5d8-a3ff-fb7787540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles WR A.J. Brown (hamstring) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1250-d245-adfb-975ff5770000</link>
      <description>Brown instead worked with a member of the Eagles’ training staff on a side field during the portion of practice open to the media. Unless something unexpectedly occurs, this will go down as another DNP. Brown should be viewed as doubtful to play at this time, though technically anything is possible. The Eagles (5-2) sit atop the NFC East, trailed by the Cowboys (3-3-1) in second place. The Eagles face the Giants this weekend, whom they lost to in Week 6, and go on bye in Week 9. Allowing Brown to rest through the bye week may be the best move for his rest-of-season health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1250-d245-adfb-975ff5770000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers QB Bryce Young (ankle) is not practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1259-d245-adfb-975f9d3c0000</link>
      <description>He’s almost assuredly going to miss Week 8’s game against the Bills, though we were fairly sure this would be the case on Monday. Week 9 is probably in play for Young, so the practice statuses will matter a bit more for that. Andy Dalton will almost assuredly draw the start against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1259-d245-adfb-975f9d3c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports that “several teams” are monitoring Saints WRs Chris Olave and Rashid Shaheed’s availability ahead of the Nov. 4 trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1240-dab4-a3fb-9b70c50f0000</link>
      <description>A prior report revealed that the Steelers had inquired about Shaheed during Pittsburgh’s Week 5 bye. Shaheed, 27, is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the year, and Olave, 25, is due for an extension soon, with his rookie contract coming to an end after the 2026 season. Should one wide receiver be moved before the deadline, it would increase the target-earning potential for the remaining Saint, though Olave’s 68 targets rank second only to Ja’Marr Chase’s 79.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1240-dab4-a3fb-9b70c50f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Schultz reports that “several teams” are interested in trading for Saints WRs Rashid Shaheed and Chris Olave ahead of the Nov. 4 trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1258-deb1-a39b-335e1ae80000</link>
      <description>The Steelers reportedly inquired about Shaheed’s availability during Pittsburgh’s Week 5 bye. Shaheed, 27, possesses the type of big-play ability that can instantly enhance an offense lacking a No. 2 wide receiver. Were Olave to be moved while Shaheed stays put, Shaheed’s weekly target-earning potential would increase substantially. Shaheed is scheduled to enter free agency at the end of the year. Should a team choose to trade for him, they may need to sign him to an extension right away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1258-deb1-a39b-335e1ae80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS’ Jonathan Jones believes the “biggest contender” to trade for a receiver is the Denver Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-126a-d245-adfb-977f10bd0000</link>
      <description>This is the first we’ve seen of Denver being tied to the wideout trade market, but it does make some sense given how disappointing Troy Franklin and Marvin Mims have been this season. Fantasy managers in deeper leagues should be aware of the fact that those players are not comfortably locked into their roles for the rest of the season. Jones notes that Denver has all of its picks through the fifth round and added a fourth-rounder (for Devaughn Vele) in the preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-126a-d245-adfb-977f10bd0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
