<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 19:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua suffered a left foot injury in the Rams’ Week 6 game against the Ravens and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d992-db72-a199-fbdbe7430000</link>
      <description>Skying for a second quarter end zone target, Nacua came down awkwardly, though he did not seem to land directly on his foot. He limped around for a moment before crumpling. He was eventually helped off the field putting very little weight on his left foot. Not good, to put it mildly. With Tutu Atwell (hamstring) also sidelined, the Rams are suddenly extremely thin at wideout behind Davante Adams. Nacua had two grabs for 28 yards before going down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d992-db72-a199-fbdbe7430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Reynolds caught all three of his targets for 25 yards in the Jets’ Week 6 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d99d-d94a-a79d-d99d39950000</link>
      <description>Reynolds operated as the Jets’ No. 2 receiver once again, though that role typically has very little fantasy value. It was enough to get him to a 17 percent target share today. That made little difference for his box score. Reynolds has three catches in back-to-back games. He is still looking for his first 30-yard game of the year. There simply isn’t enough meat on the bone in this passing game to support a No. 2 receiver. He is nothing more than a WR6 heading into Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d99d-d94a-a79d-d99d39950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mason Taylor caught his only target for two yards in the Jets’ Week 6 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d99f-d94a-a79d-d99f87550000</link>
      <description>Taylor finally appeared to be getting things going heading into Week 6. He had 14 grabs for 132 yards over his previous two starts and was emerging as the Jets’ de facto No. 2 receiver. As was the case with the entire Jets’ offense, that all came apart in London. Justin Fields completed just nine passes on 17 attempts. Only Garrett Wilson and Josh Reynolds were targeted more than once. Taylor should rebound versus the Panthers next week, but today’s fantasy flop serves as a reminder of just how bad things can get for Jets pass-catchers. He will return to the TE2 ranks for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d99f-d94a-a79d-d99f87550000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals WR Marvin Harrison Jr. entered concussion protocol during the team’s Week 6 game against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d99e-dd4c-afb9-ffdfc9440000</link>
      <description>Harrison took a hit to the head in the second quarter of the Cardinals’ game against the Colts. He went to the medical tent on the sideline and was subsequently taken to the locker room to be further evaluated for a concussion. Harrison is out for the game as Zay Jones and Michael Wilson step up for more looks with him out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d99e-dd4c-afb9-ffdfc9440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Emari Demercado (ankle) exited Week 6 against the Colts and is questionable to return.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9a4-def2-abdb-dde5fff80000</link>
      <description>Demercado suffered the injury on a special teams play, coming out of the game with an ankle issue. Offensively, he had one carry for one yard and did not catch his only target of the game. Bam Knight and Michael Carter have a hold on this backfield, so Demercado’s absence just opens up more opportunity for those two on passing downs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9a4-def2-abdb-dde5fff80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breece Hall rushed 22 times for 59 yards in the Jets’ Week 6 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9a5-def2-abdb-dde52a530000</link>
      <description>The good news is that Hall set a season-high in carries, blowing by his previous high-water mark of 19 totes set all the way back in Week 1. That’s where the good news ends. He was not targeted for the first time this year and averaged a dismal 2.7 yards per carry. Justin Fields was a non-factor as a passer, allowing the Broncos to tee off on Hall at or behind the line of scrimmage all too frequently. Things should ease up in Week 7 against the Giants and Hall is still seeing all of the backfield work in New York. He remains an RB1 despite the Week 6 bust.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9a5-def2-abdb-dde52a530000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Davis rushed two times for two yards in the Jets’ Week 6 loss to the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9b3-dd4c-afb9-fff387350000</link>
      <description>Davis “added” one catch for a one-yard loss. The second-year back earned plenty of snaps last week with Braelon Allen on injured reserve but only turned his role into four touches. The snaps fell this time around and his touch total also dropped. Davis doesn’t have any standalone fantasy value, but he remains one of the more interesting backups, especially with trade rumors increasing for Breece Hall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9b3-dd4c-afb9-fff387350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Troy Franklin caught 3-of-4 targets for 19 yards in the Broncos’ Week 6 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9b7-def2-abdb-ddf7f1760000</link>
      <description>Franklin added two yards on his lone rush of the day. Things got off to a rocky start for the young wideout with a fumble on his first touch of the game. Luckily for him, Sean Payton didn’t yank him from the lineup and he finished the day second on the team in targets. Franklin has at least three catches in three straight games but hasn’t topped 55 yards or scored since Week 2. He is nothing more than a route-runner WR5 heading into Week 7 against the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9b7-def2-abdb-ddf7f1760000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvin Mims caught 2-of-3 targets for 30 yards in the Broncos’ Week 6 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9be-db72-a199-fbff287f0000</link>
      <description>Mims also logged one carry, but he lost two yards. Despite the quiet day, he managed the second-most receiving yards for a struggling Denver offense. Mims is good for the occasional chunk play but isn’t involved enough to be a consistent fantasy option. He has more than 30 receiving yards in one game this year with one receiving touchdown and another on the ground. Mims is a WR5/6 for his Week 7 date with the Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9be-db72-a199-fbff287f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans declared K Joey Slye, DB Marcus Harris, OLB Arden Key, OL Blake Hance, OL Brandon Crenshaw-Dickson, WR Bryce Oliver, and TE Thomas Odukoya inactive for Week 6 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9c9-dd4c-afb9-ffc93bf60000</link>
      <description>Slye will miss the game with a lingering calf injury. That leaves veteran journeyman Matthew Wright as the Titans’ kicker against Vegas. He won’t be a fantasy option in most formats as the Titans don’t create the sort of game script that leads to consistent field goal tries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-d9c9-dd4c-afb9-ffc93bf60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
