<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 04:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Bengals QB Joe Burrow (toe) is on track to return in mid-December.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef61-df81-ab9b-ffe767e80000</link>
      <description>Rapoport notes that Burrow is currently just one month into his three-month recovery, but this is good news nonetheless. Although the Bengals are currently 2-4, they trail only the Steelers (4-1) in the AFC North standings. As long as they can remain in the hunt for a playoff spot, Bengals fans have a chance to see Burrow retake the field later this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef61-df81-ab9b-ffe767e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is expected to be back for the Ravens’ Week 8 game against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef5d-d651-a9df-ef5de5d50000</link>
      <description>Rapoport’s report backs up what Ravens head coach John Harbaugh said earlier this week. Both the Ravens and fantasy managers can expect to have their elite QB1 back in the lineup against the Bears’ welcoming defense next week. Credit to the Ravens for handling Jackson’s soft tissue strain smartly by allowing him to take the requisite time off for it to heal despite falling to a 1-5 record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef5d-d651-a9df-ef5de5d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers WR Quentin Johnston (hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6b-d99b-a1dd-ff6ff0b80000</link>
      <description>Johnston has not yet graduated to full practice participation, so fantasy managers must view him as questionable to play in the Chargers’ Week 7 game against the Colts this week. Were he to sit, rookie WR Tre’ Harris would get another chance to carve out a role in the offense. He caught 4-of-5 targets for just 24 yards with Johnston sidelined last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6b-d99b-a1dd-ff6ff0b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Brashard Smith (illness) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6f-da18-a39b-ff7f06c90000</link>
      <description>Smith was back at it on Thursday after taking the day off on Wednesday, so he should be good to go for the Chiefs’ Week 7 game against the Raiders. The intriguing rookie remains a high-upside bench stash, having logged seven touches on 12 snaps over the last two weeks. The coaching staff currently trusts Isiah Pacheco and Kareem Hunt despite their inefficient play, but Smith’s involvement remains promising.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef6f-da18-a39b-ff7f06c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks CB Riq Woolen (concussion) is practicing in full for Week 7 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef73-d651-a9df-ef776b5c0000</link>
      <description>Woolen is also the subject of trade rumors after up-and-down early-season performances. Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) and S Julian Love (hamstring) remain limited, while LB Derick Hall (oblique) remains sidelined. The Seahawks are tasked with containing Nico Collins on Monday night. Getting Witherspoon and Love back would be a big boost in that regard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-ef73-d651-a9df-ef776b5c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco completed 31-of-47 passes for 342 yards and three touchdowns in the Bengals’ 33-31, Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f024-da18-a39b-fa3720e80000</link>
      <description>Making his second Bengals start in five days since being acquired nine days ago, Flacco should have had a fourth touchdown but Tee Higgins turned a late 35-yard score into a 28-yard reception after he opted to slide and run clock to set up a clock-killing field goal instead. In between all that, Flacco targeted Higgins and Ja’Marr Chase an absurd — and wise — 33 combined times. The star wideouts turned that mountainous usage into 22/257/2. Flacco is doing what Jake Browning couldn’t and using the Bengals’ elite receiver duo to stay in games. This being Flacco, valleys will accompany the peaks, but peaks did not appear possible with Browning under center. Flacco’s latest “last ride” will resume in 10 days when the Bengals host the Jets’ broken-down defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f024-da18-a39b-fa3720e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ja’Marr Chase caught 16-of-23 targets for 161 yards and a touchdown in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f024-d651-a9df-f935c9f70000</link>
      <description>In addition to being new career highs, each of Chase’s targets and receptions were new Bengals team records. His 23 targets are tied for third most in NFL history. Along the way, he drew several DPIs and committed a few drops. It happens when you’re ... drawing 23 targets. This being Chase, it was “only” the eighth most yards of his career, but Joe Flacco’s insertion under center has given the superstar wideout a new lease on 2025 fantasy life. He has an absurd 26 receptions for 255 yards and two touchdowns on 35 targets in two games since Flacco replaced Jake Browning. All this in five days. The Bengals now have 10 days to rest up for a plus Week 8 home matchup with the Jets. Chase is now safely back in the mix for WR1 overall status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f024-d651-a9df-f935c9f70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tee Higgins caught 6-of-10 targets for 96 yards and a touchdown in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f043-d99b-a1dd-fa4fcc6e0000</link>
      <description>It’s a WR1 statline that was still something of a fantasy heartbreaker, as Higgins opted against scoring a second touchdown and securing the 100-yard bonus when he slid down short of the end zone on what would have been a 35-yard score. With 1:47 remaining and the Bengals trailing by one, Higgins passed up the sure score to set up a clock-killing field goal attempt. The plan ended up working to perfection as Cincinnati pulled out a 33-31 victory. Pittsburgh did get the ball back with seven seconds remaining, but that is neither here nor there. Higgins’ big statline did pale in comparison to Ja’Marr Chase, who, uhh, drew the third most targets in NFL history with 23. Chased turned those looks into 16/161/2. Life under Joe Flacco has been an infinite upgrade for both Chase and Tee. They now have 10 days to rest up for a plus Week 8 home matchup with the Jets. Higgins is officially back in the top 20 at wideout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f043-d99b-a1dd-fa4fcc6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pat Freiermuth caught 5-of-6 targets for 111 yards and two touchdowns in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f049-da18-a39b-fa5bfa370000</link>
      <description>Sitting on 8/76/0 coming into this evening, Freiermuth flirted with doubling his entire season production. Score No. 1 was a 19-yarder where Freiermuth found a seam in the middle of the field. No. 2 was a 68-yard coverage bust with 2:21 remaining. Maybe Aaron Rodgers will finally stop sending so many targets Jonnu Smith and Darnell Washington’s way. Then again, they both scored, too. With almost literally only one viable wideout in DK Metcalf, there is room for multiple tight ends to produce in this offense, but the passing volume is ultimately too limited to be messing around with Freiermuth as a TE2 until/unless he starts producing more consistent 4/50 statlines. Pittsburgh gets the Packers on Sunday Night Football for Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f049-da18-a39b-fa5bfa370000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
