<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 20:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers signed WR Hunter Renfrow.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbb3-de13-afdc-fffbc21c0000</link>
      <description>Renfrow is back with the Panthers mere days after being cut, according to a report from ESPN’s Adam Schefter. The Panthers can better use Renfrow’s services now after they traded Adam Thielen to the Vikings and Jalen Coker (quad) went down with an injury. Renfrow could see a good amount of work from the slot in at least the first four games of the season as that’s where the team planned on using Coker. Can a Hunter Renfrow PPR scam work in 2025? I guess we’re going to find out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbb3-de13-afdc-fffbc21c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL fined former Buccaneers S Shilo Sanders $4,669 for unnecessary roughness.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbeb-db7b-a5dd-fbefeb6d0000</link>
      <description>Sanders threw a punch towards Bills tight end Zach Davidson in the team’s third preseason contest and was eventually waived by the franchise. Coming after his release, the fine represents more than three times Sanders’ guaranteed money this season. Sanders remained unsigned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-fbeb-db7b-a5dd-fbefeb6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders RB Chris Rodriguez spent the offseason improving his speed, losing weight and working on his receiving skills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-00ea-db7b-a5dd-a0eed1400000</link>
      <description>Rodriguez spent 2024 floating between the practice squad and active roster, and was told by ST coach Larry Izzo to refine himself physically. He had swelled to 235 pounds following a high-ankle sprain in his 2023 rookie season. Rodriguez, now tipping the scales at 222, said he was clocked at 20-plus MPH “more times in training camp than I have in almost my whole life.” His improved speed was evident on a 40-yard preseason scamper, during which he hit 20.37 MPH. Rodriguez also hired private receiving coach Drew Lieberman, whose résumé includes Brandon Aiyuk and Chase Brown, but unfortunately dropped his lone preseason target. He has just three career catches. Rodriguez is a worthwhile dart throw given his position group’s shifting state and head coach Dan Quinn’s positive comments regarding his short-yardage rushing abilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-00ea-db7b-a5dd-a0eed1400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys signed CB DaRon Bland to a four-year, $92 million extension through 2029.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-011b-dbe3-a9bb-315bcffb0000</link>
      <description>This extension has been in the works since July, but it was likely held up by the Micah Parsons fiasco. It includes $50 million in guarantees. The fourth-year pro is expected to return to the slot-coverage role that he excelled in during his first two NFL seasons, where he racked up eight pass breakups and 14 interceptions. He primarily played on the outside last year, breaking up just three passes and recording zero interceptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-011b-dbe3-a9bb-315bcffb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs WR Jalen Royals (knee tendinitis) did not practice on Sunday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0119-de13-afdd-47dba3d30000</link>
      <description>Per head coach Andy Reid, Royals is the only player on the active roster who was unable to practice today. A 22-year-old player already dealing with tendinitis is less than ideal, but overall, this is great news. The Chiefs’ wide receiver corps was feeling a little thin, following Rashee Rice’s six-game suspension. Hollywood Brown (ankle) returned to practice on August 18th. Reports on his rehab have been sparse, but we take Reid’s comments on Royals as an indirect positive on Brown’s rehab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0119-de13-afdd-47dba3d30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Vikings are “optimistic” about WR Jalen Nailor’s (hand) availability for Week 1 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0153-de13-afdd-47db7eed0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings recently brought back Adam Thielen via trade, with Jordan Addison set to serve a three-game suspension, and immediately listed Thielen as the fill-in No. 2 wide receiver. ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that “Minnesota envisions a key role for Nailor, especially with Jordan Addison out via suspension,” but that’s tough to trust given his injury and the recent personnel development. Nailor is best-suited to single-game DFS lineups and should really only be considered for flex duties in 14-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0153-de13-afdd-47db7eed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys DT Perrion Winfrey left practice early on Sunday after suffering a “low back” injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0160-d332-a1fd-9776e1290000</link>
      <description>Winfrey, 25, has had a bumpy ride in professional football, playing both in the NFL and UFL. He made it through final cuts, listed as a third-string defensive tackle. The Cowboys, now organizationally committed to stopping the run, need all the help they can get on the defensive line. Hopefully, Winfrey is available in Week 1, even if only for a handful of snaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0160-d332-a1fd-9776e1290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles signed OG Kenyon Green to a contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-019b-d332-a1fd-97bf23e60000</link>
      <description>Green’s promotion coincides with OG/C Willie Lampkin being placed on injured reserve. Lampkin was waived by the Rams with an injury designation after suffering a preseason knee injury. Lampkin will be eligible to return after four games missed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-019b-d332-a1fd-97bf23e60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles S Andrew Mukuba (groin) was seen in pads and is “ready to practice in some form today.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0131-db7b-a5dd-a13583db0000</link>
      <description>The Eagles drafted Mukuba in the second round this year. He was competing with Sydney Brown for one of the starting safety roles when he suffered a shoulder injury in late July. He later picked up a groin injury upon returning. Mukuba is likely slated for a backup role early in the year, but his draft capital should get him more opportunities to take over as a starter as the year progresses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0131-db7b-a5dd-a13583db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Philadelphia Inquirer’s Jeff McLane reports that Eagles OG Landon Dickerson (knee) is “trending toward playing” in Week 1 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01a2-de13-afdd-47eb0df80000</link>
      <description>Dickerson recently underwent surgery to address a meniscus injury. It appears as though his rehab has gone very well. The three-time-defending Pro Bowl blocker should play a pivotal role as the Eagles likely attempt to ground-and-pound their way to victory in the second half.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-01a2-de13-afdd-47eb0df80000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
