<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 16:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings caught 4-of-6 targets for 35 yards in San Francisco’s Week 18 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-873f-d56e-afff-e7ff10df0000</link>
      <description>He finished behind only George Kittle and Christian McCaffrey in targets, but San Francisco’s pass offense was going nowhere fast against Mike MacDonald’s crew tonight. Jennings will be a reasonable DFS play in the Wild Card Round next weekend. He hasn’t cracked 100 yards in a game all season, but managed a 55/643 seasonal line with nine touchdowns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-873f-d56e-afff-e7ff10df0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Kittle caught 5-of-7 targets for 29 yards in San Francisco’s Week 18 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8741-dc7a-af9b-cfff2f1d0000</link>
      <description>Limited mostly to little dumpoffs on bootlegs, Kittle actually gained 20 of his 29 yards on one of the few sideline balls that Brock Purdy was able to fit in on San Francisco’s best drive of the game. Kittle finishes the regular season with a 57/628 receiving line in just 11 starts. He’ll be available for San Francisco’s Wild Card game against an as-of-yet undetermined opponent next weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8741-dc7a-af9b-cfff2f1d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demarcus Robinson caught 3-of-4 targets for 24 yards in San Francisco’s Week 18 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8744-d968-a19b-dff5dc120000</link>
      <description>He played 37-of-42 snaps and out-targeted Kendrick Bourne four to one in San Francisco’s finale. Assuming Ricky Pearsall is able to play in the Wild Card round, this won’t matter much. But it is worth noting that Robinson could be the DFS punt we’re interested in — rather than Bourne — if Pearsall is sidelined again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8744-d968-a19b-dff5dc120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jaylen Waddle (ribs) is not expected to play in Week 18 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-892b-d56e-afff-efeb09c70000</link>
      <description>The same is true of De’Von Achane, who is listed as doubtful with a shoulder injury. Like most teams with nothing to play for in Week 18, the Dolphins are shutting their key players down this week. The Patriots shouldn’t have any issues versus Miami this week. A win gives them the No. 2 seed in the AFC. An unlikely Denver loss on top of a New England win would give the Pats the No. 1 seed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-892b-d56e-afff-efeb09c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports De’Von Achane (shoulder) is not expected to play in Week 18 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8930-d56e-afff-eff8b91d0000</link>
      <description>This really isn’t much of a surprise. Achane was listed as doubtful after missing all three practices this week. The Dolphins are out of the playoff hunt, so there’s no reason to play Achane through the shoulder issue. Jaylen Wright should handle the bulk of the backfield touches for Miami this week, putting him on the RB2/3 border for Week 18.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8930-d56e-afff-eff8b91d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Philip Rivers “could end up as a head coach candidate this cycle.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-894d-dc7a-af9b-cfff072f0000</link>
      <description>Rapoport added, “The current belief is that Rivers gets at least one opportunity to interview, possibly more.” Rivers coached high school football for five years at St. Michael Catholic in Alabama. His football IQ is also off the charts, as evidenced by his sudden return to the game this year. The Giants and Titans are currently the only teams in need of a new head coach, though more teams will be added to the list after Week 18. Rivers might need to find work beyond the high school ranks before teams are ready to hire him as the boss of an NFL team, but a future as a professional football coach would suit him well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-894d-dc7a-af9b-cfff072f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Jane Slater reports Nico Collins will not play in Week 18 against the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-895d-d968-a19b-d9fdef8b0000</link>
      <description>The Texans could still win the AFC South with a win and a Jacksonville loss today, but the Jags face the lowly Titans. That all but guarantees them the AFC South crown, relegating Houston to a road playoff game. With little to play for, Collins will get the week off. As Slater notes, this will also give the Texans a better look at their rookie wideouts, Jaylin Noel and Jayden Higgins. Both players are now solid FLEX options for fantasy managers still setting lineups this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-895d-d968-a19b-d9fdef8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Trevon Diggs will play in Week 18 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8972-dc7a-af9b-cfff087a0000</link>
      <description>Already locked in as the No. 7 seed, the Packers are resting some of their starters this week. Diggs, however, joined the team just four days ago. A few reps today will go a long way in getting him familiar with Green Bay’s defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8972-dc7a-af9b-cfff087a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Judy Battista reports Jets owner Woody Johnson “remains committed” to head coach Aaron Glenn.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89a9-d56e-afff-efe99b9d0000</link>
      <description>Despite sitting at 3-13 with one game left to play, the Jets will give Glenn a second chance in 2026. The former Lions defensive coordinator was brought in to turn the team around this year. Instead, the Justin Fields experiment flopped and Glenn’s side of the ball failed to contribute anything to the cause. The Jets currently rank 30th in points allowed. As Battista notes, Glenn is expected to make some changes to his staff during the offseason. Offensive coordinator Tanner Engstrand could be asked to fall on his sword after a dismal season from the offense. Defensive coordinator Steve Wilks was fired in the middle of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89a9-d56e-afff-efe99b9d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Brock Purdy (left shoulder) is expected to play in the Wild Card Round.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89b4-d35e-a1bf-cdf6d8da0000</link>
      <description>Purdy got crushed by multiple Seattle defenders on his final play of the 49ers’ Week 18 loss to the Seahawks. He stayed on the field for a while before heading into the blue medical tent. Kyle Shanahan called the injury a stinger in his left shoulder after the game. He also told reports Purdy could have returned to the contest. He will likely be dealing with some pain in the Wild Card Round, but Purdy will be out there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-89b4-d35e-a1bf-cdf6d8da0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
