<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Gainwell rushed three times for 14 yards in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f061-d651-a9df-f9755cc20000</link>
      <description>Gainwell “added” two receptions for one yard. Although PFF charted Jaylen Warren as out-snapping Gainwell “just” 37-22, Warren out-touched his backfield mate 20-5, out-gaining him 158-15. This, after they played to a usage standstill in Warren’s Week 6 return from his knee injury. Tonight should be much closer to the norm going forward, removing Gainwell from FLEX consideration in most 12-team leagues heading into Week 8 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f061-d651-a9df-f9755cc20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chase Brown rushed 11 times for 108 yards in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f063-df81-ab9b-fee7d7940000</link>
      <description>Tonight was Brown’s first 100-yard effort either on the ground or from scrimmage this season, though he almost didn’t get there in the latter category after losing eight yards on his two receptions. Brown also committed an awful drop over the middle of the field. Having previously failed to notch a 20-yard carry all season, Brown had 27 and 37-yard rumbles against the Steelers as Joe Flacco created space by ripping holes in the defense through the air. The solid effort at least keeps Brown in the RB2 mix, though this was really just a bare minimum step toward him getting back on the right track. The Jets are an admittedly appetizing Week 8 matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f063-df81-ab9b-fee7d7940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Fant caught 4-of-4 targets for 44 yards and a touchdown in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f066-d99b-a1dd-fa6ef75e0000</link>
      <description>Amidst a Ja’Marr Chase/Tee Higgins targets barrage that saw 33 looks being funneled the elite wideouts’ way, Fant managed to get loose for his first score since Week 1. His 44 yards were also a new season high. What can Joe Flacco do for you? Flacco is going to keep slinging it until his arm falls off, but Fant is still unlikely to see enough volume to push for TE2 status in Week 8 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f066-d99b-a1dd-fa6ef75e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samaje Perine rushed seven times for 31 yards in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06b-da18-a39b-fa7b44a80000</link>
      <description>Perine was not targeted in the passing game as Chase Brown out-touched him 13-7 and out-snapped him 48-28 (via PFF). Perine did manage new season high in both carries and rushing yards as Joe Flacco helped open up the offense. Perine is still far more likely to hamper Brown’s fantasy value, however, than create any of his own heading into Week 8 against the Jets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06b-da18-a39b-fa7b44a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Andrei Iosivas caught 3-of-4 targets for 49 yards in the Bengals’ Week 7 win over the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06d-da18-a39b-fa7f984c0000</link>
      <description>Iosivas’ missed connection was a bad drop. Iosivas posted his second best overall statline of the season as Joe Flacco dropped back 49 times and attempted 47 passes, but he was out-targeted 33-4 by Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins’ combined efforts. It would take injury to one of the elite wideouts ahead of him for Iosivas to become fantasy relevant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06d-da18-a39b-fa7f984c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jonnu Smith caught 3-of-6 targets for 28 yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06f-df81-ab9b-feef54d50000</link>
      <description>Both the six-target effort and score were Smith’s first since Week 1, while he was the No. 2 producing tight end behind Pat Freiermuth, who turned his six looks into 5/111/2. Improbably, Darnell Washington also found the end zone. That’s the long way of saying no Steelers tight end is producing consistently enough to merit a real TE2 look ahead of Week 8 against the Packers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f06f-df81-ab9b-feef54d50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Washington caught 3-of-5 targets for two yards and a touchdown in the Steelers’ Week 7 loss to the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f071-d651-a9df-f97551ee0000</link>
      <description>Coming off a career-high 62-yard effort, Washington posted one of the more bizarre box scores you will ever see. He does now have 10 targets over the past two weeks after that number was four across his first four appearances. Perhaps his usage really is changing, but there has been little indication Washington is about to make a legitimate push for TE2 value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f071-d651-a9df-f97551ee0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers (knee/toe) did not practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f271-d651-a9df-fb75fc670000</link>
      <description>Meyers has not practiced this week ahead of the Raiders’ Week 7 game against the Chiefs. Unless you gets in at least a limited practice on Friday, he’ll likely be sidelined against KC. The Raiders, according to ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler, might be looking to trade Meyers before the league’s trade deadline after Meyers formally requested a trade just before the regular season. Meyers’ absence could be a boost for Tre Tucker and Michael Mayer in Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f271-d651-a9df-fb75fc670000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS Sports’ Matt Zenitz reports Garrett Wilson (knee) will be a DNP on Friday and miss Week 7 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f226-d99b-a1dd-fa2e06b80000</link>
      <description>This is according to a source who spoke with Zenitz, but we assume the team’s official injury report, which will come later Friday, will have Wilson ruled out. The star receiver was expected to miss multiple weeks with the knee injury he picked up in Week 6, so the idea of him missing Week 7 doesn’t come as much of a surprise. The Jets will hope the duo of Josh Reynolds and Allen Lazard can step up in Wilson’s absence as they look to pick up their first win of the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f226-d99b-a1dd-fa2e06b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero said there is “real uncertainty” about Terry McLaurin (quad) playing in Week 7 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2a5-d99b-a1dd-faada7860000</link>
      <description>Pelissero also said the same of Deebo Samuel (heel). It sounds a bit redundant given that Pelissero said on Thursday night there was “real concern” about both receivers’ Week 7 availability, but the fact the tone hasn’t changed over the last 12-plus hours suggests both receivers are trending in the wrong direction for a pivotal NFC East matchup. The Commanders will take the practice field in a few hours, so we should know more about both receivers’ availability soon. That said, a DNP for either player likely means them being ruled out for Week 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-f2a5-d99b-a1dd-faada7860000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
