<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12c1-d5d8-a3ff-fbe180c30000</link>
      <description>Watson told reporters yesterday that he plans to play in Week 8 against the Steelers, but his limited participation keeps him firmly in the questionable category. If active, one would expect Watson to play on a snap count in his first game back from a torn ACL, and the Packers already rotate their wide receivers frequently, as is. Fellow Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (calf) remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12c1-d5d8-a3ff-fbe180c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR DeAndre Hopkins (illness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12cd-d245-adfb-97dff4b20000</link>
      <description>Hopkins is the only Ravens player to miss practice on Thursday, and an illness is unlikely to sideline the veteran wide receiver on game day. Hopkins sneaks into the FLEX conversation, if active, with six teams on bye, but he largely serves as a fantasy-point booster for whichever quarterback is under center against the Bears this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12cd-d245-adfb-97dff4b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens CB Marlon Humphrey (illness) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12cd-dab4-a3fb-9bfda0140000</link>
      <description>The Ravens’ defensive health is improving, though it still lacks a capable pass rush. CB Chidobe Awuzie (hamstring) is practicing in full, as are S Kyle Hamilton (groin) and LB Roquan Smith (hamstring). This unit was one to target for fantasy purposes pre-bye, in Weeks 1-6, and will likely remain fantasy-friendly until it improves its defensive-front personnel. This week’s results against the Bears are worth watching.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12cd-dab4-a3fb-9bfda0140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets TE Mason Taylor (quad) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12e8-dab4-a3fb-9bf8bcbb0000</link>
      <description>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports that it sounds like Taylor’s quad injury is not considered “major” and that the rookie has not been ruled out for Week 8 against the Bengals. This is hardly a ringing endorsement for the rookie tight end’s health, though. Friday’s injury report should clarify his status. The Jets receiving corps is also likely to be without WR Garrett Wilson (knee). Backup TE Stone Smartt is also sidelined by a quad injury of his own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12e8-dab4-a3fb-9bf8bcbb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets RB Breece Hall (knee) was limited on Thursday</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12ef-d5d8-a3ff-fbef80db0000</link>
      <description>Hall is trending toward playing in Week 8 against the Bengals, though it would be great to see him upgrade to full participation on Friday. Hall is currently tied with Tony Pollard for the overall RB22 spot in half-PPR scoring, somewhat weighed down by consecutive RB31 finishes over the last two weeks. If active, he should run roughshod over the Bengals’ fantasy-friendly defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12ef-d5d8-a3ff-fbef80db0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12da-d5d8-a3ff-fbfb8cad0000</link>
      <description>The Jets are considering moving to Taylor as the Week 8 starter because of his passing ability. It is unclear who Taylor will be throwing to, with No. 1 WR Garrett Wilson (knee) likely sidelined and TE Mason Taylor (quad) added to the injury report as a non-participant today. For what it is worth, NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Taylor’s injury is not considered “major,” but Taylor’s QB2 viability is at least mildly tethered to his tight end’s health. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12da-d5d8-a3ff-fbfb8cad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets CB Sauce Gardner (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12f7-dab4-a3fb-9bf7b6c40000</link>
      <description>Gardner is trending toward a Week 8 absence against the Bengals, which is bad news for the Jets and good news for fantasy managers. Both Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins should have solid outings against the Jets regardless of Gardner’s health, but if Gardner is indeed ruled out, it raises both players’ scoring ceilings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12f7-dab4-a3fb-9bf7b6c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals TE Tanner Hudson (concussion) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12fc-deb1-a39b-33fe2a8d0000</link>
      <description>Hudson’s expected return bodes poorly for TE Noah Fant’s target-earning potential, though Fant should still run as the primary positional receiver. Hudson sat out in Week 7, allowing Fant to operate as a streaming TE1. Fant caught 4-of-4 targets for 44 yards and one touchdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12fc-deb1-a39b-33fe2a8d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Ben Baby reports that Bengals LB Logan Wilson has requested a trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12ff-deb1-a39b-33ff1d890000</link>
      <description>Wilson has effectively been supplanted by rookie LBs Demetrius Knight Jr. and Barrett Carter in recent weeks, yet he ties for fourth on the team in tackles (28). Wilson could help a team in need of an early-down thumper, though he is limited as a coverage defender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12ff-deb1-a39b-33ff1d890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs RB Brashard Smith (toe) is practicing in full for Week 8 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1302-d5d8-a3ff-fb63607e0000</link>
      <description>Smith must have picked up the toe injury in Week 7 against the Raiders, when he notched a season-high 19 touches. He is on track to play this week, while veteran RB Kareem Hunt (knee) heads in the other direction with a bone bruise. Smith is on the FLEX radar with six teams on bye this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1302-d5d8-a3ff-fb63607e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
