<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Justin Fields (concussion) has been cleared to start Week 4 against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8bd3-d6e9-af9d-8bd37ebe0000</link>
      <description>Things had been trending this way after Fields practice in full on both Thursday and Friday. Sidelined for Week 3, Fields had an extra day to get ready for Week 4 with the game part of a Monday night double-header. Excellent in Week 1 and awful in Week 2, Fields is returning to an A+ matchup in the ‘Fins. The only problem is the same is true for Miami’s beleaguered defense. Although Fields’ dual-threat means he always has a high-end QB1 ceiling, his floor is low enough to treat him as more of a high-end QB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8bd3-d6e9-af9d-8bd37ebe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller (hip) will make his Dolphins debut Monday evening against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8bd8-d6e9-af9d-8bd874610000</link>
      <description>Coach Mike McDaniel said Waller appeared “firmly ready to contribute” while still acknowledging he would be on a snap count. Always injured before his brief one-year retirement last season, Waller missed most of training camp before being sidelined Weeks 1-3. Even at age 33, he likely still has big-play upside, it’s just so hard to see him getting there often enough to provide true 12-team league value. He is nevertheless a name worth putting on watch lists with bye weeks beginning in Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8bd8-d6e9-af9d-8bd874610000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Jaylen Warren (knee, questionable) will be active for Sunday’s Ireland game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8bdb-d6e9-af9d-8bdb2c6c0000</link>
      <description>Warren popped up with the “knee” designation on Friday, but it seems it was purely precautionary. The Steelers have promoted veteran RB Trey Sermon from the practice squad, but that appears to have more to do with rookie Kaleb Johnson’s special teams woes. Handling basically all the work that matters in Pittsburgh’s backfield, Warren is a high-end FLEX, if one with a little more injury risk than usual this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8bdb-d6e9-af9d-8bdb2c6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said CB Cam Taylor-Britt (ankle) will play in Week 4 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c20-deb6-a7fd-dfffb64a0000</link>
      <description>Taylor-Britt’s return comes at a solid time after the defense struggled against the Vikings in Week 3. It’s a substantial return for a secondary that has performed over expectations through three weeks, largely due to heavy zone rates that require consistent communication on the back end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c20-deb6-a7fd-dfffb64a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals HC Zac Taylor said TE Noah Fant will not play in Week 4 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c24-deb6-a7fd-dffffc2c0000</link>
      <description>Fant suffered a concussion in the team’s Week 3 loss to the Vikings and did not do enough to progress through the league’s concussion protocol. His absence should boost the snap rate and route participation rate of Mike Gesicki.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c24-deb6-a7fd-dffffc2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals ruled out DE Shemar Stewart (ankle) for Week 4 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c26-deb6-a7fd-dfff88380000</link>
      <description>The ankle issue will not cost Stewart his second consecutive game after the veteran defensive end missed Week 3’s loss to the Vikings. His absence was felt considering the Bengals allowed Jordan Mason to eclipse 100 yards on the ground on just 16 carries, boosting the matchup for J.K. Dobbins in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c26-deb6-a7fd-dfff88380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s David Newton reports WR Tetairoa McMillan is expected to play in Week 4 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c28-dca3-a9fb-bdb9a0ad0000</link>
      <description>McMillan has been adamant about taking the field when the Panthers face the Patriots on the road in Week 4, something that appears to be vindicated as Sunday approaches. It is not yet apparent whether he will see any limitations but fantasy managers are likely going to start him, assuming he dodges inactives Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c28-dca3-a9fb-bdb9a0ad0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s David Newton reports Panthers RB Chuba Hubbard (calf) is expected to play in Week 4 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2b-d6e9-af9d-8ebb0f9f0000</link>
      <description>Hubbard was limited in practices this week as he tends to a calf injury, ultimately drawing the questionable tag for the team’s Week 4 road matchup with the Patriots. It now sounds like he is in line to play and fantasy managers should assume a normal workload for the veteran back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2b-d6e9-af9d-8ebb0f9f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins WR Tyreek Hill (personal) missed practice Saturday but is expected to play Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2c-d6e9-af9d-8ebce9070000</link>
      <description>Hill was absent from team practice Saturday for personal reasons but is expected to play on Monday against the Jets. The early season returns have been less than stellar for Hill and the rest of the Dolphins’ primary skill position players. The Jets no longer present the same vaunted defense as they have in previous seasons, meaning fantasy managers will want to start Hill with confidence in Week 4, regardless of his struggles through three games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2c-d6e9-af9d-8ebce9070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports TE Colston Loveland (hip) is not expected to play in Week 4 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2f-deb6-a7fd-dfffa36b0000</link>
      <description>Veteran tight end Cole Kmet has played 90% or more of the offensive snaps in every game this season and ranks third on the team in route participation rate, making him a solid streaming option in a plus matchup against the Raiders. Loveland’s next opportunity to take the field comes in Week 6 when the Bears take on the Commanders following their Week 5 bye.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8c2f-deb6-a7fd-dfffa36b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
