<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (ankle) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa8-dce4-a1da-fabe4e190000</link>
      <description>The Ravens are giving Jackson a day off fairly often at this point, though this typically occurs on Wednesday. Today’s absence could simply be standard rest and rehab, but it is hardly reassuring given Jackson’s recent streak of performances. Jackson is barely on the QB1 radar for Week 14. Hopefully, he practices fully tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa8-dce4-a1da-fabe4e190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa5-dce4-a1da-fab7b7570000</link>
      <description>Benson has been sidelined since Wednesday of last week. Whether he suffered a setback or his surgically repaired knee is simply responding poorly to his ramp-up period remains unknown. At this point, Cardinals RB Bam Knight appears to be heading toward another week operating as the team’s No. 1 running back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaa5-dce4-a1da-fab7b7570000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports that returning in time for the Lions’ Week 15 game against the Rams is more “realistic” for WR Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaca-d77b-adfa-eacb4b370000</link>
      <description>Schefter punctuates the report by adding that “the team also knows St. Brown is one of the NFL’s toughest players, and if anyone can come back sooner, it’s him.” When asked whether St. Brown will face the Cowboys this evening, Schefter clarified that the team “doesn’t know yet.” If active, he should be started as an albeit risky fantasy option. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaca-d77b-adfa-eacb4b370000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Woody Marks (ankle) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ead9-d005-a9bf-fafde0ae0000</link>
      <description>Marks missed Wednesday’s practice, but DeMeco Ryans noted that he would be “fine.” Marks returning to practice on Thursday, even in what is likely a limited capacity, is proof that those words were not without meaning. The team also updated Marks’ injury from a foot to an ankle. Assuming he can go against the Chiefs, he’ll be a low-end RB2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-ead9-d005-a9bf-fafde0ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans EDGE Will Anderson (chest) returned to practice Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eadc-dce4-a1da-fade8c870000</link>
      <description>DeMeco Ryans said yesterday that Anderson would be fine. He’s been receiving some sporadic rest under the chest tag over the past couple of weeks. He’ll likely be cleared off the injury report on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eadc-dce4-a1da-fade8c870000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers OC Greg Roman said the team is “really optimistic” that QB Justin Herbert (hand) will play in Week 14 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eae1-d005-a9bf-faf529f60000</link>
      <description>This is today’s second encouraging news item regarding Herbert’s hand injury. The Chargers’ quarterback missed a portion of his team’s second drive last week after trotting into the locker room with a swollen hand and his ring finger askew. He played through the pain after that. Herbert gets the benefit of an extra day off, with the Chargers facing the Eagles, sans DT Jalen Carter (shoulders), on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eae1-d005-a9bf-faf529f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars EDGE Travon Walker (knee) is practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eae0-dce4-a1da-faf6c1960000</link>
      <description>Almost undoubtedly a limited session after missing most of the last two weeks. The Jaguars are likely checking just how much Walker can give them ahead of Sunday’s massive top-of-AFC-South showdown with the Colts. It’s his first practice since ahead of Week 11.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eae0-dce4-a1da-faf6c1960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons WR Drake London (knee) was not seen during the media portion of practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaea-d005-a9bf-fafe6a160000</link>
      <description>It’s almost sure to go down as another DNP — London’s eighth in a row — and Raheem Morris saying that London has a chance to play feels like it’s an iffy one at best from where we sit Thursday. London will almost undoubtedly be on the questionable line if he can summon up some kind of effort in practice on Friday, but we’d have to say he’s on the pessimistic side of it without some major positive reporting appearing in the next 24 hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaea-d005-a9bf-fafe6a160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers QB Aaron Rodgers (wrist) practiced on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaec-da9b-a9bf-feedb6a30000</link>
      <description>We’d be surprised if Rodgers wasn’t up for Week 14’s game against the Ravens — it’s a huge game in the AFC North standings — but he didn’t exactly deliver a lot to the table in Week 13. From a fantasy perspective, he’s a low-end superflex QB2 at best. And after his 117-yard scoreless performance, you can argue he should be even lower.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaec-da9b-a9bf-feedb6a30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports Texans DL Tim Settle (foot) will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaef-d005-a9bf-faff4d0e0000</link>
      <description>Garafolo notes that Settle should be recovered ahead of the 2026 season. Settle posted a career-best 71.3 PFF defense grade, posting 16 hurries in 215 pass rush snaps in the middle. He’ll turn 29 ahead of next season and should have a rotational interior role somewhere in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-eaef-d005-a9bf-faff4d0e0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
