<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RB Will Shipley (ribs) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-350e-db7b-a5dd-b50efcd00000</link>
      <description>Shipley suffered a rib fracture in Week 1 against the Cowboys and appears set to miss at least a few weeks. The Eagles traded for Tank Bigsby earlier this week. Though some reports have indicated the move was based on Bigsby’s abilities as a returner, it’s a little harder to buy that explanation with Shipley likely on the sidelines for a bit. Bigsby will occasionally give Saquon Barkley a breather, but he doesn’t carry any fantasy value of his own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-350e-db7b-a5dd-b50efcd00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers said experienced back tightness in Week 1 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-350f-d332-a1fd-b73f511b0000</link>
      <description>Rodgers said he “wasn’t moving that well” and ended up running into a “at least one or two sacks” because of it. Rodgers adds that his offensive line’s pass protection “was good for most of the game.” At 41 years old, back tightness can be expected. We do not think this is anything to worry about, but it’s worth keeping an eye on the injury report just in case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-350f-d332-a1fd-b73f511b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles LG Landon Dickerson (back) practiced on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3515-d93a-abbb-7d5fa4f20000</link>
      <description>Dickerson popped up on the injury report with the back issue last week but only missed one practice and did not have a game-day designation. He suited up but left Week 1 early after the back injury flared up. Given that he was spotted at practice for the first session of Week 2, it looks like he will push through the injury for Philly’s upcoming Super Bowl rematch versus Kansas City.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3515-d93a-abbb-7d5fa4f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Jayden Reed (foot) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3519-d93a-abbb-7d5bcd950000</link>
      <description>Reed practiced in a limited capacity on Tuesday and Wednesday after leading the Packers in catches (three) and targets (five) in Week 1. Reed also found the end zone and looked spry doing so. The Packers’ balanced offensive playcalling and deep wide receiver rotation hurts Reed’s odds of consistently producing ceiling games. He’s a solid FLEX option against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3519-d93a-abbb-7d5bcd950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans placed TE Cade Stover (foot) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3522-dbe3-a9bb-35736c100000</link>
      <description>This move was expected after it was reported on Monday that Stover suffered a broken foot in Week 1. Harrison Bryant was signed to the active roster in a corresponding move. Stover’s injury should lock in Dalton Schultz for a full-time role, keeping him in the TE2 mix for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3522-dbe3-a9bb-35736c100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Matthew Golden (ankle) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34df-dbe3-a9bb-34df7f400000</link>
      <description>Golden promisingly closed the week as a full participant in consecutive practices. The rookie wide receiver finished a bit light in the box score last week, but he was promisingly on the field for his position group’s second-highest snap count (23). The Packers’ balanced offensive approach and frequent wide receiver rotation reduces his reliability though. Golden is a dart-throw FLEX option in Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-34df-dbe3-a9bb-34df7f400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers LT Ikem Ekwonu (appendectomy) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3525-d332-a1fd-b7378e630000</link>
      <description>Ekwonu returned to practice last Friday but was listed as doubtful. As expected, he did not suit up on Sunday. A full week of practice will give him a better shot at playing in Week 2. Given how poor Carolina’s offense looked in their opener versus the Jags, Ekwonu’s return can’t come soon enough for Dave Canales and Bryce Young.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3525-d332-a1fd-b7378e630000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (calf) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-350b-db7b-a5dd-b50f80170000</link>
      <description>Wicks played through the injury last week, catching 2-of-2 targets for 30 yards. The Packers seem to be content with this type of output from Wicks, making him a very shaky FLEX option in 12-team leagues. He profiles as more of a DFS dart throw than a trustworthy option in re-draft formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-350b-db7b-a5dd-b50f80170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers DL Micah Parsons (back) is questionable for Week 2 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-352b-d93a-abbb-7d7b6b410000</link>
      <description>Parsons played on 30 of the Packers’ 67 defensive snaps last week. We expect him to suit up for Week 2, while hopefully increasing his snap count a bit. He produced one sack and generated a 27.3 percent pass-rush win rate. He should continue to impact the game, even if he remains on a snap count.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-352b-d93a-abbb-7d7b6b410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook (hamstring) was limited in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3532-dbe3-a9bb-3573996d0000</link>
      <description>A limited session this early in the week is typically nothing to be concerned with, but Cook’s role is already relatively light with both Ty Johnson and Ray Davis earning a few touches every week. Even a minor decline in usage because of this injury would be a notable blow to his fantasy outlook. Cook only logged 13 carries in Week 1 but managed to find the end zone and pitched in through the air with five receptions. For now, Cook can still be penciled in as a low-end RB1 for Week 2, but fantasy managers will want to keep an eye on the Bills’ injury report for the rest of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3532-dbe3-a9bb-3573996d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
