<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:03:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rams head coach Sean McVay told reporters WR Davante Adams (hamstring) is expected to play against the Panthers in the Wild Card round.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8eea-d56e-afff-eeea25e00000</link>
      <description>Adams hasn’t played since he re-aggravated his hamstring injury in Week 15 against the Lions. The 33-year-old receiver enjoyed one of his best seasons, catching 14 touchdowns from Matthew Stafford in 14 games. The Rams tried to recreate Adams in the aggregate, using tight ends and depth receivers in his spot over the last few weeks. Stafford and McVay have to be thrilled that Adams is coming back for the playoff game against the Panthers, a team that beat the Rams in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8eea-d56e-afff-eeea25e00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders fired coach Pete Carroll.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ef4-d968-a19b-def54eb80000</link>
      <description>Of all of Monday’s firings, this one will go down as the most inevitable, as well as the most necessary. Although inarguably one of the greatest football coaches in American history, Carroll proved out of ideas as the literal oldest head coach in NFL history. His plan to “run back” his final 9-8 Seahawks campaigns with Geno Smith was dead on arrival, with an archaic offensive approach somehow proving incapable of getting the ball to the likes of Brock Bowers and Jakobi Meyers. Things were even worse along the offensive line, where Carroll curiously never placed much emphasis even during his most successful seasons in Seattle. There are bigger problems than Carroll with this franchise — who exactly is in charge, for instance — but he was not going to be the solution in 2026. The Silver and Black will be hiring their fifth full-time head coach since moving to Nevada in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8ef4-d968-a19b-def54eb80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Malik Nabers told reporters if his body doesn’t feel right, he won’t play in Week 1 next season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8efc-d968-a19b-defd9e440000</link>
      <description>Nabers is recovering from surgery on his ACL and meniscus. The 22-year-old receiver told reporters Monday, “My target date is when my body feels good to get out there and I can continue to be who I am.” As for Week 1, Nabers said, “If my body doesn’t feel right (Week 1) then I’m not going to play.” Previous reports expected him to be good to go for the start of the 2026 season, though Nabers has at least introduced the possibility that his return might take longer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8efc-d968-a19b-defd9e440000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals fired coach Jonathan Gannon.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f1a-d968-a19b-dffbee160000</link>
      <description>Despite lukewarm reports over the weekend that Gannon might be safe, the Cardinals decided to move on from the 43-year-old coach after three seasons, according to ESPN’s Adam Schefter. Arizona was 15-36 under Gannon in three years, including an 8-9 campaign in 2024. This year, the Cardinals finished the season with nine consecutive losses and losses in 14 of its last 15 games, making the situation untenable. GM Monti Ossenfort will lead the search for a new coach and is in for a busy offseason with the Cardinals also likely to move on from quarterback Kyler Murray.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f1a-d968-a19b-dffbee160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Titans QB Cam Ward (shoulder) has an AC joint sprain, but no surgery is required.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f32-dc7a-af9b-cfbf3bf40000</link>
      <description>It’s good news for the Titans quarterback. While exams revealed an AC joint sprain in his shoulder, no surgery will be required. It’s the best-case scenario for the quarterback who will turn 24 in May. Ward will be under the tutelage of a new coaching staff next year as he looks to improve his accuracy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f32-dc7a-af9b-cfbf3bf40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns GM Andrew Berry said Shedeur Sanders is “still very much a work in progress, like many people.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f56-d35e-a1bf-cfd65b390000</link>
      <description>Berry also said they’d do their work on the quarterback market and that he couldn’t say if the 2026 starter was “internal or external.” It’s not exactly a ringing endorsement for running it back with Sanders in 2026 after his mistake-prone 2025 starts. The Browns also have a lot of work to do on their offensive line, so it’s possible the team tries to handle that first while letting Sanders grow in his second season. Keeper and dynasty decisions on Sanders should not treat him as if his starting job is assured at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f56-d35e-a1bf-cfd65b390000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Charvarius Ward (concussions) is contemplating retirement.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f63-dc7a-af9b-cfff7da60000</link>
      <description>Ward is quoted as saying that even a small bump on his head in normal day-to-day activity recently left him with a debilitating migraine, and adds: “I do know going into next season, if I do come back and play again, if I get one more (concussion), I’ll for sure probably retire.” A big-name free agent addition by the Colts this past offseason, Ward was only able to play seven games while dealing with brain injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f63-dc7a-af9b-cfff7da60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys CB DaRon Bland (foot) said he expects to be fully healthy for Dallas’ offseason program.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f69-d35e-a1bf-cfeb0b490000</link>
      <description>Bland will undergo foot surgery later this week after missing the final three weeks of the season with the foot ailment. Signed to an extension during training camp, Bland had a career-worst (though still fairly solid) 64.5 PFF coverage grade in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f69-d35e-a1bf-cfeb0b490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts coach Shane Steichen said the team would like to have Daniel Jones come back.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f6e-d35e-a1bf-cfeeaf5a0000</link>
      <description>For his part, Jones also told reporters in a locker room availability that he’d like to be back. Finding the right contract for a quarterback coming off a late-season Achilles tear could be a little difficult, but it sure sounds like Indianapolis’ initial plan is to run back the first part of the 2025 season and hope that the last seven games don’t happen again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f6e-d35e-a1bf-cfeeaf5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco told reporters he isn’t considering retirement and wants to play in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f73-d56e-afff-effb06c60000</link>
      <description>Flacco finished out the season as Cincinnati’s backup quarterback after Joe Burrow returned from injury in Week 13. The soon-to-be 41-year-old told reporters he’s open to staying on as Burrow’s backup, but also open to fielding calls from a team that needed a quarterback next season. It sounds like Flacco has yet another One Last Job season loading for 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8f73-d56e-afff-effb06c60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
