<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 17:14:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers beat writer Mark Kaboly reports the Steelers are “close to” hiring Vikings tight ends coach Brian Angelichio as offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2698-d629-a1bc-b69d4b5a0000</link>
      <description>Angelichio was also the Vikings’ passing game coordinator. It was not the most successful season for the Vikings’ passing game, but Angelichio had been in that role since 2022 with previous success from Sam Darnold’s and Kirk Cousins’ offenses. He worked under Mike McCarthy in Green Bay and McCarthy is going back to familiarity with the long-time NFL tight ends coach. According to Kaboly, Angelichio’s deal could be official as soon as Wednesday; he would become the Steelers’ offensive coordinator with McCarthy calling plays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2698-d629-a1bc-b69d4b5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets hired former Panthers head coach Frank Reich as their offensive coordinator.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2921-d355-a5bd-af7549b80000</link>
      <description>Reich was Stanford’s interim head coach last year in what felt almost like a favor to former quarterback Andrew Luck. Now he finds himself in a different unenviable position with the Jets. Breece Hall is a free agent. There is no real hope of grabbing a franchise quarterback in the draft or finding one in free agency, and the only quarterbacks the team have under contract for 2026 that started games are Justin Fields and Brady Cook. Reich will have to rise well above his station to get this offense to any semblance of “average” in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2921-d355-a5bd-af7549b80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dan Duggan believes Giants head coach John Harbaugh “figures to encourage a more ground-based attack.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2935-d355-a5bd-af75c3600000</link>
      <description>Duggan notes that new OC Matt Nagy ran the ball 41.7 percent of the time during his four-year tenure with the Bears, which was a middle-of-the-pack 14th in the NFL. But the Ravens ran the ball a league-high 50.6 percent of the time over the same timespan. Assuming Cam Skattebo sticks to his training camp return timeline, he figures to be used as a workhorse for the Giants. The idea of the Giants establishing it hard under Harbaugh and Nagy would only increase his fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2935-d355-a5bd-af75c3600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears GM Ryan Poles said T Ozzy Trapilo (knee) will be out “deep into next year.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-293b-d355-a5bd-af7f952a0000</link>
      <description>Trapilo suffered a torn patellar tendon against the Packers in the Wild Card round. Theo Benedet will likely be the fill-in to start the season unless the Bears want to restructure some contracts against the cap to add a depth piece they’d prefer to Benedet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-293b-d355-a5bd-af7f952a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns GM Andrew Berry said “we’re probably going to be one of the younger teams in the league” in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-293d-d89c-a1be-affffc400000</link>
      <description>Already young at quarterback, running back, and tight end, this statement reads like an admission that the Browns plan to completely retool the offensive line in 2026. Cleveland’s entire main starting line from 2025 — Joel Bitonio, Wyatt Teller, Cam Robinson, Jack Conklin, and Ethan Pocic — are all free agents. So is swingman Teven Jenkins. Bitonio, entering what would be his age-35 season, is a candidate to retire. The fact that the Browns are, per Chris Easterling, embarking on a plan that “almost assuredly lower the average age on the roster” would seem to make it plausible that they could bring back just a scant few of last year’s linemen. It would likely help keep the Browns skill positions players as “hard to trust” in fantasy football if the Browns offensive line underwent a ton of turnover, even if they upgraded at some positions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-293d-d89c-a1be-affffc400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Paul Dehner Jr. believes there’s “no realistic scenario” where EDGE Trey Hendrickson signs with the Bengals in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2951-d89c-a1be-afdf5f820000</link>
      <description>Dehner bats around the idea of a franchise tag-and-trade scenario for Hendrickson, who he projects will get something close to the $29 million per season he made in 2025 despite missing most of the year with a core muscle injury that eventually required surgery. Ultimately, both sides are probably just tired of dealing with each other after back-to-back offseasons of contentious negotiations. We’d expect the Bengals to let Hendrickson — who should be considered one of the premiere free agents this offseason — walk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2951-d89c-a1be-afdf5f820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zach Berman believes A.J. Brown will seek a trade this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2956-d355-a5bd-af5656560000</link>
      <description>Berman ominously writes “it might be difficult to put toothpaste back in this tube, and there’s too much smoke here for me to answer this question differently,” though he admits that this remains just a guess. Brown figures to be one of the major turning points of the offseason for both the Eagles and the entirety of the NFL. None of the smoke that has come out about the relationship between the Eagles and Brown has looked encouraging for him staying in Philadelphia, and GM Howie Roseman would only resort to vague hypotheticals about how hard it is to find great players when asked about a potential Brown trade after the Eagles were eliminated from the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2956-d355-a5bd-af5656560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Zach Berman believes Dallas Goedert will “play elsewhere” in 2026.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-295c-d355-a5bd-af5caabf0000</link>
      <description>Goedert and the Eagles danced around a separation for most of last offseason, including trade rumors around the NFL Draft, but Philadelphia couldn’t find a real replacement for the 31-year-old tight end. An impending free agent, we’d expect Goedert to have an interesting market but he might struggle to land a multi-year deal considering his advanced age.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-295c-d355-a5bd-af5caabf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY’s Connor Hughes believes Jacoby Brissett is “a potential trade target” for the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2980-d042-afbc-7dd218010000</link>
      <description>Brissett checks the boxes of “has worked for Frank Reich before” and “is a functional NFL quarterback.” The real question is: Why would the Cardinals give him up? He averaged 240.4 yards per start and threw 23 touchdowns in just 12 starts. Arizona has reportedly been more interested in moving on from Murray than Brissett, who GM Monti Ossenfort drafted in New England and made a priority to sign last offseason. We’d be surprised if the Jets could do this without getting fleeced by Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-2980-d042-afbc-7dd218010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants hired NFL chief football administrative officer Dawn Aponte as their vice president.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-298e-d629-a1bc-b99f3d430000</link>
      <description>Aponte was interviewed for the Chargers GM job in 2024 and also has worked for the Dolphins, Browns, and Jets. Her top experience level with the Dolphins was as executive VP of football administration, so it’s likely this role will be somewhat similar to that one. The NFL will have someone else reading draft cards on Day 2, sadly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-298e-d629-a1bc-b99f3d430000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
