<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 04:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texans RB Nick Chubb (ribs) practiced fully on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33ab-d087-addf-b3fbbbd50000</link>
      <description>Chubb is now on track to play. Texans starting RB Woody Marks (ankle), unfortunately, remains sidelined. Chubb would likely handle interior rushing duties if Marks cannot play, but RB Jawhar Jordan would change the pace and play on passing downs. In this scenario, Chubb may be able to punch in a touchdown against the lowly Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33ab-d087-addf-b3fbbbd50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders EDGE Maxx Crosby (knee) was limited on Thursday</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33af-d35e-a1bf-77ef14c40000</link>
      <description>Crosby will likely continue playing through the pain this week. He has 10 sacks this year, and he is the only Raiders defender to log more than three. Although he will make his presence felt against the Texans, he cannot stop an offense on his own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33af-d35e-a1bf-77ef14c40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Alec Pierce (Achilles) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-337e-da28-afbb-f77f54ba0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Stephen Holder tells readers to “stand down,” because this is “just a precautionary situation.” We still think this is worth following closely. It is unclear when the injury occurred. This is the Colts’ first practice of the week. They face the 49ers on Monday night. If a capable pass catcher is removed from the offense this week, it would slightly increase the target share projections for the remaining, healthy players.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-337e-da28-afbb-f77f54ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Ameer Abdullah (knee) is practicing fully for Week 16 against the 49ers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33b8-dc7a-af9b-ffbf42b50000</link>
      <description>The 32-year-old is coming off a season-high nine touches, so a sore knee makes sense. He is difficult to trust, even in PPR formats, given the one-game blip, but he appears to be a QB Philip Rivers’ preferred checkdown option. Expect him to handle passing down duties against the 49ers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33b8-dc7a-af9b-ffbf42b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts WR Josh Downs (personal) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33b9-da28-afbb-f7fd4b3f0000</link>
      <description>We fully expect Downs to be available on Monday night, but given WR Alec Pierce’s (Achilles) limited session, this is worth keeping an eye on. The Colts’ pass catchers are now vying for opportunities in a low-volume passing attack. Removing one player makes a difference. Stay tuned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33b9-da28-afbb-f7fd4b3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports Cowboys CB DaRon Bland “is facing surgery on his left foot” and is “likely going to end up on injured reserve.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33ce-d087-addf-b3fed10d0000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. Bland broke out in 2023, breaking up six passes and recording nine interceptions. He fractured his foot during the 2024 training camp and has struggled to return to form ever since. This season, Bland has broken up five passes, intercepted one pass, totaled 53 tackles and two quarterback pressures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33ce-d087-addf-b3fed10d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars signed WR Jakobi Meyers to a three-year, $60 million extension through 2028.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33c8-d087-addf-b3f81fb50000</link>
      <description>The deal reportedly includes $40 million in guarantees. Since joining the Jaguars in Week 10, Meyers leads the team in targets, receptions and yards, while scoring the second-most receiving touchdowns, catching 27-of-37 targets for 355 yards and three touchdowns. He is a versatile, inside-outside wide receiver, thriving in head coach Liam Coen’s offensive scheme. It is a healthy payday for a 29-year-old player.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33c8-d087-addf-b3f81fb50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks declared LT Charles Cross, QB Jalen Milroe, WR Jake Bobo, OL Mason Richman, OG Bryce Cabeldue, DT Brandon Pili and OLB Jared Ivey inactive for Week 16 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33a7-d35e-a1bf-77e7f7b00000</link>
      <description>Cross will be missed. The Rams’ 39.6 percent quarterback pressure rate is the seventh-best in the NFL. Bobo will be replaced by WR Dareke Young (quad), who also contributes as a returner. He was activated from injured reserve today. Both the Rams and Seahawks are 11-3, though the Rams have already secured a playoff spot. The Seahawks can take control of the NFC West with a victory this evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33a7-d35e-a1bf-77e7f7b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams declared WR Davante Adams (hamstring) inactive for Week 16 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33d5-da28-afbb-f7fdef2e0000</link>
      <description>Adams has been rehabbing this hamstring injury for weeks. He played through it without issue in Week 14 but suffered a re-injury in Week 15. Tonight’s absence was expected. It gives rookie WR Konata Mumpfield a chance to establish himself as a contributor, though expectations must be held in check. He should not be started in re-draft formats. The Rams also declared CB Ahkello Witherspoon, QB Stetson Bennett IV, RB Jarquez Hunter, OL Beaux Limmer and OLB Nick Hampton inactive in Week 16 against the Seahawks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33d5-da28-afbb-f7fdef2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans Football’s Nick Underhill believes Saints RB Audric Estime will “probably” start in Week 16 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33c3-d35e-a1bf-77c3ef550000</link>
      <description>Given last week’s results, this makes sense. Saints RB Evan Hull and Estime were left to split work after RB Devin Neal (hamstring) left the Saints’ Week 14 game against the Panthers. Hull rushed four times for 12 yards while Estime rushed three times for 11 and caught 3-of-3 targets for 39 yards via two screen passes and one checkdown. While Estime never profiled as a deft pass catcher, it evidently occurred to Saints head coach Kellen Moore that Estime’s bruising, downhill style might be transferable in the passing game, if he can pick up a head of steam. Estime should be stashed at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-33c3-d35e-a1bf-77c3ef550000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
