<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:02:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colts RB Jonathan Taylor (neck) is absent from the Week 2 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35ff-dbe3-a9bb-35ff843b0000</link>
      <description>Taylor seemed to tweak his neck towards the end of the Colts’ Week 1 victory over the Dolphins. He was a workhorse in that game, totaling 21 touches before exiting in the third quarter. The Colts were up big, which may have contributed towards Taylor not returning to the game. The neck looks to be a minor issue as Taylor is not listed on the Colts’ injury report to start out Week 2. Fantasy managers can fire him up as an RB1 against the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-35ff-dbe3-a9bb-35ff843b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans RB Kalel Mullings (ankle) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3603-dbe3-a9bb-3653ca1f0000</link>
      <description>Mullings suffered the injury in the Titans’ Week 1 loss to the Broncos, playing three special teams snaps before exiting. Julius Chestnut is the only remaining backup to Tony Pollard, with Tyjae Spears (ankle) still sidelined. Expect Pollard to take on a workhorse role for the time being.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3603-dbe3-a9bb-3653ca1f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans OT JC Latham (hip) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-360d-db7b-a5dd-b60d25130000</link>
      <description>Latham aggravated a preseason hip injury in Week 1 against the Broncos. The 22-year-old tackle played 45 snaps before exiting, with Oli Udoh replacing him at right tackle. Latham’s status for Week 2 and the foreseeable future remains in doubt. Also not practicing for the Titans Wednesday were S Quandre Diggs (hand) and DT T’Vondre Sweat (ankle).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-360d-db7b-a5dd-b60d25130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Colby Parkinson (shoulder) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3613-dbe3-a9bb-3653cafb0000</link>
      <description>Parkinson suffered a sprained AC joint in the Rams’ Week 1 win against the Texans and starts out the week not practicing. Fellow tight end Davis Allen (knee) was limited on Wednesday. With both tight ends banged up, rookie second-rounder Terrance Ferguson may see an increase in opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3613-dbe3-a9bb-3653cafb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams OL Kevin Dotson, Rob Havenstein, and Steve Avila did not participate in Wednesday’s practice due to ankle injuries.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3622-d332-a1fd-b63681180000</link>
      <description>Dotson, Havenstein, and Avila all popped up on the injury report with ankle issues to start Week 2. Head coach Sean McVay had said Dotson and Avila are week-to-week with their ankle injuries, but Havenstein’s status remains up in the air. Matthew Stafford’s protection will look slim should any or all of these three miss time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3622-d332-a1fd-b63681180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears CB Kyler Gordon (hamstring) and DT Grady Jarrett (knee) were estimated non-participants in Wednesday’s walk-through practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3627-dbe3-a9bb-36772a4d0000</link>
      <description>Gordon and Jarrett were the only non-participants for Chicago on Wednesday. Gordon has been rehabbing a hamstring strain since last month and missed Week 1. Meanwhile, Jarrett is dealing with a knee injury from Monday’s loss to the Vikings. Wednesday’s injury report is an estimate, so Bears fans can stay tuned later in the week to see if the defenders practice in time for Week 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3627-dbe3-a9bb-36772a4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears RB Roschon Johnson (foot) was estimated as a limited participant in Wednesday’s walk-thru practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3637-d93a-abbb-7f7f06280000</link>
      <description>Johnson closed out last week with a limited practice after two DNPs, so starting out this week with a limited practice estimation indicates he is on his way back from a foot injury. Kyle Monangai is currently the backup to D’Andre Swift, though he did not receive any carries Week 1. Johnson has had little production in two years in the league, but could provide handcuff value upon his return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3637-d93a-abbb-7f7f06280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR DJ Moore (abdomen/groin) and CB Jaylon Johnson (calf/groin) were estimated full participants in Wednesday’s walk-thru practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-363b-d332-a1fd-b63f5bd10000</link>
      <description>Moore took a big hit towards the end of the Bears’ Week 1 loss to the Vikings, giving fantasy managers concerns over his health status. He finished out the game and is now estimated as a full participant in Wednesday’s walk-thru, indicating he is good to go. Meanwhile, Johnson sat out Week 1 with his injuries and appears to be a step closer to returning with a full practice estimation on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-363b-d332-a1fd-b63f5bd10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (shoulder) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-363f-db7b-a5dd-b63f2e8a0000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter had reported yesterday that Jennings was “day-to-day” with a shoulder issue. The 28-year-old was hurt in the 49ers’ Week 1 win over the Seahawks, but and MRI did not show extensive damage to his shoulder. He starts out the week missing practice, putting his status to return immediately for Week 2 in jeopardy. With George Kittle on IR and Brock Purdy likely out, the 49ers are running out of fantasy-relevant offensive players early on in the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-363f-db7b-a5dd-b63f2e8a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers RB Christian McCaffrey (calf/rest) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3649-d332-a1fd-b67fd0a90000</link>
      <description>There’s a chance we see McCaffrey pop up with the calf/resting player designation several times throughout the season as the 49ers try to manage his workload and prevent aggravation of his prior calf injury. His limited practice last week had fantasy managers concerned, but he took on a large workload in the 49ers’ Week 1 win over the Seahawks. Expect McCaffrey to play in Week 2 while continuing to take on a large offensive workload with nearly every other offensive skill player hurt for the 49ers..</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-3649-d332-a1fd-b67fd0a90000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
