<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:01:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown (shoulder) did not practice Wedneday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c8d-deb6-a7fd-7fdf60ec0000</link>
      <description>Brown exited Week 3’s win over the Texans with the shoulder injury and did not return. In his absence, Parker Washington functioned as a full-time wideout and four of 11 targets for 34 yards, leading the Jaguars in targets somehow. Brown would have to get in at least a limited practice by Friday if he has any hope to suit up in Week 5 against the 49ers. Washington would be a deep league option if Brown is out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c8d-deb6-a7fd-7fdf60ec0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants head coach Brian Daboll said QB Jaxson Dart will start for the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c9d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfcbe20000</link>
      <description>Daboll said it was his decision to bench Russell Wilson and install Dart as the rest-of-season starter. He refused to explain his thinking when asked about Wilson’s benching, which came after a disastrous performance on Sunday night against the Chiefs. Dart will get his first NFL start in Week 4 against a stingy Chargers defense that last week stalled the Broncos passing attack. Dart should bring more aggressive downfield passing to the mix and will likely take off and run more than Wilson. He’ll be viable in superflex formats this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7c9d-deb6-a7fd-7fdfcbe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants coach Brian Daboll said Tyrone Tracy (shoulder) is expected to miss a few weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ca9-dca3-a9fb-7db903970000</link>
      <description>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported a 2-4 week timeline for Tracy earlier this week. Daboll’s comments corroborate that story. As expected, Tracy won’t practice today. It would be a surprise to see him on the field at any point this week. The New York backfield is now Cam Skattebo’s for the taking. Skattebo turned 16 touches into 121 yards and a touchdown in the Giants’ Week 3 loss to the Chiefs. He was the lone bright spot on an otherwise dreadful offense that has since changed quarterbacks. Expect Daboll to lean on his ground game in Jaxson Dart’s first start, meaning an even larger workload for Skattebo in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ca9-dca3-a9fb-7db903970000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Nabers did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cba-deb6-a7fd-7fff39f00000</link>
      <description>Giants head coach Brian Daboll didn’t say why Nabers is absent from today’s practice, but it likely has something to do with the hard hit he took in Week 3 against the Chiefs. Russell Wilson threw a jump ball in the end zone to Nabers, who was promptly sandwiched between two Chiefs defenders before slamming into the turf. Nabers briefly left the game but was back on the field after a once-over by the training staff. Nabers is constantly dealing with some minor injury. He almost always finds a way to play through his various ailments. We will expect the same from him this week for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cba-deb6-a7fd-7fff39f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs coach Todd Bowles said TE Ko Kieft suffered a broken leg in Week 3 and will miss the remainder of the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ccf-d95b-addb-7ccf61b90000</link>
      <description>Kieft doesn’t have any targets this year but has been on the field for 14 percent of Tampa Bay’s offensive snaps, serving primarily as a blocker. He also pitches in frequently on special teams. Backup tight end Payne Durham could see a few more snaps each week with Kieft out of the picture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ccf-d95b-addb-7ccf61b90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Person reports Tetairoa McMillan does not appear to be practicing on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cd2-deb6-a7fd-7fdf010f0000</link>
      <description>Both T-Mac and Xavier Legette were in street clothes for the open portion of practice. It’s possible their activity ramps up later in the session, but it looks like both will go down as DNPs on Wednesday. Legette missed Week 3 with a hamstring issue but was at least limited for all three practices. A DNP would suggest the issue isn’t progressing as expected. McMillan’s injury is new, though it could be a maintenance day for the high-usage wideout. We will get more info when the Panthers drop their first injury report of the week later today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cd2-deb6-a7fd-7fdf010f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles placed OLB Nolan Smith on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ceb-dca3-a9fb-7dfb97f20000</link>
      <description>Smith reportedly re-injured the triceps muscle that he tore during Super Bowl LIX. He underwent surgery to repair the torn tissue this offseason. The Eagles believe Smith will not require surgery and hope to have him back “around” their Week 9 bye. Players placed on injured reserve are eligible to return after missing four games. The Eagles also placed CB Jakorian Bennett and WR Darius Cooper on injured reserve with undisclosed injuries. Both players are likewise expected to avoid surgery and are expected to return around Week 9. The Eagles signed S Marcus Epps, TE Cameron Latu, and CB Parry Nickerson to the active roster, and LB Lance Dixon, DB Eli Ricks, and WR Quez Watkins to the practice squad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ceb-dca3-a9fb-7dfb97f20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans CB Derek Stingley Jr. (oblique) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ce7-dca3-a9fb-7dff50fd0000</link>
      <description>Stingley left Week 3 with the injury and was quickly ruled out. Texans head coach DeMeco Ryans called him day-to-day on Monday. A DNP to open the week is an ominous sign for the shutdown corner. The Texans have been leaning on their stout defense to start the season while their offense attempts to get on track. Losing Stingley would be a notable blow to their secondary. Stingley has three pass breakups and eight tackles this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7ce7-dca3-a9fb-7dff50fd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb (ankle) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cf7-deb6-a7fd-7fffaa4b0000</link>
      <description>This doesn’t come as a surprise. Lamb suffered a high-ankle sprain in Week 3 and could miss upwards of four weeks. ESPN’s Adam Schefter called him “unlikely” to play in Week 4. Though he hasn’t been ruled out by the Cowboys yet, we fully expect that to happen on the final injury report of the week. Jake Ferguson caught 13 passes in Week 3 and is in line for a monstrous workload sans Lamb. George Pickens should also see an uptick in intermediate looks, rounding out his fantasy profile and making him a more reliable WR2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7cf7-deb6-a7fd-7fffaa4b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terry McLaurin met with core muscle specialist, Dr. William Meyers, to discuss what has been reported as a quad injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d05-d95b-addb-7d4768f70000</link>
      <description>We already knew that McLaurin was seeking a second opinion after suffering a leg injury against the Raiders in Week 3, but meeting with a core muscle specialist is a bit surprising. Groin injuries often fall into the core muscle category, and Meyers recently performed surgery on Bears CB Jaylon Johnson, who suffered a groin injury in Week 2 that has sidelined him indefinitely. McLaurin’s injury has been reported as a quad issue. The two muscle groups obviously neighbor each other, so this could just be precautionary. It’s worth noting that the injury could be more complex than initial reports indicated, though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7d05-d95b-addb-7d4768f70000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
