<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 23:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Travis Etienne rushed 12 times for 27 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 6 loss to the Seahawks, adding four receptions for 28 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da90-d94a-a79d-db9daf660000</link>
      <description>With the Jags struggling to sustain drives through the air or on the ground, Etienne’s 55 yards from scrimmage were a new season low. Etienne has actually been held below 60 total yards in three of his past four appearances, dramatically cooling off from his surprisingly hot start. Not great for fantasy managers who thought they maybe had a league-winner on their hands, but at least for now, Etienne is not losing meaningful volume to Bhayshul Tuten. He’s a floor-based RB2 for Week 7 against the Rams in England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da90-d94a-a79d-db9daf660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon had two rushes for one yard in the Dolphins’ Week 6 loss against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da90-dd4c-afb9-ffd101790000</link>
      <description>Gordon, who had averaged 4.5 carries per game headed into Week 6, was invisible in this one, as De’Von Achane dominated the Miami backfield. Gordon should be stashed in most fantasy leagues in case Achane misses any time, in which case Gordon would be a locked-in top-15 option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da90-dd4c-afb9-ffd101790000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bhayshul Tuten rushed two times for 12 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 6 loss to the Seahawks, adding two receptions for 14 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da98-db72-a199-fadb0c900000</link>
      <description>Stuck in the 3-5 touch zone for the better part of the month, Tuten isn’t making workload inroads behind Travis Etienne despite the veteran back’s recent mediocre statlines. Perhaps the Jags will shake things up when they return from bye in Week 9, but for now, Tuten isn’t a viable FLEX option for Jacksonville’s Week 7 London road trip to face the Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da98-db72-a199-fadb0c900000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (ankle) is questionable to return in Week 6 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da4a-db72-a199-fa4b199a0000</link>
      <description>Wicks was announced as questionable to return in the fourth quarter. Before exiting, he caught 2-of-2 targets for 15 yards against the Bengals. Wicks took a backseat to X-receiver Romeo Doubs and rookie WR Matthew Golden, who was incorporated as both a receiver and a rusher. Wicks could face stiffer target competition soon, with WR Christian Watson (knee) expected to return in the coming weeks. Wicks does not need to be rostered in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da4a-db72-a199-fa4b199a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tre’ Harris caught 4-of-5 targets for 24 yards in the Chargers’ Week 6 win against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da93-def2-abdb-dff3957b0000</link>
      <description>Harris functioned as the team’s No. 3 receiver with Quentin Johnston (hamstring) sidelined. Harris finished fourth in targets on the day, working mostly as a short-area target for Justin Herbert. Harris, a rookie, will likely lose this role if Johnston is able to return to the lineup in Week 7 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da93-def2-abdb-dff3957b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dyami Brown caught 2-of-5 targets for 13 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 6 loss to the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da9c-d94a-a79d-db9d10b50000</link>
      <description>It’s an identical statline to Brown’s Week 5 return. Neither Brian Thomas Jr. nor Travis Hunter are setting the world on fire in the Jags’ top-two receiving spots, but Brown is destined to remain a strict role player even with Brenton Strange (quad, hip) on the shelf.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da9c-d94a-a79d-db9d10b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will Dissly caught both of his targets for 18 yards in the Chargers’ Week 6 win against the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da9d-d94a-a79d-db9d4f780000</link>
      <description>Oronde Gadsden II, meanwhile, had seven receptions for 68 yards on eight targets against Miami. Gadsden appears to have taken over the primary pass-catching tight end role in Greg Roman’s offense. Dissly can be left on the waiver wire for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da9d-d94a-a79d-db9d4f780000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tory Horton was held without a catch on one target in the Seahawks’ Week 6 win over the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da9e-db72-a199-fadf81750000</link>
      <description>The catch-less outing was Horton’s first since the opener. It came as Cooper Kupp scored his first Seahawks touchdown, and AJ Barner posted a new career high for yardage for the second consecutive week. With this a narrow target tree in a limited-volume offense, Horton has little shot at carving out consistent WR5 value behind Kupp and WR1 overall candidate Jaxon Smith-Njigba.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-da9e-db72-a199-fadf81750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Higbee caught 4-of-4 targets for 40 yards and a touchdown in the Rams’ Week 6 win over the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-daa2-def2-abdb-dfe3265d0000</link>
      <description>The yards were a new season high, the catches matched a season high, and the touchdown was his first of 2025. The big day, relatively speaking, came with Puka Nacua battling an ankle injury. Nacua is highly questionable for Week 7 against the Jaguars in London, meaning Higbee could be needed for an extra target or two. He will still have a hard time even approaching the top 24 at tight end, let alone cracking it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-daa2-def2-abdb-dfe3265d0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
