<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 19:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Ravens QB Lamar Jackson could be out again for Week 8’s matchup with the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1b73-dab4-a3fb-9b7390f00000</link>
      <description>While Ravens coach John Harbaugh said Jackson had a full practice Friday, Rapoport passes along that the 28-year-old quarterback actually ran the scout team. Couple that with Harbaugh being noncommittal about Jackson starting this week and Jackson could be another week away from playing. Tyler Huntley would be in line to start against the Bears if Jackson is unavailable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1b73-dab4-a3fb-9b7390f00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Bengals EDGE Trey Hendrickson (hip) is expected to play against the Jets in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1bc0-d245-adfb-9fdf5dd90000</link>
      <description>Hendrickson missed Week 7’s game against the Steelers on a short week, but he appears to be ready to return against the Jets in Week 8. The defensive end who turns 31 in December was a limited participant in practice for most of the week. Hendrickson could be a name to watch as the trade deadline approaches, though the Bengals have some momentum coming off a win that got them to 3-4 last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1bc0-d245-adfb-9fdf5dd90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Ravens QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) is out for Week 8’s matchup with the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1bcb-dab4-a3fb-9bfb902e0000</link>
      <description>Following a report early Saturday morning from NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport that Jackson could miss Week 8, Schefter is now reporting Jackson will in fact miss the game against the Bears with Tyler Huntley set to start. While Jackson was able to practice this week, Rapoport reported at least some of that practice work came while running the scout team. Jackson has a good chance to return in Week 9 on Thursday against the Dolphins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1bcb-dab4-a3fb-9bfb902e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders WRs Terry McLaurin (quad) and Deebo Samuel (heel) will play in Week 8 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c30-d245-adfb-9d7f7f590000</link>
      <description>No surprise here as McLaurin and Samuel each had consecutive full practices this week. For McLaurin, it was the first time he had practiced in full since Week 2. The 30-year-old receiver has missed the last four games with a quad injury. The Commanders will be happy to have him back, though the team will be without starting quarterback Jayden Daniels (hamstring), which dings each receivers’ fantasy value just a bit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c30-d245-adfb-9d7f7f590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens ruled out QB Lamar Jackson (hamstring) for Week 8 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c35-d245-adfb-9d7fce0c0000</link>
      <description>Jackson’s Friday practice and game status was curiously updated Saturday afternoon by the Ravens after multiple reports that he would miss the Week 8 matchup with the Bears. Maybe the Ravens just need to brush up on their order of operations, but changing Jackson’s Friday practice status from a full to a limited participant on Saturday afternoon is something the league might want to look into. Tyler Huntley is poised to start for the Ravens this week while Jackson sets his sights on a Week 9 return against the Dolphins on Thursday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c35-d245-adfb-9d7fce0c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New York Post’s Brian Costello reports Jets QB Justin Fields will start against the Bengals in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c46-d245-adfb-9d5f3d620000</link>
      <description>New York’s other option Tyrod Taylor was questionable and his since been ruled out with a knee injury. Given the Jets’ refusal to publicly name a quarterback prior to Taylor being ruled out, it’s safe to say the team wasn’t planning on giving Fields another start here. With six teams on bye week and quarterback injuries around the league, Fields is an upside QB2 against the Bengals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c46-d245-adfb-9d5f3d620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New York Post’s Brian Costello reports Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (knee) has been ruled out against the Bengals in Week 8.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c49-dab4-a3fb-9f7989b50000</link>
      <description>Taylor was likely in line to start over Justin Fields this week, but he popped up on the injury report earlier this week. The 36-year-old quarterback practiced in a limited fashion for most of the week. While Jets coach Aaron Glenn told reporters Friday that Taylor was trending in the right direction, he still refused to name a starting quarterback. Depending on how Fields does against the Bengals, Taylor could be an option to start for the Jets as soon as Week 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c49-dab4-a3fb-9f7989b50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets downgraded WR Josh Reynolds (hip) to out for Week 8 against the Bengals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c55-d5d8-a3ff-fd754d660000</link>
      <description>The Jets will now be without their top two receivers, in addition to quarterback Tyrod Taylor, for their game against the Bengals. Rookie tight end Mason Taylor is also listd as questionable but is expected to play, potentially serving as the top pass-catcher for Justin Fields in a plus matchup for tight ends.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c55-d5d8-a3ff-fd754d660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants downgraded S Jevon Holland (knee) to out for Week 8 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c7e-dab4-a3fb-9f7e0d9a0000</link>
      <description>Holland’s absence is big news for a Giants team also without cornerback Paulson Adebo. The fantasy upside of DeVonta Smith and Dallas Goedert continues to grow as Sunday approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-1c7e-dab4-a3fb-9f7e0d9a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
