<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka (hamstring) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12ba-deb1-a39b-33be6da20000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from Wednesday’s DNP. Egubka logged 12 targets while playing 75.4 percent of the snaps against the Lions on Monday night. A short week ahead of Tampa Bay’s game against the Saints probably contributed to his DNP estimated practice on Wednesday. Given he played through the injury last week and is participating in practice more often than he did ahead of MNF, we’d bet on him playing in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12ba-deb1-a39b-33be6da20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns WR Jerry Jeudy (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12b8-d5d8-a3ff-fbf94cba0000</link>
      <description>Jeudy is now trending toward playing in Week 8 against the Patriots, but he barely warrants FLEX consideration. The Browns’ wide receiver has produced one WR3 finish and two WR4 finishes in seven games this season. Patriots CB Christian Gonzalez will likely cover Jeudy on the perimeter. It is a situation to avoid in most cases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12b8-d5d8-a3ff-fbf94cba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baker Mayfield (knee) practiced in full on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12bd-d5d8-a3ff-fbfd555b0000</link>
      <description>It’s an upgrade from Wednesday’s limited session. Mayfield did notably sail some balls on Monday night while not looking 100 percent comfortable, but it was never particularly likely that he’d miss any time. He’ll be a good-to-go QB1 against the Saints in Week 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12bd-d5d8-a3ff-fbfd555b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns TE David Njoku (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12bc-deb1-a39b-33beed3f0000</link>
      <description>Njoku is on track to play through the pain in Week 8 against the Patriots. The Browns’ veteran tight end was seen wearing a sizable brace on his left leg, but Njoku is no stranger to playing through injury. Assuming he is active, he belongs in the TE1 ranks and will likely compete with rookie TE Harold Fannin Jr. for the team lead in targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12bc-deb1-a39b-33beed3f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bucs S Antoine Winfield (toe) was limited in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12bf-dab4-a3fb-9bff0d270000</link>
      <description>It seems like, with Wednesday’s practice being a walkthrough, the Buccaneers opted to go easy on some of their veterans. Lavonte David (knee/rib) and Winfield both upgraded from DNPs to limited sessions on Thursday, putting them in line to play. The same can’t be said for EDGE Haason Reddick (ankle/knee), who remained a DNP and could be in line to miss more weeks. We’re a little surprised Todd Bowles didn’t rule out Reddick when he said that Bucky Irving and Chris Godwin weren’t going to play this week, but he did say they were still waiting for the results of his MRI when asked about it on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12bf-dab4-a3fb-9bff0d270000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR Stefon Diggs (chest) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12be-deb1-a39b-33be9fb60000</link>
      <description>The Patriots kept Diggs limited on Wednesday and Thursday before allowing him to practice in full on Friday. He is seemingly on track to do the same this week. He caught 7-of-7 targets for 69 yards against the Titans, once again operating as the team’s top target earner. He can be expected to do so again this week against the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12be-deb1-a39b-33be9fb60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle (hamstrings/rest) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12c3-d5d8-a3ff-fbe323890000</link>
      <description>It was a new injury listing, though it’s hard to understand how serious it is with the “rest” designation added. Waddle’s absence — should that be where this heads — would be enormous for the Dolphins, who would have to build an entire passing game out of Malik Washington and Nick Westbrook-Ikhine. As it is, we don’t want to overreact to it, but Waddle will be a major domino on the injury report watchlist on Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12c3-d5d8-a3ff-fbe323890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers RB Josh Jacobs (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12c6-deb1-a39b-33ce59cd0000</link>
      <description>Jacobs logged a season-low 14 touches in Week 7, his first game with fewer than 20, yet tied for the overall RB7 finish in half-PPR scoring. The Packers are smartly managing his practice repetitions in the lead-up to their Week 8 game against the Steelers. Jacobs remains firmly in the RB1 tier this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12c6-deb1-a39b-33ce59cd0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers WR Christian Watson (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12c1-d5d8-a3ff-fbe180c30000</link>
      <description>Watson told reporters yesterday that he plans to play in Week 8 against the Steelers, but his limited participation keeps him firmly in the questionable category. If active, one would expect Watson to play on a snap count in his first game back from a torn ACL, and the Packers already rotate their wide receivers frequently, as is. Fellow Packers WR Dontayvion Wicks (calf) remains sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12c1-d5d8-a3ff-fbe180c30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens WR DeAndre Hopkins (illness) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12cd-d245-adfb-97dff4b20000</link>
      <description>Hopkins is the only Ravens player to miss practice on Thursday, and an illness is unlikely to sideline the veteran wide receiver on game day. Hopkins sneaks into the FLEX conversation, if active, with six teams on bye, but he largely serves as a fantasy-point booster for whichever quarterback is under center against the Bears this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-12cd-d245-adfb-97dff4b20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
