<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:04:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson (chest) exited in the third quarter of Week 15’s game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f2b-d77b-adfb-dfab54be0000</link>
      <description>Watson, who is questionable to return, was targeted on a deep ball by Jordan Love and fell hard to the ground. What appeared to be a shoulder injury was later listed as a chest injury. He remained down for several minutes before making his way to the sideline and later the locker room. If he doesn’t return, Watson’s day will end with a 3-29-0 line on five targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f2b-d77b-adfb-dfab54be0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adonai Mitchell caught 6-of-9 targets for 58 yards and a touchdown in the Jets’ Week 15 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f2c-d77b-adfb-dfafaa290000</link>
      <description>Mitchell’s second touchdown in three weeks was a nine-yard strike from Brady Cook in the second quarter. It was an end zone laser where Mitchell displayed sure hands. All three of Mitchell’s catches, targets and yards were his second most as a Jet since arriving from Indianapolis. Good stuff, but this is probably about his ceiling right now with Gang Green down to its No. 3 quarterback. We have no idea who will be under center for Week 16 in New Orleans, but Cook is probably the favorite. Mitchell will be a passable WR4 no matter who gets the call.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f2c-d77b-adfb-dfafaa290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashee Rice caught 7-of-11 targets for 51 yards in the Chiefs’ Week 15 loss against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f30-d005-a9bf-df342d340000</link>
      <description>Rice easily led the Chiefs in targets but didn’t make much of the opportunity with short-area look from Patrick Mahomes, who went down in the fourth quarter with a serious knee injury. Rice missed a portion of Week 15’s loss after taking a vicious shot to the upper body on an intermediate target in double coverage. Three of Rice’s past five outings have been ordinary, leaving doubts about whether Rice will have any upside in the season’s final two weeks. Rice will be a low-end WR2 option in Week 16 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f30-d005-a9bf-df342d340000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Watson (chest) will not return in Week 15 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f3d-d77b-adfb-dfbfbdbc0000</link>
      <description>Watson exited in the third quarter with a chest injury and went to the locker room for X-rays after leaving the field. He was ruled out shortly after, as his day now comes to an end with a 3-29-0 receiving line on five targets. We’ll likely know more on the specifics of his injury soon, but the oft-injured receiver could be at risk of missing a pivotal Week 16 game at the Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f3d-d77b-adfb-dfbfbdbc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Metchie caught 4-of-5 targets for 25 yards in the Jets’ Week 15 loss to the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f3d-d77b-adfb-dfbf8bc00000</link>
      <description>The good news: Metchie has now caught at least four passes in four consecutive contests. The bad: He has not exceeded 34 yards in any of the past three weeks. Throw in the Jets’ ongoing quarterback carousel, and you have a No. 2 wideout struggling for WR4 relevance in fantasy football. There are worse 14-team league plays, but far, far better 12-team league options.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f3d-d77b-adfb-dfbf8bc00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micah Parsons (knee) exited in the third quarter of Week 15’s game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f44-d1bc-a3fb-9f6405b00000</link>
      <description>This one didn’t look good. Parsons suffered a non-contact knee injury late in the third quarter while pursuing Bo Nix and remained down for several minutes after the play. The injury occurred to his left knee when he attempted to change direction, and Parsons was in obvious pain. He eventually walked off the field with the assistance of trainers, but this has the potential to be a devastating injury for Parsons and the Packers’ sixth-ranked defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f44-d1bc-a3fb-9f6405b00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakobi Meyers caught 5-of-7 targets for 71 yards in the Jaguars’ Week 15 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f45-d77b-adfb-dfc713280000</link>
      <description>Meyers led the Jags’ receiver corps in receiving but not their skill corps, as Travis Etienne somehow turned his three catches into 3/73/3. Meyers’ 71 yards were his second most as a Jag. Good stuff, if maybe a bit disappointing on an afternoon where Jacksonville erupted for 48 points. Somehow, four of Trevor Lawrence’s five passing scores went to running backs. 5/71 is close to both Meyers’ weekly floor and ceiling. That makes him a perfectly fine WR3, but not much more as fantasy managers go upside hunting during the playoffs. The Broncos are a brutal Week 16 matchup for the Jags’ pass catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f45-d77b-adfb-dfc713280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys declared WR Jalen Tolbert, RB Jaydon Blue, T Tyler Guyton, DT Jay Toia, and DT Perrion Winfrey inactive for Week 15 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f47-d77b-adfb-dfc7e0b20000</link>
      <description>Guyton continues his rehab from a high-ankle sprain suffered in Week 12, leaving Nate Thomas to draw another start. The Cowboys enter Sunday Night Football in desperate need of a win as they aim to keep their fading playoff hopes alive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f47-d77b-adfb-dfc7e0b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thomas caught 4-of-7 targets for 66 yards and a touchdown in the Jaguars’ Week 15 win over the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f49-d005-a9bf-df7dbbf30000</link>
      <description>This was Thomas’ second straight “pretty good” game, though “pretty good” was not what fantasy managers were signing up for in the second round. Astoundingly, his four catches were his most since Week 6. We are getting signs of life from one of the season’s biggest fantasy disappointments, but not performances that say he needs to be jammed back into your WR2 spot. That is especially true for tough matchups like next week’s date with the Broncos in Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f49-d005-a9bf-df7dbbf30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings declared QB John Wolford, OLB Chaz Chambliss, T Christian Darrisaw, T Walter Rouse, DL Elijah Williams inactive for Week 15 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f48-d005-a9bf-df7ce79a0000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw’s absence is bad news for the Vikings considering the strength of the Dallas defense is their ability to generate pressure in the backfield. Furthermore, quarterback J.J. McCarthy has been highly sensitive to pressure during his sophomore campaign. Look for head coach Kevin O’Connell to continue the ball-out-quick mentality that saw McCarthy experience a bump in efficiency from a week ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1f48-d005-a9bf-df7ce79a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
