<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said QB Marcus Mariota would start in Week 15 against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0951-d8cf-affb-bd7b634f0000</link>
      <description>Daniels did not suffer structural damage to his injured left elbow last week against the Vikings, Quinn added. It appears the listless Commanders are intent on protecting Daniels from further setbacks in a lost season. Mariota, who has a higher drop back EPA than Daniels through Week 14, would profile as a superflex option against the soft Giants defense allowing the league’s fifth highest rate of yards per play this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0951-d8cf-affb-bd7b634f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders head coach Dan Quinn said the team is not shutting down QB Jayden Daniels (elbow) for the season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-095d-d8cf-affb-bd7f3b4d0000</link>
      <description>There seems to be no real plan for how to handle Daniels in the final weeks of a disastrous season for Washington. Daniels, after aggravating his elbow injury in Week 14 against the Vikings, has been ruled out for Week 15’s game against the Giants. Quinn said Daniels will practice this week for some reason. Marcus Mariota, who has a higher drop back EPA than Daniels this season, will draw another start and becomes a viable streaming play in 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-095d-d8cf-affb-bd7f3b4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor (groin) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0965-da9b-a9bf-df6d56950000</link>
      <description>With Taylor and Justin Fields (knee) sidelined, Brady Cook will get all the first-team practice reps ahead of the team’s Week 15 game against the Jaguars, according to head coach Aaron Glenn. Cook threw for 163 yards, no touchdowns, and two interceptions while completing 46.7 percent of his passes against the Dolphins in relief of Taylor last Sunday. He would be a significant downgrade for all New York pass catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0965-da9b-a9bf-df6d56950000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Justin Fields (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0968-d77b-adfb-cbeb3de50000</link>
      <description>Tyrod Taylor was also a DNP on Wednesday after injuring his groin last week against the Dolphins. Undrafted rookie QB Brady Cook is set to see all the first-team practice reps ahead of the Jets’ Week 15 game against Jacksonville. Cook, who had 163 yards, no touchdowns, and two interceptions against Miami, would barley be startable even in superflex formats this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0968-d77b-adfb-cbeb3de50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor said Tee Higgins (concussion) will practice on a “very limited basis” on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-096e-d8cf-affb-bd6e66a20000</link>
      <description>Higgins was checked for a concussion multiple times on Sunday but never officially left the game with an injury designation. He wound up scoring twice in a losing effort to the Bills. Higgins then reported concussion symptoms after the game and entered the league’s concussion protocol. That he is on the field practicing in any capacity today is a good sign for his Week 15 availability. Higgins will need to get up to a full practice before being cleared for action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-096e-d8cf-affb-bd6e66a20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals designated EDGE Shemar Stewart (knee) to return from injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-097b-da9b-a9bf-df7f08a00000</link>
      <description>Stewart will return to practice this week. The Bengals now have 21 days to activate him from injured reserve. The first-round rookie hasn’t played much this year because of ankle and knee injuries. He has six combined tackles and eight pressures in five appearances so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-097b-da9b-a9bf-df7f08a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamar Jackson was not seen at Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-098d-d8cf-affb-bdafa5a10000</link>
      <description>This is standard operating procedure for Jackson at this point. He had been held out of Wednesday practices for a few weeks until suiting up for last Wednesday’s session. The Ravens instead chose to hold him out of Thursday’s practice. Jackson has been listed with more injuries than we can count over the past month. None of them has caused him to miss any playing time. We fully expect him to suit up versus the Bengals this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-098d-d8cf-affb-bdafa5a10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keaton Mitchell (knee) practiced on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0985-da9b-a9bf-df8de3810000</link>
      <description>Mitchell suffered a knee injury in the Ravens’ Week 14 loss to the Steelers. He left the game early and was subsequently ruled out. An MRI after the game revealed it to be only a minor injury. All signs point to Mitchell suiting up for Week 15 versus the Bengals. The explosive backup will sit in the RB4 ranks for a potential shootout in Cincinnati.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0985-da9b-a9bf-df8de3810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drake London (knee) will not play in Week 15 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0993-d8cf-affb-bdbbf2540000</link>
      <description>A short turnaround to Thursday Night Football made it all but impossible for London to suit up this week. London did not practice this week and hasn’t played since suffering a sprained PCL in Week 11. Nearing the end of a lost season, the Falcons would gain little by rushing him back. His status for Week 16 is now up in the air as well. Kyle Pitts will continue operating as the team’s de facto No. 1 receiver this week, putting him in the TE1 ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0993-d8cf-affb-bdbbf2540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Pitts (knee) is questionable for Week 15 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0999-da9b-a9bf-df9dc1a60000</link>
      <description>Pitts was listed as limited in practice throughout the week before receiving the questionable designation. He appears to be trending toward playing, but fantasy managers will want to check in on Atlanta’s inactives before setting their lineups. With Drake London already ruled out, Pitts will project for TE1 numbers if he is good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-0999-da9b-a9bf-df9dc1a60000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
