<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:09:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>De’Von Achane rushed 14 times for 67 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 9 loss to the Ravens, adding six receptions for 39 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3856-d45b-affe-7dd689e20000</link>
      <description>Continuing to operate with efficiency on the ground and volume through the air, Achane lost a seventh catch to a questionable second half review overturn. Achane looked smooth and explosive vs. the Ravens’ shaky defense, but Tua Tagovailoa couldn’t sustain drives long enough for Achane to get enough handles on the ground. Fantasy managers will still take the 100-plus yards and six receptions. Operating as a high-floor RB1, Achane gets the Bills’ awful run defense in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3856-d45b-affe-7dd689e20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zay Flowers caught 5-of-5 targets for 64 yards in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-385a-d713-ad9e-7c5ebd4a0000</link>
      <description>5/64 meant it was not a disastrous night in PPR leagues, but fantasy managers will lament that Lamar Jackson threw for four scores and none of them went his No. 1 wideout’s way. Then again, Jackson’s overdue return to the lineup means Flowers will have an enhanced floor and elevated ceiling going forward. That includes for Week 10 against a swarming Vikings defense that is nevertheless prone to surrendering big plays. Flowers is a strong WR2 who will mix in WR1 statlines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-385a-d713-ad9e-7c5ebd4a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Andrews caught 2-of-3 targets for 22 yards and two touchdowns in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-385e-d1e7-a1fa-7afe890f0000</link>
      <description>It was the second time in five days Andrews commanded only three targets. The difference this time, as you can see, is that he scored two touchdowns. The first was a two-yarder on a first quarter fourth down where Andrews got lost in the back of the end zone. The second was a 20-yarder where two Dolphins defenders freed Andrews by running into each other. Sometimes it’s better to be lucky than good. Elsewhere, Andrews converted a tush push as a runner and watched Isaiah Likely turn his four targets into 3/60. With Likely and Lamar Jackson finally both healthy at the same time, Andrews’ already perilously low floor could be sinking even lower. He will be more of a TE2 than TE1 for Week 10 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-385e-d1e7-a1fa-7afe890f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely caught 3-of-4 targets for 60 yards in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3863-d713-ad9e-7c77de1c0000</link>
      <description>Finally healthy at the same time as Lamar Jackson, Likely more than doubled his previous season production and was just four yards off Zay Flowers for the team lead. Likely’s biggest gain was a 35-yard catch-and-run as time expired in the first quarter. Always capable of long gainers down the seam, Likely could be something of a second half X-factor for the Ravens, though he’s probably still a lower-end TE2 as he fights Mark Andrews for seam looks in a run-based offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3863-d713-ad9e-7c77de1c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Malik Washington caught 3-of-3 targets for 48 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 9 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3866-d673-a39e-bcf7edca0000</link>
      <description>Washington also lost a fourth quarter fumble in a red zone pileup at the Ravens’ 14-yard line. Not ideal. His 48 yards receiving were at least a new season high after he reached that number twice as a rookie. Decent enough, but Washington is still stuck on 3-6 weekly targets even after Tyreek Hill was lost for the season. WR4 value is not materializing. Maybe that will change for Week 10 for a Bills contest where the Dolphins will undoubtedly have to throw more than they would like.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3866-d673-a39e-bcf7edca0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ollie Gordon II rushed two times for six yards in the Dolphins’ Week 9 loss to the Ravens before departing with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3869-d673-a39e-bcf9a4c20000</link>
      <description>Rolled up late in the second quarter, Gordon was announced as “questionable” but never returned despite standing on his own two feet on the sideline. Hopefully he has avoided a high-ankle sprain with 10 days to heal up for Week 10 against the Bills. Before the injury, Gordon slipped and drew a bogus tripping penalty, wiping out a 36-yard Jaylen Waddle grab. The Dolphins have wanted to get Gordon more involved but perpetually poor game scripts is going to make it difficult for the No. 2 back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3869-d673-a39e-bcf9a4c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rashod Bateman caught 2-of-4 targets for 13 yards and a touchdown in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3871-d673-a39e-bcf113410000</link>
      <description>The touchdown was nice, but even with Lamar Jackson returning, tonight was the seventh time time in eight 2025 appearances Bateman was held to two-or-fewer catches. The one-time WR4 is now in danger of tumbling out of the top 60 even with Jackson back at the controls following a one-month absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3871-d673-a39e-bcf113410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Dulcich caught 5-of-5 targets for 49 yards in the Dolphins’ Week 9 loss to the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3873-d713-ad9e-7c7761110000</link>
      <description>Promoted from the practice squad eight days ago after the Dolphins lost Darren Waller to a pec injury, Dulcich wasn’t targeted against the Falcons in Week 8 but surprisingly caught just one fewer pass than each of Jaylen Waddle and De’Von Achane this evening. Although we would like to think it is something to build off of for a former hype merchant who is still only 25 years old, it is far more likely to be a fluke. Dulcich isn’t worth a re-draft FAAB expenditure ahead of Week 10 against the Bills. Maybe you can toss one more Hail Mary in dynasty leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3873-d713-ad9e-7c7761110000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keaton Mitchell rushed four times for 11 yards in the Ravens’ Week 9 win over the Dolphins, adding a seven-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3877-d713-ad9e-7c770b6c0000</link>
      <description>Five touches for 18 yards is nothing to call home about, but this was the second consecutive week Mitchell out-touched Justice Hill. He was also cutting into Hill’s breather back snaps behind workhorse Derrick Henry. Hunting for sparks as they keep digging out of the hole from their 1-5 start, the Ravens are probably committed to increasing Mitchell’s role at Hill’s expense. Just don’t expect it to turn into 12-team league value any time soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3877-d713-ad9e-7c770b6c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puka Nacua said he is “ready to go” for Week 9 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3a41-d45b-affe-7fd7a7eb0000</link>
      <description>We still have one day of practice to go, but it sounds like Nacua, who said he feels “fantastic” after Friday’s full practice, is shaping up for a return in Week 9. Head coach Sean McVay said at the start of the week that he expected Nacua to be good to go for this week’s game against the Saints, and things are clearly trending in that direction. We’ll see what happens on Friday, but it wouldn’t be surprising if Nacua was removed from the injury report entirely before the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3a41-d45b-affe-7fd7a7eb0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
