<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 03:28:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Russell Wilson completed 3-of-5 passes for 107 yards and one interception in the Giants’ preseason game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b547-d45c-a7fc-b75f96c80000</link>
      <description>Wilson’s signature deep ball was on full display in this one. The Giants’ QB1 completed an 80-yard pass to rookie UDFA Beaux Collins, who was taken down at the Jets’ one-yard line, and later found Jalin Hyatt on a 21-yard completion early in the second quarter. Wilson again attempted another deep ball late in the second quarter to Collins, which resulted in an interception. Although it’s worth noting, there appeared to be confusion regarding the route between Wilson and Collins. Wilson has now completed 10-of-13 passes for 136 yards in two preseason games, and remains the expected starter when the Giants open Week 1 against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b547-d45c-a7fc-b75f96c80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Braelon Allen rushed seven times for 34 yards in the Jets’ preseason game against the Giants.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b55b-d90d-a5bd-b75b57560000</link>
      <description>Breece Hall rushed seven times for 26 scoreless yards, but perhaps more notable than Allen’s rushing performance was his usage on third downs. Per PFF, Allen appeared on all five first downs the Jets faced when Allen was in, while Hall failed to see a third-down snap. There’s a chance this is by design as the Jets continue to ready for Week 1 against the Steelers, but it is worth noting that Hall has not played a third-down snap through two preseason games. Entering his second season and playing under a new coaching regime, Allen is expected to play a big role that could prove valuable for fantasy even if Hall remains the lead back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b55b-d90d-a5bd-b75b57560000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emeka Egbuka caught 1-of-2 targets for five yards and a touchdown in the Buccaneers’ preseason Week 2 game against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b533-d05a-adda-bfb34ed50000</link>
      <description>Egbuka played the first three series of the game before hitting the sidelines, catching his five-yard touchdown as the final play of his night. Egbuka appears locked into a legitimate early-season role for the Bucs, one that could further grow pending the status of Chris Godwin to start the regular season. That leaves him with an enticing risk-reward profile in the middle rounds of fantasy drafts this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b533-d05a-adda-bfb34ed50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers HC Kyle Shanahan said RB Patrick Taylor (shoulder) will miss a couple of weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b563-df63-a199-fd6b2d060000</link>
      <description>Taylor exited Saturday’s preseason game against the Raiders with the injury and did not return to the field. Rookie UDFA Corey Kiner also exited with a high-ankle sprain and is expected to miss a couple of weeks. The 49ers are already dealing with injuries to Isaac Guerendo (shoulder) and rookie Jordan James (knee). Behind Christian McCaffrey is journeyman Ke’Shawn Vaughn and the recently re-signed Jeff Wilson, who rushed for 8-16-1 against the Raiders while adding another catch for 16 yards. Both Vaughn and Wilson could spell McCaffrey in Week 1 against the Seahawks if Guerendo, James, and Taylor are all sidelined. That said, none of these players carry much fantasy upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b563-df63-a199-fd6b2d060000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jalen McMillian (neck) exited Saturday’s game against the Steelers and did not return to the field.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b56a-df63-a199-fd6b9c6e0000</link>
      <description>McMillian was cut down by Steelers DB Darryl Porter on a contested catch and landed on his neck. The second-year receiver was subsequently folded in half upon hitting the ground and remained down after the play. Thankfully, and surprisingly, he was able to walk off under his own power before eventually being carted to the locker room. Although he was seen sporting a neck brace after the game, McMillan was cleared to fly home with the team. McMillan isn’t expected to make much of an impact to start the season, but could have some value on the outside if Mike Evans were to ever miss time. He caught one pass for 18 yards in Saturday’s game. It was also reported later by the team’s site that McMillan wasbeing evaluated for a concussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b56a-df63-a199-fd6b9c6e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miles Sanders rushed seven times for 15 yards Saturday in the Cowboys’ preseason game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b573-df63-a199-fd7bc5140000</link>
      <description>Just days after it was reported the Cowboys had no clear leader for their RB1 role, it’s safe to assume Sanders didn’t do anything to separate himself from the pack. The veteran running back drew the start in Saturday’s contest, playing 11 snaps while handling seven carries. His longest rush came on a seven-yard gain. Rookie Jaydon Blue (ankle) wasn’t active for this one, and Javonte Williams, who is healthy, was held out. We can’t say for certain that this is the worst backfield in football, but there’s little reason to believe a bona fide stud emerges from this group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b573-df63-a199-fd7bc5140000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaxson Dart completed 14-of-16 passes for one touchdown in the Giants’ preseason game against the Jets, adding two carries for five additional yards and one touchdown.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b58e-df63-a199-fdaf804a0000</link>
      <description>The Giants’ rookie signal-caller continues to impress, and played on another level on Saturday night. While his 87.5 completion percent is impressive on its own, we can’t overlook the fact that Dart completed the final 13 passes he attempted on the day, and capped his final drive with a one-yard score on a QB sneak. Dart was in control throughout the afternoon and slung a nicely thrown ball to Greg Dulcich for a 20-yard score on the opening drive of the third quarter. Despite two solid preseason performances, Dart isn’t expected to unseat Russell Wilson before Week 1’s game against the Commanders, but it’s safe to assume he’s rapidly bridging the gap and could soon find himself earning first-team reps in practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b58e-df63-a199-fdaf804a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Milton completed 9-of-18 passes for 122 yards, one touchdown, and one interception in the Cowboys’ preseason game against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b593-d90d-a5bd-b7db95a00000</link>
      <description>At one point, Milton was 3-of-10 passing. The second-year quarterback who took a sack for a safety on his team’s opening drive looked as erratic as we’ve seen during his time as a pro, and ended the day with an absurd 15.2 ADOT. Milton missed his intended target all night, with PFF attributing just one of his incompletions to a dropped pass. His best play on the night came on a 49-yard completion to Jonathan Mingo, but it’s hard to ignore what we’ve witnessed from Milton through two preseason games. He’s completed 26-of-47 passes (55.3 percent) for one touchdown and two interceptions, and has taken three sacks on 10 pressures. Thankfully for the Cowboys, Dak Prescott is healthy, but it may be time for the Cowboys to explore additional depth behind their QB1 after Milton appears to have reverted to the player we saw for parts of six college seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b593-d90d-a5bd-b7db95a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sixth-round rookie Tyler Loop has been named the Ravens’ starting kicker.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b5f2-d05a-adda-bff2f1a50000</link>
      <description>“He’ll be the kicker,” coach John Harbaugh confirmed after Saturday’s preseason game. “He’s earned it.” Loop was always the favorite to replace Justin Tucker by virtue of having draft capital. Despite his rookie status and strong if not impeccable college pedigree, Loop is immediately fantasy relevant as the kicker for one of the league’s highest-scoring offenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b5f2-d05a-adda-bff2f1a50000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens coach John Harbaugh revealed Keaton Mitchell’s injury is to his hamstring, but that he could return this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b5f5-d45c-a7fc-b7ffcdef0000</link>
      <description>It’s not a major concern, but the 23-year-old has now been sidelined over a week as he tries to challenge Justice Hill for change-of-pace work behind Derrick Henry. It all but guarantees he will begin the season as a somewhat distant No. 3 back, keeping him off the radar in most 12-team leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-b5f5-d45c-a7fc-b7ffcdef0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
