<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders signed WR Marquez Callaway.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ae5-d05a-adda-bae73ce70000</link>
      <description>Cut after the draft by the Buccaneers and by the 49ers in training camp, Callaway continues his quest to be rostered for the 2025 season. He has five targets and no catches since 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ae5-d05a-adda-bae73ce70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Cameron Heyward said “It’s hard for me, after the year that I had, to really justify playing at the number I’m playing at.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9aea-d90d-a5bd-bafb2e4c0000</link>
      <description>It’s possible Heyward is just letting his thoughts be known while he seeks a reworked deal, but it’d be foolish to think these comments may not foreshadow a potential holdout or hold-in at some point before the season starts. Heyward, 36, is currently the 22nd-highest paid defensive tackle in the league and is coming off his fourth First-Team All-Pro season since 2017. ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported last week that Heyward and the Steelers “have not made any progress” in talks for a new deal, which has likely led to the star lineman growing increasingly disgruntled as the season approaches. Heyward signed a three-year extension just last offseason, which may further complicate things. It’s safe to assume this won’t be the last we hear from Heyward on the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9aea-d90d-a5bd-bafb2e4c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns listed Shedeur Sanders as their QB4 on their second unofficial depth chart.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b05-d90d-a5bd-bb5f9fef0000</link>
      <description>We take these depth charts with a grain of salt, but for anybody who thought the team would reward Sanders for his preseason performance with a higher spot on the depth chart, that would appear not to be the case. Sanders was solid in his first taste of pro football, throwing for 138 yards and two scores in nearly three full quarters of play. For now, Joe Flacco, Kenny Pickett, and Dillon Gabriel all remain ahead of Sanders on the depth chart. He should see plenty of action in the Browns’ next preseason game, which will come on Saturday against the Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b05-d90d-a5bd-bb5f9fef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns DE Myles Garrett was cited for doing 100 mph in a 60 mph zone early Saturday morning.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b3e-df63-a199-db3f13d90000</link>
      <description>Browns beat reporter Mary Kay Cabot broke the news first, stating that the star defensive end was cited going 100 mph in a 60 mph zone just after 2 am Saturday morning after the team returned from Charlotte. Cabot also noted that Garrett had “vowed to slow down” after flipping his Porsche and that the team was aware of his citation. This is unlikely to draw any league discipline but demonstrates an alarming pattern of reckless driving out of Garrett.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b3e-df63-a199-db3f13d90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans TE Brevin Jordan (leg) injured Monday at practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b42-d90d-a5bd-bb5bc1cb0000</link>
      <description>From the words of Texans beat reporter Aaron Wilson, “He appears to be in serious pain. Lot of noise coming from the field team huddled around him. Practice halted as Brevin Jordan is hurting very badly. Inconsolable.” We’ll need official word from the team before any conclusions can be drawn, but it certainly looks like an unfortunate injury for a tight end that was attempting to come back from a lost season in 2024 due to a torn ACL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b42-d90d-a5bd-bb5bc1cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens hosted RB Boston Scott for a visit over the weekend.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b68-d05a-adda-bbea7f740000</link>
      <description>Scott is reportedly healthy and looking for the right opportunity to contribute, saying he’s in “terrific” shape. He last played in 2023, his sixth season with the Eagles, and could make sense for a team like the Ravens as a contingent third-down option and special teams contributor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9b68-d05a-adda-bbea7f740000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Insider Jordan Schultz reports Saints OG Will Clapp suffered “a serious foot injury that is believed to be season-ending.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ba5-d05a-adda-bba77d8f0000</link>
      <description>Reports surfaced earlier Monday that Clapp sustained the injury but it wasn’t until Schultz’s report that we had any clue into the severity. Schultz adds that the foot injury is likely to require surgery and would keep Clapp out for the duration of the 2025 regular season, a tough blow to the veteran after he was brought in to operate as a sixth offensive lineman for the Saints. The team is awaiting final confirmation pending follow-on testing but it appears as if Clapp’s season is over before it began.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9ba5-d05a-adda-bba77d8f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Cook practiced Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9e69-d45c-a7fc-9e7b762b0000</link>
      <description>Bills head coach Sean McDermott, meanwhile, said “things have changed” in Cook’s ongoing contract talks with the team. Tuesday would mark Cook’s first practice of training camp after he reported refused to play in last weekend’s preseason game against the Giants. It appears his hold-in is over — for now — and he could be on his way to starting Week 1 for the Bills. Cook is coming off an 18-touchdown season thanks to heavy red zone usage he did not see in his first two NFL seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9e69-d45c-a7fc-9e7b762b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said WR Darnell Mooney (shoulder) will play at some point in 2025.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9e84-df63-a199-dfaf956d0000</link>
      <description>Morris’ comments about the injured Mooney suggest the wideout could miss significant time in the regular season. “Kind of just waiting and rolling. Kind of a week-to-week basis,” Morris said of Mooney, who will miss training camp with his shoulder injury. “I feel good about getting him back healthy and ready to go. When? I don’t know. We’ll have him back healthy this year, though.” Mooney in 2024 was a mainstay in two-receiver sets and had 992 receiving yards and five touchdowns as Atlanta’s WR2. His absence would open more routes and targets for KhaDarel Hodge and Ray-Ray McCloud, the team’s primary slot receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9e84-df63-a199-dfaf956d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants WR Malik Nabers (shoulder) did not practice Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9e89-d90d-a5bd-bedb1f4b0000</link>
      <description>Nabers said last week that it’s “part of the plan” for him to miss portions of Giants practice in the coming weeks as he deals with a shoulder issue. Hopefully Nabers can fully ramp up in the days before the team’s regular season opener against the Commanders. Last year, Nabers had 19 catches for 186 yards and one touchdown in two games against Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-9e89-d90d-a5bd-bedb1f4b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
