<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 22:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Emanuel Wilson had 18 rushes for 44 yards in the Packers’ Week 18 loss against the Vikings, adding one catch for four yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8af9-d968-a19b-daf9fa050000</link>
      <description>Wilson got the start in Week 18 with Josh Jacobs resting his various leg injuries ahead of the postseason. Wilson had an efficient day if you eliminate an 18-yard loss on a third quarter rushing attempt where Wilson kept reversing field looking for some kind of opening. Wilson will return to his RB2 role behind Jacobs in the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8af9-d968-a19b-daf9fa050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylin Noel caught his only target for 13 yards in Houston’s Week 18 win over the Colts.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8afc-dc7a-af9b-cffff83f0000</link>
      <description>Noel managed just 11 offensive snaps, but still outgained Christian Kirk (39 snaps, minus-3 yards on two targets) in the box score. We don’t get it, and we haven’t all season. The Texans look happy with him as a kick returner but Noel has made no real in-roads to a starting job in the 2025 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8afc-dc7a-af9b-cffff83f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunnar Olszewski caught 8-of-9 targets for 103 yards in a Week 18 win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8afb-d35e-a1bf-cffbecfc0000</link>
      <description>Olszewski also threw a pass on a reverse and had a wide-open receiver in the end zone, but he bounced the pass. The 29-year-old is primarily a special teamer and came into today with two catches on four targets for 43 yards and one touchdown. He is highly unlikely to be a receiving option in 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8afb-d35e-a1bf-cffbecfc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Josh Downs caught 4-of-4 targets for 61 yards in Indianapolis’ Week 18 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aff-d35e-a1bf-cfffd6860000</link>
      <description>Downs didn’t exactly suffer an efficiency drought. He still caught four touchdowns, he played well when he was healthy. The Colts simply crowded him off the field after drafting Tyler Warren and watching Alec Pierce have a breakout season. Downs played only 58.4 percent of the offensive snaps through Week 17, and only took over 70 percent of the snaps in two games with Philip Rivers towards the end of a doomed season. Entering the final year of his rookie deal, Downs is a plausible WR3 if the Colts move on from Michael Pittman Jr. and/or Pierce. He just needs an every-down role to actually have fantasy value.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8aff-d35e-a1bf-cfffd6860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Warren caught 5-of-8 targets for 26 yards in Indianapolis’ Week 18 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b01-dc7a-af9b-cfbf2ef00000</link>
      <description>The standard pre- and post-Daniel Jones splits for Colts skill players hit Warren. He averaged five receptions and 61.7 yards per game over Indy’s first 10 games. From Weeks 11-17, with Jones injured and later lost for the season, Warren averaged 3.5 catches for 29 yards a game, scoring just once. He remains a plausible TE1, and will have top-five upside cases entering the offseason as the Colts could lose Alec Pierce in free agency and move on from Michael Pittman Jr. Warren isn’t a special mover, but he’s a stellar technician with more tackle-breaking power than you’d expect based on his pure size.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b01-dc7a-af9b-cfbf2ef00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Pittman caught 2-of-4 targets for 11 yards in Indianapolis’ Week 18 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b02-dc7a-af9b-cfbf03d80000</link>
      <description>Through the first 10 weeks of the season, Pittman was averaging 5.4 catches and 58 yards with six touchdowns. Afterwards, with Daniel Jones hurt and then out for the year, he had just one game with more than 10 targets and cracked 35 yards just once from Weeks 11-17. Entering his age-29 season, Pittman has a wide range of offseason outcomes. His $29 million cap hit is prohibitive enough that the Colts could release him, trade him, or re-sign him to lower his cap hit. All that we’re sure about is he’s not playing on that cap number. Alec Pierce could re-sign with the Colts, or he could move on and vacate targets. Pittman’s upside case is in the WR2 range, but the median in his range of outcomes is probably more like a high-end WR4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b02-dc7a-af9b-cfbf03d80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Bellinger caught both of his targets for 38 yards and a touchdown in a Week 18 win over the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b00-dc7a-af9b-cfbf23260000</link>
      <description>Bellinger’s touchdown catch was on a shovel pass from Jaxson Dart. Dart was under heavy pressure and evaded a sack by throwing a back-handed toss to Bellinger, who caught the ball just inches off the ground and rumbled 29 yards for a touchdown. The 25-year-old had some moments of success earlier in the season when the Giants’ receiving room was really banged up and will finish with 19 catches on 26 targets for 286 yards and two touchdowns. He’ll be a free agent in the offseason, and it remains to be seen if he’ll return to his committee role in New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b00-dc7a-af9b-cfbf23260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clayton Tune completed 6-of-11 attempts for 34 yards in the Packers’ Week 18 loss against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b01-d35e-a1bf-cfc354810000</link>
      <description>Tune got the start with Jordan Love resting for the postseason and Malik Willis inactive with multiple injuries. He had negative passing yardage until the final few minutes of the game in a game plan that included 11 passes and 33 rushing attempts. Tune was sacked four times and pressured on almost every drop back. He’ll go back to QB3 status in the playoffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b01-d35e-a1bf-cfc354810000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mo Alie-Cox caught 3-of-4 targets for 22 yards in Indianapolis’ Week 18 loss to the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b02-d968-a19b-dbf3e7d20000</link>
      <description>Cox barely cracked 100 yards for the season with this effort, leading a major comeback effort with 58 receiving yards in his last three games to get it done. He’ll be ticketed for free agency this offseason and the Colts let him languish there before re-signing him just ahead of the draft in 2025, so the 32-year-old is no guarantee to be back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b02-d968-a19b-dbf3e7d20000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
