<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:01:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Chiefs G Trey Smith (ankle) won’t play in Week 13 against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c067-d90e-a9da-df6f994a0000</link>
      <description>Smith sustained two sprains on the same ankle in the team’s Week 12 game against the Colts and did not practice Tuesday ahead of KC’s Thanksgiving matchup with the Cowboys. It’s a blow to the Chiefs offense, as Pro Football Focus grades Smith as the NFL’s tenth best pass-blocking guard this season. The Dallas front seven has been much improved over the past three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c067-d90e-a9da-df6f994a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Patriots LT Will Campbell (knee) will miss at least four weeks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c06c-d90e-a9da-df6fb7750000</link>
      <description>Campbell went down with an MCL injury in Week 12 against the Bengals. Russini said Campbell, who has excelled as a pass protector this season, “will most likely land on injured reserve” and could return for the postseason. Losing Campbell could mean more pressure on Drake Maye, who in Week 12 struggled against pressure. On the season Maye has completed 55 percent of his throws when facing pressure and has averaged 8.2 yards per attempt, the third highest mark in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c06c-d90e-a9da-df6fb7750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Vikings QB J.J. McCarthy (concussion) is not expected to play in Week 13 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c071-d6c4-abfb-d673d4940000</link>
      <description>After another catastrophic outing in Week 12 against the Packers, McCarthy was placed in the league’s concussion protocol. Rookie QB Max Brosmer is slated to start for Minnesota against a tough Seattle defense. It’s hard to imagine Brosmer playing any worse than McCarthy has over the past few weeks. Look for the Vikings to remain a run-heavy offense in Week 13 and beyond. Brosmer should be rostered in superflex formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c071-d6c4-abfb-d673d4940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports George Pickens (calf/knee) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c075-d6c4-abfb-d677bd5e0000</link>
      <description>Pickens practiced Tuesday ahead of the Cowboys’ Thanksgiving Day matchup against the Chiefs. He should be a full go and remain in fantasy lineups. Pickens this season is second in the NFL in receiving yards — trailing only Jaxon Smith-Njigba — and sixth in air yards. He has functioned as the team’s No. 1 wideout for most of the past month while CeeDee Lamb struggles with drops. Look for the Cowboys to go pas heavy against a KC defense that has been tough against the run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c075-d6c4-abfb-d677bd5e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Josh Jacobs (knee) is expected to play in Week 13 against the Lions.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c092-d82c-a79a-f39612210000</link>
      <description>Dealing with a bone bruise on his knee, Jacobs was limited in Tuesday’s practice and should be good to go for Thanksgiving Day against Detroit. Whether he’ll see his usual massive workload remains to be seen, especially after Emanuel Wilson acquitted himself well as the Packers’ starting back in Week 12 against the Vikings. Jacobs, who has at least 17 carries in seven games this season, should be locked into all fantasy lineups for Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c092-d82c-a79a-f39612210000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Jayden Daniels (elbow) could return in Week 14 against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c0c0-db57-afda-d6f2ee7e0000</link>
      <description>Daniels is expected to remain sidelined in Week 13 against the Broncos, with Marcus Mariota drawing the start against an elite Denver defense. Though there’s not much point in Daniels returning to the Commanders in a lost season, he could be under center for Week 14 barring setbacks to the gruesome elbow injury he sustained in early November. Daniels should remain a fantasy bench stash until then. Mariota is barely a superflex-worthy play in Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c0c0-db57-afda-d6f2ee7e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports the Vikings could pursue QB Daniel Jones in free agency this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c0c5-d82c-a79a-f3d5b53c0000</link>
      <description>The Vikings let Jones walk in free agency last offseason, along with Sam Darnold. With the J.J. McCarthy experiment all but dead after his historically awful play in 2025, Fowler said the Vikings could sign a veteran to compete for the startig QB job in 2026. “The funny thing about that scenario is Jones would be an ideal fit in Minnesota, where he backed up Sam Darnold last season. But as the top free agent quarterback, he will score a sizable deal in Indianapolis or elsewhere,” Fowler said. “Still, the Vikings really liked Jones, and their situation this offseason will be far different than the one from a year ago. Making a play for Jones would give him multiple options to consider.” Though Jones has struggled of late, his play is much improved from his final seasons in New York. He could have several free agency suitors barring a disastrous finish to the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c0c5-d82c-a79a-f3d5b53c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Jones (fibula) was limited during Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c102-d82c-a79a-f396cfac0000</link>
      <description>Jones sustained the injury near the end of the Colts’ Week 12 loss to the Chiefs. He should be OK for Week 13 against a stingy Houston defense that shut down Josh Allen and the Bills last week. It’s an awful matchup for Jones, who struggles immensely under pressure. He should not be started in 12-team one-QB fantasy formats this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c102-d82c-a79a-f396cfac0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills released WR Elijah Moore.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c111-db57-afda-d733d33d0000</link>
      <description>The Bills this week signed veteran journeyman Brandin Cooks, making Moore expendable after he appeared in nine games for the team this season and had nine catches for 112 yards. Moore could land with a receiver-needy team in the coming weeks, though he would likely remain a rotational player. Moore had 61 receptions for 538 yards and a touchdown last year in Cleveland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c111-db57-afda-d733d33d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons head coach Raheem Morris said Drake London (knee) is doubtful for Week 13 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c113-d6c4-abfb-d7133d040000</link>
      <description>The Falcons seem intent on playing it safe with their superstar wideout during the final weeks of another lost season. It wouldn’t be a surprise if London doesn’t see the field again in 2025 after sustaining a knee injury in Week 11. Look for Darnell Mooney to continue functioning as the Falcons’ de factor WR1 with London sideline. Mooney had 71 yards and a touchdown on three targets last week against the Saints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c113-d6c4-abfb-d7133d040000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
