<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:01:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Ravens are looking for a head coach to “invigorate” QB Lamar Jackson.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9913-d35e-a1bf-ddd309d20000</link>
      <description>Rapoport added that a new Baltimore head coach would ideally “reach” Jackson and “get the absolute most” out of the two-time NFL MVP. Jackson, who appeared checked out and low-effort at time in 2025, will remain the centerpiece of the Ravens offense in the aftermath of John Harbaugh’s firing after 18 years at the helm. There was reportedly a rift between Jackson and Harbaugh in the months leading up to Harbaugh’s dismissal. Jackson in 2025 saw a significant statistical drop off from his wildly efficient 2024 season. His passing success rate (46 percent) was the third lowest of his NFL career and he took a sack on 10.3 percent of his drop backs, the highest rate of his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9913-d35e-a1bf-ddd309d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills placed DT Jordan Phillips (ankle) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9933-d35e-a1bf-ddf39b150000</link>
      <description>The Bills will enter the postseason without one of their main run stoppers. It’s a tough break for a Buffalo front seven that has been one of the softest against the run throughout the 2025 season, allowing the third highest yards per carry and the most rushing touchdowns. It sets up well for Travis Etienne in the Wild Card round against the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9933-d35e-a1bf-ddf39b150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNY TV’s Connor Hughes reports the Giants are “all in” on hiring former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9942-dc7a-af9b-dfff285e0000</link>
      <description>Though they’ll likely interview a few head coaching candidates, it looks like the Giants are ready to do what it takes to land Harbaugh after he was fired by the Ravens following 18 years at the helm. “Just about every team has interest in him (obviously), but the other that I heard is increasingly interested is the Falcons,” Hughes said. Harabugh would be tasked with making the right hires to develop Jaxson Dart, particularly as a passer. Even with Dart, Harbaugh would be entering a rebuild of a Giants team with major roster holes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9942-dc7a-af9b-dfff285e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports former Falcons head coach Raheem Morris will interview with the Titans, Cardinals, and Giants for their head coaching vacancies.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995a-dc7a-af9b-dfff37180000</link>
      <description>Morris, fired by the Falcons after going 20-25 over three seasons, will join a bevy of former head coaches and coordinators in interviewing with the Cardinals, Titans, and Giants, who are reportedly “all in” on hiring former Ravens head coach John Harbaugh. Morris, 49, struggled with in-game decision making and was among the league’s most conservative fourth down decision makers during his three years in Atlanta. His defensive background would be appealing to any of these three teams after their defenses collapsed in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995a-dc7a-af9b-dfff37180000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns requested an interview with Bengals offensive coordinator Dan Pitcher for the team’s head coaching vacancy.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995e-d56e-afff-fffe56850000</link>
      <description>Pitcher, 39, has garnered some head coaching interest in previous hiring cycles but has never been considered a leading candidate for any job. He would be a long shot to land the Browns head coaching job, though the team could fall back on Pitcher if other, more experienced candidates turn down one of the most thankless jobs in football. Pitcher is known for his work with quarterbacks — a key qualification for anyone who gets the head coaching gig in Cleveland. Pitcher once worked for the Colts scouting department alongside Browns general manager Andrew Berry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-995e-d56e-afff-fffe56850000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills head coach Sean McDermott said Josh Allen (foot) was a “full go” for Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-996c-d968-a19b-d9fd7fb00000</link>
      <description>Allen played just one snap in a meaningless Week 18 against the Jets after struggling with a foot injury the week before. Allen, among the toughest NFL players in recent memory, should be fine for the Bills’ Wild Card game against the Jaguars. Jacksonville’s ability to stop the run could force Allen into more drop backs than usual. He’s had more than 30 pass attempts in a game six times in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-996c-d968-a19b-d9fd7fb00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills opened the 21-day practice window for S Damar Hamlin (pec).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-996f-dc7a-af9b-dfff5d6d0000</link>
      <description>Hamlin could return as soon as this week against the Jaguars in the Wild Card round. He’s been sidelined since early October with the pectoral injury. Hamlin would likely be a rotational player in the Buffalo secondary against the Jags. He had one tackle and zero interceptions before his pec injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-996f-dc7a-af9b-dfff5d6d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Steelers head coach Mike Tomlin could part ways with the team this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9972-d968-a19b-d9f3550c0000</link>
      <description>While Fowler conceded there “is no firm evidence as of now” that Tomlin will walk away from the Steelers head coaching job following the 2025-26 season, a source close to Tomlin “believes stepping away is at least a possibility.” Another source told Fowler Tomlin will return to the team for a 20th season at the helm. Fowlers said Tomlin “would be more intrigued by doing TV than returning to the coaching market, should he leave the Steelers. The source wonders what Tomlin has left to chase as an NFL coach.” The team rallied around Tomlin in December and January when it was clear his job could be on the line without a postseason berth. It’s possible Monday night will be Tomlin’s final game on the Pittsburgh sideline, however.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9972-d968-a19b-d9f3550c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (knee) practiced in a limited capacity on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-997e-d35e-a1bf-ddfedc600000</link>
      <description>Kincaid should be able to suit up in the Wild Card round against the Jaguars if he can practice in some capacity on Thursday and Friday. Kincaid, who had three receptions for 48 yards last week against the Jets, could be a key player for Buffalo as they face the NFL’s most extreme pass-funnel defense. Jacksonville allows 8.7 tight end targets per game, the second highest mark in the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-997e-d35e-a1bf-ddfedc600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills K Matt Prater (quad) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9986-d35e-a1bf-ddc63f3f0000</link>
      <description>Prater appeared to re-injure his quad in Week 18’s meaningless game against the Jets and is now iffy for the Wild Card round against Jacksonville. The Bills could re-sign veteran journeyman K Michael Badgley, who spent time on the practice squad in December. Prater has converted 18 of his 20 field goal tries this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-9986-d35e-a1bf-ddc63f3f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
