<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns declared RT Jack Conklin, CB Cameron Mitchell, DT Mike Hall, QB Shedeur Sanders, G Zak Zinter, RB Raheim Sanders, and S Damontae Kazee inactive for Week 3 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cec-d1b3-a5dd-6dfd69aa0000</link>
      <description>Conklin’s absence due to an eye injury is bad news for Joe Flacco and the Browns’ passing offense as they take on Micah Parsons and a ferocious Green Bay front seven that has wreaked havoc through two weeks of the regular season. Green Bay’s defense is an elite fantasy option against Flacco and the Browns. Harold Fanni and David Njoku could see plenty of check downs from Flacco against the Packers’ pass rush, which has pressured passers at a 27 percent rate this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cec-d1b3-a5dd-6dfd69aa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons declared WR Jamal Agnew, CB AJ Terrell, OL Jack Nelson, WR Casey Washington, and DL Sam Roberts inactive for Week 3 against the Panthers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ce6-dfde-a1bd-7eef81290000</link>
      <description>Agnew has been dealing with a groin injury that caused him to miss Week 2. He did not practice all week and will now miss Week 3 against the Panthers. Also out is Casey Washington (concussion) as the Falcons will have to rotate around the injuries for the lower half of the receiving depth chart. Terrell was ruled out earlier in the week with a hamstring issue after leaving Week 2 with the injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ce6-dfde-a1bd-7eef81290000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Emeka Egubka (hip/groin) is active for Tampa Bay’s Week 3 game against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cea-d93f-ad9d-7eef77c20000</link>
      <description>It does sound like there’s some question as to how much he will play in Week 3 with Adam Schefter saying that he’s expected to have his snaps monitored and limited. Egbuka is on pace to score in every game of his career, which would be a record. It sounds like he’ll have less chances to do so today and may need to be treated as a borderline WR3. Inactive for the Buccaneers are: WR Chris Godwin (knee), T Tristan Wirfs (knee), RB Josh Williams, TE Devin Culp, CB Kindle Vildor, and S Rashad Wisdom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cea-d93f-ad9d-7eef77c20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles declared QB Sam McKee, DE Azeez Ojulari, RB Will Shipley, DE Ogbo Okoronkwo, LB Patrick Johnson, OL Drew Kendall and OL Kenyon Green inactive for Week 3 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cea-d93f-ad9d-7eef52860000</link>
      <description>McKee will be the third QB for the tilt against Los Angeles, with Sam Howell operating as the backup to Jalen Hurts. Shipley is out with an oblique injury, paving the way for Tank Bigsby and A.J. Dillon — not necessarily in that order — to get the carries behind bellcow Saquon Barkley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cea-d93f-ad9d-7eef52860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers DT Derrick Harmon (knee) is active for Week 3 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cec-d1b3-a5dd-6dfd55bc0000</link>
      <description>The No. 21 overall pick will make his NFL debut today after missing the first two weeks of the season with a knee issue. Running back Kaleb Johnson is active despite making a catastrophic blunder on a kickoff last week that resulted in a Seahawks touchdown. He won’t return kicks but could still be in the backfield mix for a few snaps. Inactive for the Steelers are CB Joey Porter Jr., S DeShon Elliott, OLB Alex Highsmith, G Andrus Peat, and DT Esezi Otomewo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cec-d1b3-a5dd-6dfd55bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared CB DeCamerion Richardson, RB Raheem Mostert, DE Charles Snowden, OT Charles Grant, OG Caleb Rogers, and DT J.J. Pegues inactive for Week 3 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cee-dfde-a1bd-7eef55730000</link>
      <description>Nothing to see here. The biggest question mark throughout the week was Brock Bowers, who was removed from the team’s final injury report on Friday. The Raiders will look to get back on track in Week 3 against a banged-up Commanders team that allowed 124 receiving yards to Tucker Kraft in Week 2, which could signal a productive day for Bowers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cee-dfde-a1bd-7eef55730000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Charvarius Ward (concussion) is active for Week 3 against the Titans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cee-d93f-ad9d-7eef3e860000</link>
      <description>Ward missed Week 2 after going down in the opener but is thankfully ready to return after a one-game absence. He has a DB’s dream matchup in the Titans’ struggling passing attack. Inactive for the Colts are QB Riley Leonard, TE Will Mallory, LB Chad Muma, OT Luke Tenuta and EDGE JT Tuimoloau.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6cee-d93f-ad9d-7eef3e860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans declared RB Dameon Pierce, DE Darrell Taylor, QB Graham Mertz, WR Braxton Berrios, RB British Brooks, TE Brenden Bates, and T Blake Fisher inactive for Houston’s Week 3 game against the Jaguars.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eede17e0000</link>
      <description>Pierce has been officially passed by Woody Marks and is a drop in 12-team leagues. With Jaylin Smith hitting IR before the game, this entire list is full of healthy scratches. Christian Kirk will officially be active and make his Texans debut. Berrios, who also was healthy for the first time all season, apparently has not cracked the rotation at wideout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eede17e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers declared WR Xavier Legette (hamstring) inactive for Week 3 against the Falcons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eed874f0000</link>
      <description>Legette was limited in practice with a hamstring issue all week, but the Panthers make the choice to keep him inactive against the Falcons. The 24-year-old infamously has 15 targets for eight total yards so far this season, so this may also be a reset for him. For fantasy managers, Legette is droppable until we see any kind of production. David Moore will start in his place on the perimeter. Also inactive for the Panthers in Week 3 are WR Jimmy Horn Jr., C Nick Samac, TE James Mitchell, OLB Patrick Jones Jr., and DT Tershawn Wharton.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eed874f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams declared OLB Nick Hampton, QB Stetson Bennett, TE Terrance Ferguson, OT DJ Humphries and LG Steve Avila active for Week 3’s game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eedd50c0000</link>
      <description>Ferguson is inactive with the Rams getting Parkinson back from a shoulder injury. Braden Fiske is also active after being considered questionable with an oblique issue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-6ced-dfde-a1bd-7eedd50c0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
