<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 20:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons TE Kyle Pitts (knee) is not on Atlanta’s final Week 16 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3810-d087-addf-b9f0c77f0000</link>
      <description>Pitts was limited in Friday’s practice. It feels likely that he’s just being managed since the Falcons don’t have anything to play for at this point. With Drake London returning, Pitts profiles more as a low-end TE1 in Week 16 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3810-d087-addf-b9f0c77f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saints WR Mason Tipton (illness) is questionable to play in Week 16 against the Jets.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3810-dc7a-af9b-ffbfc0d20000</link>
      <description>Tipton missed the Saints’ last two practices. Players typically play through illnesses, but he appears to be truly questionable. Were he to sit out, it would leave the Saints with only WRs Chris Olave, Kevin Austin Jr. and Dante Pettis on the active roster. Olave should handle a significant target share, per usual.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3810-dc7a-af9b-ffbfc0d20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons EDGE James Pearce (foot) is questionable for Atlanta’s Week 16 game against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3813-dc7a-af9b-ffbf343f0000</link>
      <description>He was added to the report on Friday after practicing in full most of the week and was a “DNP.” DT Brandon Dorlus (illness/shoulder) joins Pearce on the questionable line, while CB Mike Hughes (ankle) has been ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3813-dc7a-af9b-ffbf343f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills CB Christian Benford (toe) is not on the final injury report for Week 16 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3814-da28-afbb-fc7d24ba0000</link>
      <description>Benford will miss just one game with the toe injury suffered during practice in Week 15. It is bad news for a talent-deficient Browns receiving corps. The Bills’ defense struggles to slow opposing run games, though, giving the Browns a clear lane to either produce an upset or lose with style.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3814-da28-afbb-fc7d24ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero believes Tua Tagovailoa has “in all likelihood has played his final down” for the Dolphins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3816-dc7a-af9b-ffbf31680000</link>
      <description>Pelissero says that part of the reason behind benching Tagovailoa was making sure he made it to 2026 healthy to “complicat[e] whatever long-shot trade scenarios you have.” The NFL Network’s reporter said that the “most likely scenario” for the Dolphins is making Tagovailoa a post-June 1 release, which would leave Tagovailoa with major cap hits in 2026 and 2027 ala Russell Wilson with the Broncos. Tagovailoa should find some sort of market as a rehab project — Justin Fields just did it without anywhere near the same amount of career success — but it’s hard to imagine him being fantasy-interesting in 2026 without an absolutely ideal landing spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3816-dc7a-af9b-ffbf31680000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants EDGE Kayvon Thibodeaux (shoulder) will not play in New York’s Week 16 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-381c-d087-addf-b9fca0bc0000</link>
      <description>It’s the fifth straight game missed by Thibodeaux. He did not practice all week, as usual. Someone should be letting Joe Schoen know about the existence of an injured reserve list any day now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-381c-d087-addf-b9fca0bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers WR Mike Evans (collarbone/rest) is not on Tampa Bay’s final Week 16 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-381f-dc7a-af9b-ffbf63430000</link>
      <description>The veteran receiver got in a full session on Friday and will be on the WR2 line against the Panthers in the first of two clashes between the NFC South co-leaders. Evans got a full day off on Thursday, but was limited on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-381f-dc7a-af9b-ffbf63430000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers TE Cade Otton (knee) is not on Tampa Bay’s final Week 16 injury report.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3821-dc7a-af9b-ffbf0dd10000</link>
      <description>With Mike Evans, Chris Godwin, and Jalen McMillan all back, Otton is drawing dead on any sort of upside play. He’s probably only a borderline TE2 against the Panthers in Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-3821-dc7a-af9b-ffbf0dd10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings placed LT Christian Darrisaw (knee) on injured reserve</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-381a-d35e-a1bf-7dda70920000</link>
      <description>Darrisaw tore his left ACL and MCL in October 2024. He retook the field for the first time in Week 3 this season, following the injury, but the knee continued to bother him. He allowed 18 quarterback pressures in 10 games this season. Hopefully, he can put the knee injury behind him with another offseason of rest and rehab.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-381a-d35e-a1bf-7dda70920000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
