<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 21:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Amon-Ra St. Brown (ankle) won’t practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03d-d90e-a9da-ff3f617e0000</link>
      <description>He added that if St. Brown can possibly play, he will. And since he also ruled out fellow wideout Kalif Raymond in this presser, it sounds like there is a non-zero chance that St. Brown plays against the Cowboys on Thursday. St. Brown would later speak to reporters and say that his status for Thursday is “up in the air.” We would still regard him as on the pessimistic side of questionable given the two missed practices, but the Lions look like they’ll take this up to inactives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03d-d90e-a9da-ff3f617e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Kalif Raymond (ankle) will not play in Detroit’s Week 14 game against the Cowboys.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03f-d6c4-abfb-f63f917e0000</link>
      <description>Since suffering this ankle injury in Week 12, Raymond has not yet practiced. Isaac TeSlaa took over as the third wideout last week and scored despite seeing just two targets. TeSlaa has already proven himself a big-play threat, but his target volume is so low he’ll be hard to trust in a FLEX spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e03f-d6c4-abfb-f63f917e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams coach Sean McVay said he’d like to get Tutu Atwell (hamstring/IR) active “if that fits for the collective relative to the 48, there’s a lot of factors for that.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e04b-db57-afda-f67b36170000</link>
      <description>Atwell surprisingly carried no injury status for Week 13, but was not activated from injured reserve. Xavier Smith, who returns kicks, was up and managed a 3/83 day in Atwell’s absence. It doesn’t sound like the Rams are all that fussed about the $10 million Atwell getting back. He’s droppable in all but the deepest fantasy leagues based on this update.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e04b-db57-afda-f67b36170000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants RB Tyrone Tracy told reporters he left New York’s Week 13 game against the Patriots with a hip contusion and a stinger.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e060-d90e-a9da-ff6f19e30000</link>
      <description>In other words, he should be fine coming off New York’s Week 14 bye. Cancel the Devin Singletary As Rest Of Season RB1-sized FAAB bids, though Singletary has claimed enough of the backfield to merit consideration off waivers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e060-d90e-a9da-ff6f19e30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS’ Matt Zenitz reports it’s “viewed as likely” that Omarion Hampton (ankle/IR) will be able to play against the Eagles on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e06f-d6c4-abfb-f66f2e0a0000</link>
      <description>We were beginning to suspect a rug pull between the Chargers signing Jaret Patterson to the 53-man roster and adding Royce Freeman to the practice squad over the last couple of days. Hampton also was spotted in a non-contact jersey for Friday’s practice. This story probably has some more unfolding to do, but the Chargers would likely be relying on Hampton in a big way on Monday night after what the Bears did to the Eagles on the ground on Black Friday. Especially with Justin Herbert (hand) potentially playing through injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e06f-d6c4-abfb-f66f2e0a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler believes the Commanders are a “team to potentially watch” for Brandon Aiyuk.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e07c-d82c-a79a-f3fca85c0000</link>
      <description>Fowler notes that Aiyuk played with Jayden Daniels at Arizona State and that Adam Peters, a former San Francisco assistant GM, is running the show in Washington. This is in a hypothetical scenario where Aiyuk becomes a free agent — we don’t necessarily know that we’re going to end up here — but the fact that the 49ers voided his guarantees makes it a plausible idea.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e07c-d82c-a79a-f3fca85c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions S Kerby Joseph (knee) did not practice on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0cc-d82c-a79a-f3dc6c920000</link>
      <description>It’s a downgrade after a limited Monday session. FOX’s Jordan Schultz reports that Joseph “will likely seek treatment for the knee in the offseason, but he plans to be on the field in the coming weeks.” That doesn’t necessarily sound like a report about a player who will play on Thursday. The injury is “not considered career-altering” per multiple sources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0cc-d82c-a79a-f3dc6c920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers waived CB Darius Slay.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0ce-d6c4-abfb-f6cfc29c0000</link>
      <description>In a corresponding move, the Steelers signed Asante Samuel Jr. to the active roster. ESPN’s Adam Schefter framed this as the two “mutually agree[ing] to part ways.” The obvious re-landing spot for Slay is in Philadelphia, though he’s free to consider other options now. The 34-year-old had a 58.6 PFF coverage grade for the Steelers, his lowest since his final season in Detroit during the 2019 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0ce-d6c4-abfb-f6cfc29c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts waived K Michael Badgley.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0d2-db57-afda-f6f26f070000</link>
      <description>The Money Badger missed a huge extra point against the Texans in Week 13 and had missed three of his 21 extra points in total. It’ll be a different kicker for the Colts after today’s tryouts resolve, and whoever they pick will find themselves in a favorable Week 14 situation against the Jaguars. Blake Grupe was one name publicly identified from the tryouts earlier today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0d2-db57-afda-f6f26f070000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys WR George Pickens (calf/knee) practiced in full on Tuesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0d6-d90e-a9da-ffdfe2430000</link>
      <description>As expected. Pickens should be good to go on Thursday after a limited session on Monday. He’ll be a WR1 against the Lions on Thursday night. He played through this listing during Thanksgiving’s game against the Chiefs and put up an 88-yard day on 13 targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-e0d6-d90e-a9da-ffdfe2430000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
