<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 20:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jaguars coach Liam Coen said the coaching staff is still evaluating Travis Hunter’s usage in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0667-de13-afdd-46ef5d230000</link>
      <description>The question asked was if Hunter would start on both sides of the ball. Coen emphasized that they’re working through it and he “missed a lot of time” with his upper body injury. This isn’t necessarily a fantasy football fire alarm, but it does sound like Hunter’s preseason injury should have us with slightly lowered expectations for Week 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0667-de13-afdd-46ef5d230000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said S C.J. Gardner-Johnson (knee) is expected to play in Week 1 against the Rams.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-066c-db7b-a5dd-a66c0fe20000</link>
      <description>Gardner-Johnson went down in early August with a knee injury that was expected to threaten his season, but Gardner-Johnson has been able to rehab it successfully and it thankfully was not as bad as it initially looked. Gardner-Johnson should have a decent role in Houston this year, though Jalen Pitre is probably the IDP Texans back-seven player you want to roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-066c-db7b-a5dd-a66c0fe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jauan Jennings (calf) was seen practicing on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-063d-d332-a1fd-963ff21e0000</link>
      <description>The Niners don’t need to release an official practice report until Wednesday, but a Monday return in any capacity is good news for Jennings, who has been dealing with a calf injury since late July. General manager John Lynch said last week that the team is “hopeful” Jennings could return for Week 1 against the Seahawks, but didn’t sound overly optimistic. Jennings’ status will be one to monitor on Wednesday for when the first practice report is released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-063d-d332-a1fd-963ff21e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports it is still “uncertain” if Packers EDGE Micah Parsons (back) will play in Week 1.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-067e-d332-a1fd-967e4a6b0000</link>
      <description>Schefter said that Parsons may need an epidural prior to the game and that the star rusher has been dealing with an “L4/L5 facet joint sprain” in his back. We don’t really know how much stock to put into this given Parsons said he’s feeling great on Friday — it almost reads like a Cowboys source dumping what they know to make the trade look better because of the details on what the Cowboys wanted Parsons to do. It does sound like perhaps the idea that Parsons’ back injury was pure cover-up is off-base. Parsons practiced in what appeared to be a limited basis today per ESPN’s Rob Demovsky.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-067e-d332-a1fd-967e4a6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Nick Wagoner believes 49ers WR Jordan Watkins (ankle) “doesn’t seem too far off.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0695-db7b-a5dd-a695f9050000</link>
      <description>But, he adds, the team might place Watkins on IR to make room for Kendrick Bourne if Bourne ends up signing with the 49ers. It sounds like Watkins has missed his chance to make a fantasy impact piece early in the season either way, but he’s still worth monitoring in dynasty leagues after making a lot of noise early in training camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0695-db7b-a5dd-a695f9050000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darnell Mooney (shoulder) still considered day-to-day.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0691-d332-a1fd-96b76de20000</link>
      <description>Head coach Raheem Morris said Mooney participated in Monday’s jog through, but still said the veteran receiver will remain day-to-day ahead of the first official practice on Wednesday. Mooney has been dealing with a shoulder injury since July and did log a practice late last week. We’ll see where things stand on Wednesday when the first practice report is released, but it sounds like he’s trending in the right direction ahead of Week 1’s game against the Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-0691-d332-a1fd-96b76de20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Najee Harris (eye) is cleared for contact and there’s a chance he plays in Week 1 against the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06a3-dbe3-a9bb-36f3e4f80000</link>
      <description>Things have been trending in a positive direction for Harris over the last two weeks, but Harbaugh has yet to out-and-out say that he will play in Week 1. Greg Roman said a few weeks ago that Omarion Hampton will split snaps with someone in Week 1 — Harris if he plays, or (likely) Hassan Haskins if Harris sits. We’ll be monitoring Harris’ practice status all week but being cleared for contact is a good sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06a3-dbe3-a9bb-36f3e4f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers coach Jim Harbaugh said Quentin Johnston has cleared concussion protocol.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06b3-db7b-a5dd-a6b704b20000</link>
      <description>Johnston’s role in the offense remains murky after the Keenan Allen addition. We suspect that Johnston will be battling the inconsistent Tre’ Harris for snaps and targets outside, but either way this is probably only news for DFS contests at the moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06b3-db7b-a5dd-a6b704b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaire Alexander (knee) did not practice Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06be-db7b-a5dd-a6be15490000</link>
      <description>We’re in midseason form. Alexander has not practice since August 9th per The Athletic’s Jeff Zrebiec. There’s still plenty of time for him to get cleared this week, but nobody should be surprised if Alexander misses Week 1 after this long of a layoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06be-db7b-a5dd-a6be15490000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isaiah Likely (foot) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ac-de13-afdd-46ef3a310000</link>
      <description>Likely underwent foot surgery on August 1 and hasn’t been on the field since. The fourth-year tight end avoided opening the season on injured reserve, suggesting he will be able to return before Week 4, but he’s far from a lock to play in Week 1 against the Bills. The Ravens don’t have to release their first official practice report until Wednesday, which should give us a better sense of Likely’s availability for Week 1. Even if he is active, he’ll be hard to rely on in fantasy with Mark Andrews still operating as the team’s top tight end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-06ac-de13-afdd-46ef3a310000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
