<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 19:01:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots coach Mike Vrabel said CB Christian Gonzalez (hamstring) is expected to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58a4-dfde-a1bd-5ead896f0000</link>
      <description>Gonzalez has yet to practice or play this season while dealing with a lingering hamstring issue. We would expect his workload in Wednesday’s practice to be rather light, but it’s a step in the right direction for the young corner. The Patriots just gave up 27 points to a Dolphins offense that looked lifeless in their previous appearance. Getting Gonzalez back won’t turn things around overnight, but it will certainly stem the bleeding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58a4-dfde-a1bd-5ead896f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals coach Zac Taylor declined to rule out Joe Burrow (toe) for the year on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ab-d1b3-a5dd-59fbe1b20000</link>
      <description>Taylor did not have a timeline for Burrow’s impending surgery, though it should happen soon. The fact that a 2025 return is still on the table is notable, though it does not mean Burrow will actually play again this season. Burrow is expected to be sidelined for a minimum of three months, meaning the earliest he could get back on the field would be the middle of December. Burrow stands almost no chance of playing at the end of the year if the Bengals aren’t in the playoff hunt late in the season. Jake Browning is penciled in as the starter for now. Browning went 4-3 as the team’s starter in 2023 and should be able to get the ball into the hands of Ja’Marr Chase and Tee Higgins often enough to keep both from bottoming out as fantasy assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ab-d1b3-a5dd-59fbe1b20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed EDGE Preston Smith, formerly of the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58b3-d6a5-adff-fef7d6a00000</link>
      <description>Smith got his start in the pros as a second-round pick with the Commanders in 2015. He then spent six years in Green Bay, though the Packers traded him to Pittsburgh in his final year with the team. Smith totaled two sacks in eight games as a rotational EDGE for the Steelers. He will give the Commanders some extra depth at the position after they lost Deatrich Wise to a season-ending leg injury last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58b3-d6a5-adff-fef7d6a00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said Xavier Worthy (shoulder) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58b9-d1b3-a5dd-59f983600000</link>
      <description>Worthy got in a pair of limited sessions last week after being listed as a DNP on Wednesday. Getting on the field for the first practice of the week this time around is a step in the right direction and suggests Worthy could be ready to return to action on Sunday. He is reportedly dealing with a fully torn labrum after taking a brutal hit from Travis Kelce in Week 1. Getting Worthy back after just one game would be a massive win for a Chiefs team still in search of its first win of 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58b9-d1b3-a5dd-59f983600000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs coach Andy Reid said WR Jalen Royals (knee) will practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58c1-d1b3-a5dd-59f1133e0000</link>
      <description>It will be Royals’ first practice of the season after missing the opening two weeks while dealing with knee tendinitis. Reid was cagey when talkign about Royals, saying, “He’s coming pretty good, we’ll see how he does here. He’s been out for a while.” Even if he is healthy for Week 3, it wouldn’t be surprising for the rookie to get another week off to ensure he doesn’t suffer any setbacks. For now, Royals is only on the radar in dynasty formats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58c1-d1b3-a5dd-59f1133e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers signed OL Brandon Parker, formerly of the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58db-d93f-ad9d-5adfad380000</link>
      <description>The 49ers correspondingly placed OG Ben Bartch on injured reserve with an ankle injury and promoted TE Brayden Willis from the practice squad. Parker was a liability as a run blocker and pass protector but the former 2018 third-round pick is at least an experienced veteran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58db-d93f-ad9d-5adfad380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts CB Charvarius Ward (concussion) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58c3-d93f-ad9d-5ac767120000</link>
      <description>Ward did not practice last week because of his concussion and was ruled out on Friday. A return on Wednesday puts him in line to suit up for Week 3, but the veteran corner will still need to clear the league’s concussion protocol before being given the green light. Fellow Indy defender Laiatu Latu was also spotted at practice. The second-year EDGE missed Week 2 with a hamstring injury. Getting both players back for Week 3 would be a big win for a Colts defense that just gave up 28 points to the Broncos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58c3-d93f-ad9d-5ac767120000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) is questionable for Week 3 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58e6-d6a5-adff-fee740190000</link>
      <description>Waddle was a surprise addition to Tuesday’s injury report after not appearing on the first report of the week. He was listed as limited and got in another partial session today before being listed as questionable. He should be able to play through the shoulder ailment, but fantasy managers will want to keep tabs on this situation when the Dolphins release their inactives before kickoff. Malik Washington would slide into the No. 2 role if Waddle is unable to suit up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58e6-d6a5-adff-fee740190000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Waller (hip) will not play in Week 3 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ea-dfde-a1bd-5eef0f650000</link>
      <description>Waller was limited in all three practices this week, suggesting he is making progress with the hip issue. He has yet to play in 2025 after coming out of retirement during the summer to backfill Jonnu Smith’s role. Even if he does return next week, fantasy managers can ignore the age-33 tight end for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ea-dfde-a1bd-5eef0f650000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins RB Jaylen Wright (knee) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 3 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ec-d93f-ad9d-5aef1aee0000</link>
      <description>Wright missed the first two games of the year with a knee issue he suffered just before the start of the season. He was limited in the first two practices of the week but managed a full session today. Ollie Gordon failed to carve out a meaningful role in Miami while Wright was sidelined. Neither back has much fantasy value going forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-58ec-d93f-ad9d-5aef1aee0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
