<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 03:13:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers RG Mekhi Becton (concussion) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82ef-dca3-a9fb-bfff7a000000</link>
      <description>The Chargers’ center-to-right tackle trio exited Week 3 in rough shape. The group’s overall health is improving, though. C Bradley Bozeman (back) returned to practice in a limited capacity on Thursday and RT Trey Pipkins III (knee) was upgraded to full participation. Becton evidently has not made progress in the NFL’s concussion protocol. He may miss the Chargers’ Week 4 game against the Giants, but the other two should be good to go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-82ef-dca3-a9fb-bfff7a000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks RB Zach Charbonnet (foot) is active for Week 4 against the Cardinals.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-830f-dca3-a9fb-bf9fff5a0000</link>
      <description>Aside from Charbonnet, Seahawks CB Devon Witherspoon (knee) and S Julian Love (hamstring) are also returning to action this evening. Charbonnet can be expected to handle 10-plus touches against the division rival. The Seahawks declared S Nick Emmanwori, LB Jared Ivey, TE Nick Kallerup, LB Connor O’Toole, OT Josh Jones, OL Mason Richman and WR Cody White inactive for Week 4 against the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-830f-dca3-a9fb-bf9fff5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals LT Paris Johnson (knee) is active for Week 4 against the Seahawks.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8306-deb6-a7fd-d3dfe44d0000</link>
      <description>Kyler Murray will have his top-tier left tackle protecting his blindside against the Seahawks’ pass rush this evening. The Cardinals declared CB Will Johnson, WR Zay Jones, LB Xavier Thomas, OL Will Hernandez, OL Demontrey Jacobs and TE Travis Vokelek inactive for Week 4 against the Seahawks. The Cardinals’ secondary is in rough shape. They lost CB Starling Thomas V to a torn ACL this summer and placed CB Garrett Williams on injured reserve last week with a knee injury of his own. Johnson has played very well when available. Hopefully, his groin injury heals up in time for Week 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8306-deb6-a7fd-d3dfe44d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams WR Davante Adams (hamstring) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8327-dca3-a9fb-bfbf94280000</link>
      <description>Adams has now missed the first two practices of Week 4, putting him on the wrong side of questionable. A veteran like Adams does not need to practice in order to play, but two missed practices are concerning nonetheless. If active against the Colts in Week 4, he’s a low-end WR2. His Friday status will be critical though.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8327-dca3-a9fb-bfbf94280000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rams TE Tyler Higbee (hip) was added to the injury report on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-832a-d95b-addb-eb6ecf4d0000</link>
      <description>The 32-year-old tight end has five targets in three games, so his potential absence is hardly a needle-mover. Unfortunately, the Rams’ No. 2 WR Davante Adams has missed two practices with a hamstring injury, so QB Matthew Stafford could be working with a short-staffed receiving corps in Week 4 against the Colts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-832a-d95b-addb-eb6ecf4d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Jauan Jennings (ankle/shoulder) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8320-dca3-a9fb-bfb959ff0000</link>
      <description>Wednesday beat reports indicated Jennings’ shoulder injury may be behind him but it was all for naught. The 49ers’ veteran wide receiver is on the injury report with both ankle and shoulder ailments. If he can return to practice on Friday, he can be expected to play. If active, Jennings is worthy of a start in the FLEX spot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8320-dca3-a9fb-bfb959ff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Brock Purdy (toe/left shoulder) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8331-dca3-a9fb-bfb927dc0000</link>
      <description>Purdy appears to be on track to play in Week 4 against the Jaguars, as long as he remains setback-free. We expect Purdy’s scrambling ability may be a bit compromised in his return, so he is best viewed as a QB2. Fortunately, the 49ers have the NFL’s checkdown option in Christian McCaffrey, so Purdy should be able to get rid of the ball quickly when pressured. 49ers head coach Kyle Shanahansaidhe thinks Purdy’s toe injury “is feeling better each day and if that continues he should be good on Sunday.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-8331-dca3-a9fb-bfb927dc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers QB Mac Jones (knee) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-833a-d6e9-af9d-8bba030d0000</link>
      <description>Jones continues through practice after re-injuring the PCL sprain he suffered during training camp, which is a great sign for his Week 4 availability. Brock Purdy (toe/left shoulder) is on track to play, so Jones is unlikely to be called upon. His expected availability helps insulate the 49ers’ pass catchers in fantasy, though, in the event that Purdy suffers a re-injury of some sort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-833a-d6e9-af9d-8bba030d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Mike Garafolo reports that Terry McLaurin (quad) does not need to undergo surgery “as of right now.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-833f-deb6-a7fd-d3ffad460000</link>
      <description>Garafolo introduced the segment by lightheartedly referring to McLaurin’s “quad, hip, groin” injury, which affirms concerns that this injury is not necessarily limited to one singular muscle group. If McLaurin were to undergo surgery, it would potentially require “six-to-eight” weeks of recovery. McLaurin is currently not expected to play in Week 4 against the Falcons, but we will know for sure on Friday. Deebo Samuel will operate as the Commanders’ No. 1 wide receiver in McLaurin’s stead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-833f-deb6-a7fd-d3ffad460000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks EDGE DeMarcus Lawrence was forced from Seattle’s Week 4 game against the Cardinals with a quad injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-83ef-d95b-addb-ebef3cb10000</link>
      <description>Initially announced with a thigh injury, Lawrence told the Amazon broadcast it was actually his quad. It’s almost certainly some sort of deep bruise. Lawrence was announced as doubtful early on then officially ruled out at halftime. The only good news is he has 10 days to get healthy for Week 5 against the Bucs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-83ef-d95b-addb-ebef3cb10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
