<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 18:01:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Colts CB Kenny Moore will miss a few weeks with a calf injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7228-d93f-ad9d-7aefe96a0000</link>
      <description>Moore exited Week 3’s game against the Titans and didn’t return to the field. The Colts went out and signed veteran slot corner Mike Hilton early Monday morning, which served as the initial indicator that Moore, whose injury is not believed to be too serious, was set to miss some time. We’ll hopefully get a more exact timeline on Moore’s absence when head coach Shane Steichen speaks to the media, but it sounds like he is looking at a multi-week absence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7228-d93f-ad9d-7aefe96a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jordan Raanan reports Tyrone Tracy will miss time after suffering a dislocated shoulder in Week 3’s loss to the Chiefs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7243-dfde-a1bd-7ecf5ab10000</link>
      <description>It felt like things were trending in this direction after Tracy took a hard hit in the first quarter and immediately exited the game. Tracy didn’t return to the game and is now slated to miss a few weeks while recovering from the injury. Rookie Cam Skattebo, who rushed 10 times for 60 yards and a touchdown in Week 3’s loss to the Chiefs, is expected to take on a significant workload with Tracy now sidelined, and will profile as a strong RB2 with potential RB1 upside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7243-dfde-a1bd-7ecf5ab10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buccaneers HC Todd Bowles reports tests revealed a “low-grade” hamstring injury for Mike Evans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7255-dfde-a1bd-7edd89840000</link>
      <description>Evans is still likely to miss some time, but the initial diagnosis is mostly positive. Evans suffered the injury in the fourth quarter of Sunday’s win over the Jets and did not return to the field. Depending on his expected recovery time, it’s possible Evans avoids injured reserve if the team thinks he can return inside of the four-game minimum he would need to miss on IR. It seems unlikely Evans plays in Week 4, but we’ll see what his practice status is when the first injury report drops on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7255-dfde-a1bd-7edd89840000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns LT Dawand Jones (knee) will be placed on season-ending injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7261-dfde-a1bd-7eed748e0000</link>
      <description>KT Leveston is the next man up at tackle. Jones has hit season-ending IR in three consecutive years since being drafted in the fourth round. He’ll enter the final year of his rookie deal as someone the Browns will likely want to do better than, though the disastrous Deshaun Watson contract may keep them from doing so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7261-dfde-a1bd-7eed748e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Addison is eligible to return from suspension in Week 4 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7261-d93f-ad9d-7ae7371d0000</link>
      <description>Addison’s three-game suspension is up once the league’s calendar year flips to Week 4. He’s on track to return to the team just in time to join them for a trip to Ireland to face the Steelers, which precedes a Week 5 trip to London to face the Browns. Addison should immediately slot in as the Vikings’ No. 2 receiver opposite Justin Jefferson and will be on the WR3 radar against the Steelers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7261-d93f-ad9d-7ae7371d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans coach DeMeco Ryans said Derek Stingley (oblique) is “day to day.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7264-d6a5-adff-f6e550d00000</link>
      <description>However, he also said the evaluation process is still ongoing. Stingley left Week 3’s game against the Jaguars in the first half and did not return. Tremon Smith was pressed into extra action outside and would seem to be a possible starter if Stingley cannot play in Week 4 against the Titans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7264-d6a5-adff-f6e550d00000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Bears TE Colston Loveland (hip) “is expected to have a chance” to play in Week 4 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-726f-d6a5-adff-f6ef3cbe0000</link>
      <description>According to Schefter, Loveland’s injury “is not believed to be serious.” The rookie tight end caught one pass for 31 yards in Week 3’s win over the Cowboys before exiting Sunday’s contest, and has caught three passes for 31 yards on six targets. Loveland can’t be trusted by fantasy managers in Week 4 even if he is active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-726f-d6a5-adff-f6ef3cbe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on 105.3 the Fan, Cowboys executive vice president Stephen Jones declined to commit to CeeDee Lamb (ankle) playing in Week 4 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-727a-d1b3-a5dd-737b59470000</link>
      <description>Lamb is dealing with a high-ankle sprain. He expressed optimism after Sunday’s loss to the Bears, saying he “absolutely” feels like he can play in Week 4 against the Packers, but Jones is opting to take a more measured approach. Jones said the Cowboys will wait and see how the week goes for Lamb before deciding whether or not he’ll have a chance to suit up on Sunday night. This will be something to watch throughout the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-727a-d1b3-a5dd-737b59470000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders signed S Darnell Savage.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7286-dfde-a1bd-7e8fff940000</link>
      <description>He’ll take Will Harris’ place in the rotation. Savage had an underwhelming couple of years in Jacksonville but should be a potential starter for the Commanders. The 28-year-old had one tackle in two games with the Jaguars before being released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7286-dfde-a1bd-7e8fff940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans HC Brian Callahan said “everything is under evaluation and consideration” when asked if he could give up offensive play-calling.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7284-d93f-ad9d-7ac7e37a0000</link>
      <description>The 0-3 Titans are open to anything to secure that much-needed first win of the season. Currently ranking 31st in both EPA per play and offensive success rate (36.8 percent), Callahan’s offense is in need of a spark, which could come from a change in play-calling. The former OC, who was once praised for the elite offenses he oversaw during his time in Cincinnati, has struggled to live up to the hype in his brief tenure as head coach of the Titans. The Titans are riding a nine-game losing streak that dates back to last season and were a bottom-tier offense in 2024, which ultimately led them to the No. 1 overall pick and QB Cam Ward this offseason. Offensive coordinator Nick Holz, who last served as OC in 2022 while at UNLV, would presumably take over at play-calling if a change were to be made. He joined Callahan’s staff during the 2024 offseason and has never held a play-calling role in the NFL.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-7284-d93f-ad9d-7ac7e37a0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
