<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders opened the 21-day practice window for QB Aidan O’Connell (wrist).</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30ad-de12-a19e-36ad903b0000</link>
      <description>O’Connell has been sidelined for nearly two months with a wrist injury. He could be back as the Raiders’ backup QB for Week 9 against the Jaguars, or the team could wait until Week 10 or 11 to make him active. O’Connell could end up seeing playing time in 2025 unless Geno Smith can turn it around in the next few weeks. Smith has been among the least efficient quarterbacks in football this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30ad-de12-a19e-36ad903b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ray Davis (illness) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30b5-d48c-ad9f-fcfdc01d0000</link>
      <description>Davis still has a good chance to suit up in Week 9 against the Chiefs if he can get in a limited practice on Thursday and Friday. Davis is purely a contingency fantasy option behind James Cook for now. In Week 8, Davis had nine rushes for 16 yards in garbage time against the Panthers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30b5-d48c-ad9f-fcfdc01d0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills activated WR Gabe Davis to the team’s practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30c1-d48c-ad9f-fccd1d540000</link>
      <description>Davis will practice with the Bills for the first time this season after signing with the team in early September. He’s coming off a terrible 2024 season in Jacksonville, where he managed 20 catches for 239 yards and two touchdowns over ten games before injuring his knee. Davis could be active for Week 9 against the Chiefs, who in the 2023 postseason allowed 201 yards and four touchdowns to Davis as the Bills fell in overtime to KC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30c1-d48c-ad9f-fccd1d540000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports there’s “no chance” Myles Garett will be traded ahead of the league’s trade deadline.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30e3-de12-a19e-36e335150000</link>
      <description>“People have a better chance of winning the lottery,” a source told Schefter. It appears Garrett, who has ten sacks through eight games this season, will remain with the Browns for at least another lost season. Garrett, 29, would surely draw a king’s ransom from a contending team looking to shore up their defense ahead of the postseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30e3-de12-a19e-36e335150000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calvin Ridley (hamstring) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30ed-d321-a5bf-b2ff6e620000</link>
      <description>Ridley has missed two games with the hamstring issue and now appears likely to sit for a third straight week. Van Jefferson, Elic Ayomanor, and Chimere Dike all saw exactly eight targets last week. Dike was the only one who cashed in with a strong fantasy day, reeling in seven of his looks for 93 yards. He also logged one rush attempt. Dike went for 70 yards and scored two weeks ago. Though there isn’t much fantasy value to be had in Tennessee, Dike is looking like a weekly WR4 with Ridley sideliend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30ed-d321-a5bf-b2ff6e620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans DT Jeffery Simmons (hamstring) did not practice Wednedsay.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30f0-d48c-ad9f-fcfdf2f30000</link>
      <description>Simmons missed Week 8’s game with the same hamstring issue. He now looks likely to miss a second week because of it. Fellow pass-rusher Arden Key also remains out of practice. He is dealing with a quad issue. The Titans didn’t have a great defense before these injuries. Losing Simmons and Key will make them an easier matchup for the Chargers on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30f0-d48c-ad9f-fcfdf2f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isiah Pacheco (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30f6-d321-a5bf-b2f73fc10000</link>
      <description>Pacheco suffered an MCL sprain in the Chiefs’ Week 8 win over the Commanders. It’s not believed to be a long-term issue, but NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero called him “week to week.” That typically means the player in question will miss at least one game. Kareem Hunt is the next man up for Kansas City. Hunt was already operating as the team’s short-yardage back this year and will now take on some of Pacheco’s work between the 20s. Rookie running back Brashard Smith should also be more involved, albeit as a change-of-pace option. Both backs are worth a look as FLEX plays in a potential shootout with the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30f6-d321-a5bf-b2f73fc10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giants TE Daniel Bellinger (neck) will not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30fa-d48c-ad9f-fcffcdc40000</link>
      <description>Bellinger was limited in practice throughout last week because of the neck issue. He was eventually cleared to play but ultimately left Week 8’s game against the Eagles after the injury resurfaced. He will likely miss some time while recovering. His absence could mean a few extra routes for Theo Johnson, though Bellinger was largely taking the field alongside Johnson for 12-personnel sets. Expect more three-wide looks if Bellinger can’t suit up this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-30fa-d48c-ad9f-fcffcdc40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots signed RB D’Ernest Johnson off the Cardinals’ practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3101-d4ed-a9de-778f9fa90000</link>
      <description>Johnson will go from Arizona’s practice squad directly to their 53-man roster. Johnson hasn’t seen any action in 2025 but should be active for New England once he gets up to speed on the playbook. His signing could send things from bad to worse for rookie TreVeyon Henderson, who has played sparingly this year and coughed up a fumble late in New England’s Week 8 win over the Browns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3101-d4ed-a9de-778f9fa90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Flacco (shoulder) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3118-d4ed-a9de-779ef62b0000</link>
      <description>Flacco’s status is up in the air because of an AC joint sprain he suffered versus the Jets. He briefly went into the locker room late in the Bengals’ Week 8 loss but did manage to return without missing a snap. His absence would put Jake Browning back under center. Browning struggled mightily as the starter earlier this year, forcing the Bengals to trade for Flacco. His return to the lineup would be a massive downgrade for all Cincy pass-catchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-3118-d4ed-a9de-779ef62b0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
