<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>David Njoku (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2db0-d005-a9bf-fdb477d70000</link>
      <description>Njoku missed Week 15 with the knee issue. He didn’t practice once last week and now looks unlikely to suit up for Week 15. Harold Fannin led the Browns with seven catches on Sunday. He turned that into 48 yards. Fannin is in line for another TE1 ranking this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2db0-d005-a9bf-fdb477d70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets ruled out TE Mason Taylor (neck) for Week 16 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2db9-d77b-adfb-efbb5d9b0000</link>
      <description>Taylor will miss his second consecutive game with the neck injury. The news comes shortly after the front office signed 25-year-old TE Jeremy Ruckert to a two-year, $10 million extension, which is unfortunate. The Jets face the Patriots in Week 17. Hopefully, Taylor can return in time to face them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2db9-d77b-adfb-efbb5d9b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Sampson (calf) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dba-d005-a9bf-fdbeea6b0000</link>
      <description>Sampson missed Week 15 with the calf issue. Trayveon Williams played the role of RB2 versus Chicago. He touched the ball three times and generated seven yards. Sampson’s likely absence for Week 16 will simply mean more receiving opportunities for Quinshon Judkins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dba-d005-a9bf-fdbeea6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns RG Wyatt Teller (calf) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dbe-d1bc-a3fb-adbe716c0000</link>
      <description>Right tackle Jack Conklin remains out of practice with a concussion and left guard Joel Bitonion remains out with a back issue. Teller’s return will help a struggling Browns offense, but it isn’t going to change their fortunes overnight. Expect this to be a low-wattage offense for the remainder of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dbe-d1bc-a3fb-adbe716c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CeeDee Lamb (illness) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dc1-d77b-adfb-efc3ba010000</link>
      <description>This is probably nothing, but it’s worth having on the radar if you are continuing on Lamb for fantasy production. Lamb should be able to play through the issue as long as he practices in some capacity this week. Coming off a 111-yard outing versus the Vikings, Lamb will be locked in for a WR1 ranking as long as he gets cleared to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dc1-d77b-adfb-efc3ba010000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Brady Cook will start in Week 16 against the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dbe-d8cf-affb-bdbea2a70000</link>
      <description>Cook finished as the overall QB26 last week against the Jaguars. Although this week’s opponent fields a more fantasy-friendly defense, Cook remains a low-end QB2 at best. Both QB Tyrod Taylor (groin) and QB Justin Fields (knee) are returning from injury. Jets head coach Aaron Glenn said that the healthier player will be given the No. 2 quarterback role on game day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dbe-d8cf-affb-bdbea2a70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saquon Barkley (stinger) returned to practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dc6-d005-a9bf-fdf6153c0000</link>
      <description>Barkley missed Tuesday’s session because of the issue, raising some concern that he could miss Week 16 versus the Commanders. Even a limited practice today eases those worries for Eagles fans and fantasy managers alike. Barring a setback, Barkley is on track for an RB1 performance in the fantasy football semi-finals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dc6-d005-a9bf-fdf6153c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers WR Tetairoa McMillan (foot/ankle) did not practice on Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dcd-d8cf-affb-bdef2afc0000</link>
      <description>This is unfortunate. The Panthers’ No. 1 wide receiver finished as the half-PPR WR23 and WR72 over the team’s last two games, while slot WR Jalen Coker notched WR14 and WR19 finishes. Panthers head coach Dave Canales said McMillan got “rolled up on” during a run play against the Saints last week. The plan is to hold McMillan out today and “try to get him back for tomorrow.” The Panthers (7-7) face the Buccaneers (7-7) on Sunday. The winner takes control of the NFC South.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dcd-d8cf-affb-bdef2afc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dalton Kincaid (knee) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dd4-d8cf-affb-bdfe8d100000</link>
      <description>Kincaid has been playing through the knee issue for a few weeks and didn’t miss any practice time ahead of Week 15. A DNP today could be a sign that he suffered a setback on Sunday. The hope, however, is that it’s simply a maintenance day for Kincaid. Dawson Knox would be the next man up if Kincaid sits for Week 16.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dd4-d8cf-affb-bdfe8d100000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles RT Lane Johnson (foot) did not practice Wednesday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dda-d77b-adfb-efdba3050000</link>
      <description>Left guard Landon Dickerson (calf) was also held out of practices. That’s two DNPs to open the week for the pair of starting linemen. Both players can be considered on the wrong side of questionable for Week 16. With a winnable game versus Washington on tap, it could make sense for the Eagles to give their injured linemen the week off ahead of a Week 17 date with the Bills.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-2dda-d77b-adfb-efdba3050000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
