<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:01:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (groin) did not participate in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a2e-d93f-ad9d-5aef509c0000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals’ rookie second-round pick missed Wednesday’s practice session with a groin issue. Through two games, the 22-year-old has a 75.0 PFF grade, good for No. 18 among cornerbacks. If he cannot go on Sunday, Elijah Jones is in line for the start.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a2e-d93f-ad9d-5aef509c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Garrett Williams (knee) will be placed on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a36-d93f-ad9d-5af7746c0000</link>
      <description>Williams suffered the knee injury in Week 2 against the Panthers and will be sidelined for the near future. Head coach Jonathan Gannon said Williams will be placed on injured reserve with a chance to return. Meanwhile, CB Max Melton (knee) was a limited practice participant. Losing Williams and potentially Will Johnson (groin) for Week 3 is a tough blow to the secondary, but Melton at least has a shot to play against an equally banged-up 49ers receiving group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a36-d93f-ad9d-5af7746c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>According to Broncos beat reporter Zac Stevens, head coach Sean Payton said RB RJ Harvey is “an important piece of what we’re doing.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a3b-dfde-a1bd-5ebf444b0000</link>
      <description>Harvey was a second round pick by the Broncos this year, but has seen just 11 carries and three targets through the first two games of the season. Veteran J.K. Dobbins has been the lead back, but Payton was insistent that Harvey is a key piece of the offense when speaking to the press Wednesday. We have yet to see Harvey utilized like an “important piece”, but rookies often require patience. Payton can be frustrating for fantasy managers with his skill player rotations, but more usage is on the horizon for Harvey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a3b-dfde-a1bd-5ebf444b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fox Sports’ Greg Auman reports Buccaneers OG Cody Mauch will require knee surgery that is expected to end his season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a5f-d93f-ad9d-5adfc3ae0000</link>
      <description>Mauch, the Bucs’ starting right guard, injured his knee in the Week 2 victory over the Texans. Auman now reports the knee will require surgery, which is expected to sideline the 26-year-old for the remainder of the 2025 season. It is another brutal blow to the Bucs’ offensive line with Tristan Wirfs and Luke Goedeke also sidelined. Mauch will aim to come back for 2026 while the Bucs signed Dan Feeney off the Bills’ practice squad for depth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5a5f-d93f-ad9d-5adfc3ae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Dolphins “hope” Jaylen Waddle (shoulder) is able to play in Week 2 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ce3-d1b3-a5dd-5df383890000</link>
      <description>Waddle will test out his shoulder in warmups before being clear for action. He briefly left the Dolphins’ Week 2 loss to the Patriots to be checked out by trainers but returned to the game and wasn’t listed on Monday’s injury report. He was then added as a limited participant on Tuesday and Wednesday. It sounds like the Dolphins are just being cautious with a receiver known for laboring through injuries, but fantasy managers will want to check Miami’s inactives 90 minutes before kickoff to be sure. If Waddle can’t suit up, second-year wideout Malik Washington would be in line for No. 2 receiver duties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5ce3-d1b3-a5dd-5df383890000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jets QB Tyrod Taylor will start in Week 3 against the Bucs.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5cea-d1b3-a5dd-5dfb61a80000</link>
      <description>First-year head coach Aaron Glenn didn’t string Jets fans or the Bucs along with the idea that Justin Fields might play this week. He ruled out the young quarterback on Wednesday, giving him a week to recover from the concussion he suffered on Sunday versus Buffalo. That puts Taylor in line to make his first start as a Jet after backing up Aaron Rodgers in 2023. Taylor made five starts with the Giants in 2023. He went 2-3 with five touchdowns and three interceptions. Taylor is as conservative as you would expect a 36-year-old journeyman to be, but that should keep the fantasy stocks of Breece Hall and Garrett Wilson afloat. Taylor himself is nothing more than a 2QB dart-throw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5cea-d1b3-a5dd-5dfb61a80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports a Week 4 return for Chris Godwin (ankle) “feels like a real possibility.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d5d-d6a5-adff-ffddfb1a0000</link>
      <description>Bucs GM Jason Licht said at the end of training camp that Godwin was likely to play in Week 5 or later, so a Week 4 return would be a great outcome for the veteran wideout. We remain skeptical that he will actually be ready by next week, but Fowler’s reporting at least indicates that things are going smoothly in Godwin’s rehab. Emeka Egbuka and Mike Evans will hold things down until Godwin returns. If he looks anything like he did in 2024, Godwin will be a problem for both wideouts. He averaged 7.1 receptions for 82 yards in his seven appearances last year. It might take a few more weeks, but Godwin should be back in the WR2 ranks before midseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d5d-d6a5-adff-ffddfb1a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers coach Kyle Shanahan said how Mac Jones plays “doesn’t really affect” whether Brock Purdy (toe) will play in Week 3.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d69-dfde-a1bd-5fed04ed0000</link>
      <description>Shanahan is already getting out ahead of a potential quarterback controversy by reiterating that there isn’t anything Mac Jones can do to earn more playing time. He will stay under center until Purdy is healthy and then head back to the bench. The 49ers just signed Purdy to a contract extension this offseason, keeping him in town through the 2030 season. Purdy’s deal also includes a no-trade clause. Even if Jones outplays Purdy, there’s no viable way for the team to make the switch. Purdy is practicing this week and could return after missing one game, though we suspect he will be held out until at least Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d69-dfde-a1bd-5fed04ed0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed S Tony Jefferson from their practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d7e-dfde-a1bd-5ffff3940000</link>
      <description>Jefferson came out of retirement to play for Jim Harbaugh in 2024. He was released by the team this year at the end of camp but immediately joined LA’s practice squad. He started for the Chargers versus the Raiders last week and broke up two passes with one interception. The strong performance was enough to earn him a permanent spot on the roster.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d7e-dfde-a1bd-5ffff3940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers signed EDGE Clelin Ferrell, formerly of the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d83-d1b3-a5dd-5df36fa30000</link>
      <description>Ferrell appeared in 14 games for the Commanders last year, operating as a rotational pass-rusher. He notched 3.5 sacks and a forced fumble. With Khalil Mack landing on injured reserve because of an elbow injury, the Chargers were bound to add some depth at EDGE. Ferrell will work his way into the mix as a part-time player until Mack is ready to return.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-5d83-d1b3-a5dd-5df36fa30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
