<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:04:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Prater was ruled out for the remainder of Week 18 with a quad injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b4b-dc7a-af9b-cfffbd700000</link>
      <description>Prater missed the last two games with a quad injury, but was able to return for this one. That may have been a mistake by the Bills. It appears Prater reaggravated his injury on his third extra point attempt, so the Bills will play the remainder of the game without a kicker. What’s worse, the Bills may have to find another kicker for the playoffs. They had Michael Badgley on their roster for the last two weeks, but he was released from the practice squad, so they’ll likely hold tryouts this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b4b-dc7a-af9b-cfffbd700000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colts announced they will retain HC Shane Steichen and GM Chris Ballard.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b4f-dc7a-af9b-cfff99bc0000</link>
      <description>After falling from 8-2 to out of the playoffs it’s a mild surprise that both will return. The Colts would probably be hardpressed to do better than Steichen as an offensive mind, so that part makes some sense even if he hasn’t made the playoffs yet. But Ballard’s trade for Sauce Gardner has left the franchise without a first-round pick in 2026 or 2027 and has almost forced them to look into retaining Daniel Jones off a torn Achilles. Ballard hasn’t won a playoff game since 2018. Principal owner Carlie Irsay-Gordon will speak with the media tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b4f-dc7a-af9b-cfff99bc0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audric Estime rushed 21 times for 63 yards in the Saints’ Week 18 loss to the Falcons, adding five receptions for 43 yards.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b56-d968-a19b-dbf7717b0000</link>
      <description>Playing out the string for the Saints’ injury-ruined backfield, Estime reached 100 yards from scrimmage for the first time in his career after posting 98 the week before. Not a bad end to the year for a player who spent the first half of the season on practice squads. Still only 22 years old, Estime is buying himself time to get established in the NFL, but he still probably mostly profiles as a special teamer if he’s going to make a 53-man roster out of camp. Considering the Saints’ issues at running back, it could very well be in New Orleans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b56-d968-a19b-dbf7717b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Allgeier rushed seven times for 16 yards in the Falcons’ Week 18 win over the Saints, adding a three-yard reception.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b5b-d56e-afff-effb58c70000</link>
      <description>Although he stole some clock-killing and goal-line work, contract-year player Allgeier finishes with 610 yards from scrimmage while Bijan Robinson led the league at 2,298. A little older than you might imagine (26 in April), Allgeier now heads to free agency with the kind of profile that will land guaranteed money, but not necessarily a starting job. He is a reasonably versatile player, one who has a 1,000-yard rushing campaign on his résumé. He was a “success rate” all star this year. Allgeier is a player who could be a lot more valuable in dynasty leagues three months from now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b5b-d56e-afff-effb58c70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Sills caught an 11-yard pass in the Falcons’ Week 18 win over the Saints.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b60-dc7a-af9b-cfff147b0000</link>
      <description>Sills’ grab was his only target. Although he somewhat improbably emerged as a red-zone option for Kirk Cousins this season, Sills caught just 18 total passes. That was a new career high, but this is a journeyman special teamer who turns 30 in May. This might be the last time you see his name in fantasy football.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b60-dc7a-af9b-cfff147b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs QB Chris Oladokun was benched in favor of Shane Buechele.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b64-dc7a-af9b-cfff9b1e0000</link>
      <description>Oladokun was lost throughout the first half, even in a clean pocket. He completed 11 of 17 attempts for 58 scoreless yards and was sacked three times against a Raiders defense that ranks among the league’s worst against the pass. Oladokun will revert to practice squad status for 2025 if he remains in Kansas City.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b64-dc7a-af9b-cfff9b1e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravens declared WR Rashod Bateman, QB Cooper Rush, WR Keith Kirkwood, CB Keyon Martin, CB Amani Oruwariye, OL Joseph Noteboom and DT Aneas Peebles inactive for Week 18 against the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b64-d35e-a1bf-cfe6c27e0000</link>
      <description>Bateman was ruled out Saturday because of illness. Kirkwood was just elevated from the practice squad, but won’t play in the winner-take-all game. Rush is the emergency third quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b64-d35e-a1bf-cfe6c27e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers ruled out WR KeAndre Lambert-Smith (hamstring) in Week 18 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b0c-d35e-a1bf-cfcebf5a0000</link>
      <description>Shortly before halftime, Lambert-Smith picked up a first down after snagging a pass from QB Trey Lance via a slant route. He was tackled at the Broncos’ 12-yard line. After the play, Lambert-Smith could be seen grabbing at his left hamstring. He quickly met with trainers for an evaluation, and the team initially labeled him as questionable to return. He finishes his day having caught 2-of-5 targets for 24 yards and returned two kicks for 45 yards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b0c-d35e-a1bf-cfcebf5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steelers declared EDGE T.J. Watt active for Week 18 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b6e-d968-a19b-dbffd0b10000</link>
      <description>Watt isn’t expected to get his usual amount of snaps, but the future Hall of Famer will be able to held as a pass-rusher in sub-packages in the winner-take-all game. The Steelers inactives for Week 18 will be WR Roman Wilson, QB Will Howard, RB Kaleb Johnson, CB Tre Flowers, LB Jeremiah Moon and OT Jack Driscoll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b6e-d968-a19b-dbffd0b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks signed LT Charles Cross to a four-year, $104.4 million extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b73-d968-a19b-dbf3ec240000</link>
      <description>Seattle’s stalwart left tackle signs an extension despite being inactive for the last couple games of the 2025 season with a hamstring injury. Cross posted a 73.2 PFF grade in 2025, a bit down from his 2024 grade of 82.5 but still rather good. The 25-year-old is now tied to the Seahawks for at least the next couple of seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-8b73-d968-a19b-dbf3ec240000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
