<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:06:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders HC Klint Kubiak said they “definitely want to have a two-man show (at RB),” this season.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9b83-dbf6-abdd-ff934f380000</link>
      <description>It’s not the news dynasty managers who spent valuable draft capital last season want to hear, but it isn’t all that surprising to hear from Kubiak, who deployed both Kenneth Walker and Zach Charbonnet at high rates last season. Jeanty will almost certainly operate as the lead back, but it is a bit alarming when you consider how Walker and Charbonnet were utilized last season, and the fact that both running backs finished as the RB28 in PPR points per game (11.3). It’s far too early to panic, but fantasy managers already participating in early best ball drafts may want to consider this latest piece of news before selecting Jeanty in the last first/early second round of drafts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9b83-dbf6-abdd-ff934f380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaking on the Pat McAfee Show, Panthers GM Dan Morgan said “I haven’t talked to any teams about a trade (for Andy Dalton).”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9bcc-d042-afbc-ffde0fef0000</link>
      <description>This comes a day after ESPN’s Adam Schefter reported the Panthers had been receiving calls about Dalton for a potential trade. Morgan said he “would talk to Andy” about any requests for a trade that may come through, but it’s hard to imagine the 38-year-old signal-caller being in high demand with free agency and the draft still to go. Dalton has one more year remaining on his current deal with the Panthers, and could make for a nice bridge for a team bringing in a younger quarterback, but wouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a one-year option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9bcc-d042-afbc-ffde0fef0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PennLive’s Nick Farabaugh reports the Steelers met with Penn State QB Drew Allar at the NFL Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9bf9-dbf6-abdd-fff977160000</link>
      <description>A true wild card in this year’s draft, Allar saw his 2025 season cut short due to a season-ending ankle injury. The former Nittany Lion started each of his last three years with the team and put together a mixed bag of performances while throwing for 7401-61-13 and adding another 732 yards and 12 touchdowns on the ground. Allar has a chance to improve his draft stock with a solid combine, where he is expected to throw, and should meet with plenty of teams who are interested in finding out what he could offer as a Day 2 or Day 3 selection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9bf9-dbf6-abdd-fff977160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders released C Tyler Biadasz.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9c63-d89c-a1be-bfffe2e40000</link>
      <description>Biadasz joined the Commanders in 2024 and started all 31 games he played. The veteran center’s release comes with one year still left on his deal, but it can net the team savings just north of $8.285 million if he’s designated as a post-June 1 release. A one-time Pro Bowler, Biadasz will be 28 at the start of next season and earned a PFF grade of 71.5 while playing on 954 snaps, per PFF. He should have plenty of suitors on the open market in the coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9c63-d89c-a1be-bfffe2e40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports extending Will Anderson “is a priority” for the Texans this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9c98-d629-a1bc-bc9df1ba0000</link>
      <description>Anderson has totaled 23 sacks over the last two seasons and has wasted little time establishing himself as a premier pass-rusher in the league. The former No. 3 overall pick is entering the fourth-year of his contract and will have his fifth-year option picked at some point in the coming weeks. When he signs his deal, Anderson, 24, could reset the market for pass rushers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9c98-d629-a1bc-bc9df1ba0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills re-signed S Sam Franklin Jr. to a three-year contract.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f49-d629-a1bc-bf5db7f80000</link>
      <description>According to ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler, Franklin can earn up to $7.5 million on his new deal, with $5 million coming in the first two years. Franklin is a career special-teams player who appeared on 329 special-teams snaps for the Bills last season, totaling 13 tackles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f49-d629-a1bc-bf5db7f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State WR Carnell Tate said he is only planning to run the 40-yard dash at the NFL Scouting Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f4f-d629-a1bc-bf5fac5a0000</link>
      <description>Tate is widely believed to be the top receiver in this year’s class and has confirmed he will run on Saturday when the receivers, quarterbacks, and running backs get their chance to shine. Tate caught 51 passes for 875 yards and nine touchdowns last season while averaging 17.2 YPR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f4f-d629-a1bc-bf5fac5a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USC WR Makai Lemon will not run the 40-yard dash at the NFL Scouting Combine.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f5a-dbf6-abdd-ff5b84b10000</link>
      <description>Lemon will participate in the gauntlet and run routes, but will skip out on the 40 and all testing drills. The USC product caught 79 passes for 1,156 yards and 11 touchdowns last season and has played 65.6 percent of his snaps from the slot, per TruMedia. Lemon is expected to hear is name called in the first round of the draft and has drawn comparisons to fellow Trojan Amon-Ra St. Brown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f5a-dbf6-abdd-ff5b84b10000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Person reports the Panthers have given DT A’Shawn Permission to seek a trade.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f7b-d89c-a1be-bfff72e80000</link>
      <description>As Person points out, this was expected. Robinson is considered to be a trade/cut candidate, which would free up $10.5 million for the Panthers. The veteran lineman who will be 31 next season continues to play at a high level. Robinson totaled 65 tackles, three TFLs, and 2.5 sacks last season, and had 80 tackles, eight TFLs, and 5.5 sacks in 2024. With just one year left on his current deal, Robinson could likely be acquired for a late Day 3 pick, but given the possibility of a release, teams may just wait until he hits the open market before attempting to acquire him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9f7b-d89c-a1be-bfff72e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Todd Archer reports the Cowboys will officially place the franchise tag on George Pickens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fa1-d89c-a1be-bfff77c10000</link>
      <description>Cowboys executive VP Stephen Jones hinted at tagging Pickens earlier this week but didn’t entirely commit to the idea, despite things clearly heading in that direction. Now, according to Archer, the Cowboys will tag Pickens on Friday, placing him under team control through the 2026 season. While it’s possible the Cowboys will attempt to sign Pickens to a long-term extension later this offseason, they could also look to deal him for draft pick compensation in the coming weeks or force him to play out the year on the tag, which will guarantee him just over $28 million this season. Pickens finally showed his fully potential in 2025 after being traded to the Cowboys. He posted career highs in receptions (93), receiving yards (1,429), and receiving touchdowns (9), while looking every bit like a true No. 1 receiver despite playing opposite CeeDee Lamb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019c-9fa1-d89c-a1be-bfff77c10000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
