<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Saints placed WR Bub Means (leg) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a53f-d90d-a5bd-a77f86250000</link>
      <description>The move ends Means’ season unless he is released with an injury settlement. Means went down with an apparent lower leg injury in the Saints’ preseason opener versus the Chargers and was carted to the locker room. The second-year wideout had a chance at carving out a rotational role behind Chris Olave and Rashid Shaheed before going down with the injury. Brandin Cooks now appears to be locked into the WR3 job for New Orleans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a53f-d90d-a5bd-a77f86250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys owner Jerry Jones said “nothing” is preventing contract talks with EDGE Micah Parsons.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a5a1-d45c-a7fc-a7bbee640000</link>
      <description>The Cowboys front office and Parsons and his camp have yet to restart talks on a contract extension. Jones said ,"I don’t know that necessarily talks will” pick up when the team goes to Dallas and that “nothing” is preventing the discussion, though clearly there is a rift between the two parties. When approached by reporters on the topic, Parsons said, “my mouth’s closed.” The relationship between Parsons and the Cowboys still seems in the bitter stages of the contract dispute, though the 26-year-old is present at training camp. Jones adamantly expects Parsons to play under his current contract, saying, “You don’t have deadlines when you’re playing under a contract.” The Parsons-Cowboys contract saga remains at a stalemate as the regular season approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a5a1-d45c-a7fc-a7bbee640000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Orleans Times-Picayune’s Luke Johnson reports Saints QB Spencer Rattler got “an extended look with the first team” in Wednesday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a65d-d90d-a5bd-a65f0e590000</link>
      <description>Rattler began the preseason as the Saints’ starter and continues to get the practice reps for it. Johnson reports that rookie Tyler Shough and Rattler rotated with the first team in Wednesday’s practice, with Rattler getting “an extended look.” Meanwhile, Jake Haener took just four third-team scrimmage snaps. Johnson believes he is the odd man out of the starting quarterback competition. The Saints’ quarterback room has taken shape with Rattler starting, Shough the backup, and Haener third. Head coach Kellen Moore could go with Rattler to start the season with Shough waiting in the wings to take over eventually.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a65d-d90d-a5bd-a65f0e590000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins placed OL Germain Ifedi on season-ending injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a562-df63-a199-fd6b708c0000</link>
      <description>The team signed offensive lineman Yodny Cajuste in a corresponding move. Ifedi made seven starts for the Browns last year and signed with the Dolphins as a depth piece less than two weeks ago. Cajuste’s last NFL snap came in 2022 with the Patriots. While Ifedi wasn’t projected to start for Miami, losing depth this early in training camp is never a good sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a562-df63-a199-fd6b708c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The PewterReport’s Scott Reynolds “would be shocked” if Chris Godwin (ankle) doesn’t start the year on the PUP list.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a8cf-df63-a199-f9efbae70000</link>
      <description>That would sideline Godwin for at least four games. Godwin suffered a dislocated ankle in Week 7 last year and has yet to return to practice. He underwent an initial surgery after suffering the injury and needed a second procedure in the spring, though that was reportedly for a minor cleanup. Godwin looks like a safe bet to miss Week 1. Now the question is whether or not Tampa Bay will put him on ice for four games to open the year. First-round rookie Emeka Egbuka will take his place in the lineup for at least Week 1. Egbuka has drawn rave reviews in training camp and is pushing for a WR3 ranking based on recent ADP.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a8cf-df63-a199-f9efbae70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons agreed to terms with CB C.J. Henderson, formerly of the Steelers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a8db-df63-a199-f9fb67250000</link>
      <description>Per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport, Henderson still has to pass his physical. The deal will be official once that happens. Henderson spent a month on the Steelers’ practice squad last year before being called up to the active roster. He did not, however, appear in a single game as a Steeler. His last live reps came with the Panthers in 2023. He made 10 starts, appeared in all 17 games, and broke up six passes with two interceptions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a8db-df63-a199-f9fb67250000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Sam LaPorta (undisclosed) will miss “a little bit of time.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a8e5-d05a-adda-aae7dcf40000</link>
      <description>Campbell didn’t give any specifics on the injury, only calling it a minor issue. Barring a setback, it doesn’t sound like this is something that will have any effect on LaPorta for Week 1. Still, it’s something for fantasy managers to monitor. LaPorta got off to a slow start last year after suffering an ankle injury in Week 3. He didn’t top 53 yards in a game until Week 15. LaPorta then surpassed 60 yards three times in his final four appearances. He should be able to ride that momentum into the start of the 2025 season as long as this current injury doesn’t spiral.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a8e5-d05a-adda-aae7dcf40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Tony Grossi reports Browns QB Dillon Gabriel (hamstring) is expected to be “full go” in Thursday’s practice.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a8f4-d45c-a7fc-aafe63f60000</link>
      <description>Gabriel has been dealing with a hamstring injury for over a week. He has been getting in some reps during team drills and now appears to be back at full strength. Gabriel is in line to start the Browns’ second preseason game versus the Eagles if he makes it to Saturday without any setbacks. With Shedeur Sanders and Kenny Pickett both sidelined because of injuries, Gabriel will get plenty of playing time if he’s active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a8f4-d45c-a7fc-aafe63f60000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports Rashee Rice’s disciplinary hearing is scheduled for September 30th.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a90f-d90d-a5bd-ab5f4b2e0000</link>
      <description>Rice was sentenced to five years of probation and 30 days in jail for his involvement in a multi-car crash in Dallas over a year ago. The ruling allowed the NFL to move forward with its disciplinary process, which will now take place after Week 4. Rice is expected to be given a multi-game suspension, though estimates for how long that will be range from two to eight games. No matter the length, it’s unlikely the suspension prevents him from playing in the fantasy playoffs. Fantasy managers should still expect to be without him for roughly four games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a90f-d90d-a5bd-ab5f4b2e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers placed OT Andre Dillard on season-ending injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a918-d05a-adda-ab9ad60f0000</link>
      <description>San Francisco placed Dillard on the PUP list ahead of training camp. Dillard underwent offseason ankle surgery and was still recovering from the procedure. He came off the PUP list earlier this week. It’s unclear if he suffered a setback or if this is a new issue. Either way, the 49ers are down a potential swing tackle as the season approaches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000198-a918-d05a-adda-ab9ad60f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
