<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 17:01:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders coach Pete Carroll said he expects TE Michael Mayer (ankle) to miss Week 14’s game against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f084-d77b-adfa-fa876e620000</link>
      <description>Carroll is “hopeful” that Mayer will play against the Eagles in Week 15. Fantasy managers have not been given a compelling reason to roster Mayer for the better part of the last month, and this latest rule out won’t help matters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f084-d77b-adfa-fa876e620000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears WR Rome Odunze “needs rest” after playing through a stress fracture in his foot and is now considered week-to-week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f088-d8cf-affb-fcaa7ffa0000</link>
      <description>Prior to the foot listing, Odunze had been a fixture on the Bears’ injury report with heel and ankle issues dating back to late October. It’s possible these listings are all related. NFL Network’s Tom Pelissero reports that “the belief is it’s nothing long term and he’ll be back soon.” The Bears (9-3) sit atop the NFC standings. Preserving Odunze’s health for the playoffs makes sense. The Bears sandwich a Week 15 game against the Browns with games against the division-rival Packers in Weeks 14 and 16. Hopefully, Odunze is good to go for the rematch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f088-d8cf-affb-fcaa7ffa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders ruled out WR Dont’e Thornton (concussion) for Week 14 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f092-d77b-adfa-fa933c960000</link>
      <description>Raiders head coach Pete Carroll said he expects rookie WR Jack Bech to be involved “a lot” in Week 14. Bech will likely play more snaps, but expecting him to be involved a lot as a receiver seems foolhardy. Thornton has earned just 25 targets all year and Bech somehow trails him with 14. Bech warrants mild DFS consideration but should not be in re-draft lineups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f092-d77b-adfa-fa933c960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills claimed S Darnell Savage off waivers from the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f097-da9b-a9bf-fe9f0e130000</link>
      <description>The Bills placed CB Darius Slay on the reserve/did not report list earlier today, so Savage’s addition makes sense. Savage has played for both the Jaguars and Commanders this season, logging one pass breakup, 13 tackles and two quarterback pressures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f097-da9b-a9bf-fe9f0e130000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos WR Pat Bryant (hamstring) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f0a3-d005-a9bf-f8b7ed380000</link>
      <description>Bryant’s youthful hamstring is evidently good to go. The rookie wide receiver was added to Thursday’s injury report as a limited participant. He remained limited on Friday as well. The soft tissue injury adds volatility to his outlook, but he is a decent bet to earn a moderate single-digit target sum on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f0a3-d005-a9bf-f8b7ed380000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys head coach Brian Schottenheimer said WR CeeDee Lamb (concussion) “had a good day” on Friday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f0f2-d005-a9bf-f8f6d1980000</link>
      <description>Lamb still has to get through the NFL’s concussion protocol, but this is nice to hear. Allowing the symptoms to abate through rest and rehab is key. Players frequently miss at least one game after entering the protocol, but the added rest time afforded to Lamb thanks to the Cowboys’ Week 14 Thursday Night Football game could help him take the field in Week 15 against the Vikings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f0f2-d005-a9bf-f8f6d1980000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders QB Geno Smith (foot) was removed from the injury report and will play in Week 14 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f11e-d005-a9bf-f93ee2bf0000</link>
      <description>Smith practiced fully on Thursday and Friday, which is a good sign. The error-prone quarterback cannot be started in single-quarterback leagues and is barely on the QB2 radar, given the tough matchup. Tight ends have had success against the Broncos this season, so hopefully, Smith locks onto TE Brock Bowers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f11e-d005-a9bf-f93ee2bf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Chargers QB Justin Herbert (hand) is expected to play against the Eagles in Week 14.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f227-d8cf-affb-fe2f74660000</link>
      <description>It’s been trending this way all week with Herbert participating on a limited basis in practice. The 27-year-old quarterback fractured a finger that required surgery on his non-throwing hand against the Raiders in Week 13. The Chargers have publicly maintained optimism around Herbert’s availability throughout the week. Still listed as questionable, Herbert is expected to play against the Eagles in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f227-d8cf-affb-fe2f74660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Dianna Russini reports Cardinals could move on from QB Kyler Murray this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f44e-d005-a9bf-fc7edabe0000</link>
      <description>Russini writes that executives around the league wouldn’t be surprised if Murray is on the move this offseason. Murray’s contract will complicate matters given his nearly $60 million dead cap hit next year and almost $40 million in guaranteed money. Still, Russini suggests the Cardinals could opt to release Murray in the unlikely scenario where they can’t find a trade partner. Even before Murray got hurt this year, the writing was on the wall that this marriage wasn’t working out. Now that he’s been ruled out for the year by coach Jonathan Gannon, it’s increasingly likely he’s played his final snaps with the Cardinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f44e-d005-a9bf-fc7edabe0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports Chargers RB Omarion Hampton (ankle) “should be” activated for Week 14’s matchup with the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f48a-d8cf-affb-fcaaeedf0000</link>
      <description>Hampton practiced in full on Friday and Fowler passes along that the Chargers feel good about his progress. The 22-year-old running back appears to be on the right side of questionable. Hampton is an RB2 against the Eagles in Week 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-f48a-d8cf-affb-fcaaeedf0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
