<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 23:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Browns activated RB Quinshon Judkins.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-440c-d86f-abdd-45bd110b0000</link>
      <description>Judkins is now clear to make his professional debut for the Browns against the Ravens in Week 2. He has had very little time with the team after dealing with offseason legal issues but will at least be available for the first time this season. Don’t expect Judkins to see many snaps after missing all of his rookie camp and preseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-440c-d86f-abdd-45bd110b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcons K Younghoe Koo will not travel with the Falcons for their Week 2 game against the Vikings.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4438-d86f-abdd-45bdb9920000</link>
      <description>The team has made a change at kicker following Koo’s missed 44-yard field goal attempt in the closing stages of their loss to the Buccaneers. Falcons signed Parker Romo earlier in the week, who will kick for the team against the Vikings Sunday. We could see Koo released by the Falcons in the coming week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4438-d86f-abdd-45bdb9920000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks HC Pete Carroll said TE Brock Bowers (knee) is expected to play in Week 2 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44a9-d294-a19b-e4f9da5b0000</link>
      <description>Bowers did not practice Thursday or Friday but returned to the field Saturday. His level of participation in Saturday’s practice is not yet known, but it was apparently enough to give Carroll confidence in Bowers’ availability Monday. Bowers drew the questionable tag for Week 2, so fantasy managers counting on Bowers would do well to either back him up with Michael Mayer or make other plans at the position consider the Raiders play in the final game of the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44a9-d294-a19b-e4f9da5b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Christian Kirk (hamstring) is out for Week 2 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44b1-d294-a19b-e4f14f2c0000</link>
      <description>Kirk continues to nurse a hamstring injury sustained in the lead up to the team’s Week 1 game against the Rams. He will now miss his second consecutive contest, leaving Justin Watson, Jayden Higgins, and Jaylin Noel to split work behind established veterans Nico Collins and Xavier Hutchinson. Kirk’s next chance to return to game action comes in Week 3 when the Texans face the Jaguars in Jacksonville.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44b1-d294-a19b-e4f14f2c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texans WR Braxton Berrios (hamstring) is out for Week 2 against the Buccaneers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44b4-d294-a19b-e4f4b2960000</link>
      <description>Both Berrios and Christian Kirk will miss the team’s Week 2 game against the Buccaneers with hamstring injuries. Berrios is more valuable for his contributions on special teams. His next opportunity to hit the gridiron comes in Week 3 when the Texans travel to Jacksonville to face the Jaguars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44b4-d294-a19b-e4f4b2960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cowboys signed OG Tyler Smith to a four-year, $96 million extension.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44b7-d86f-abdd-45bf2ffa0000</link>
      <description>Smith receives a massive $81.2 million in guaranteed money and is now under team control through the 2029 season. Smith has received above average grades in both run blocking and in pass protection in each of his three professional seasons and will now anchor the offensive line in Dallas for the foreseeable future. He becomes the highest-paid guard in the league with the new deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44b7-d86f-abdd-45bf2ffa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins placed OT Austin Jackson (toe) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44bb-d294-a19b-e4fb4d020000</link>
      <description>Jackson joins OG James Daniels on injured reserve, meaning the Dolphins will now be without two starters along the offensive line for the foreseeable future. Early returns from this unit do not inspire confidence that the Dolphins will be able to return to their previous form after struggling throughout the 2024 campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44bb-d294-a19b-e4fb4d020000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chargers LB Denzel Perryman (ankle) is out for Week 2 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44bf-da67-a99f-ccffffae0000</link>
      <description>This was to be expected after it was revealed Perryman sustained a high-ankle sprain in the team’s Week 1 win over the Chiefs. Expect Troy Dye to step into the vacated snaps in the center of the Chargers’ defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44bf-da67-a99f-ccffffae0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders LB Elandon Roberts (elbow) is off the injury report and will play in Week 2 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44c9-dc44-a9d9-47efd4260000</link>
      <description>Roberts reportedly suffered a sprained elbow in the team’s Week 1 win over the Patriots. He missed practice Thursday but managed to increase his participation each subsequent day, getting in a limited session Friday before upgrading to a full practice Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-44c9-dc44-a9d9-47efd4260000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Adam Schefter reports the Giants have “no sense of urgency” with regards to their quarterback situation.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4529-d86f-abdd-45bdcf260000</link>
      <description>Specifically, there is no sense of urgency to “to bench Russell Wilson and start rookie Jaxson Dart.” The report only exists, of course, because there is already very much a sense of urgency in the public discourse. Per Schefter, the team is leaving itself wiggle room. “It doesn’t mean a change can’t come soon at the quarterback position, but the Giants would prefer that it not happen anytime soon, according to sources.” That, we believe, but it will come sooner rather than later if Wilson continues to play like he did in the Giants’ opener against the Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-4529-d86f-abdd-45bdcf260000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
