<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 20:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (undisclosed) did not practice on Monday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bd2-d95b-addb-fbd64c160000</link>
      <description>Not normally a noteworthy bit of information, Benson’s status is interesting because the Cardinals signed Michael Carter to their active roster on Monday. Theo Mackie of the Arizona Republic speculates that the Cardinals could turn to Carter as their lead back if Benson is hurt, and coach Jonathan Gannon would give only a vague “taking it day by day” update on Benson. This is a bit of an odd injury update timing since Arizona played on Thursday Night, but it’s certainly possible that Benson pops up on the injury report ahead of Week 5. Carter would seem to be the back to roster in what is shaping up to be a dream matchup against a beleagured Titans unit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bd2-d95b-addb-fbd64c160000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions coach Dan Campbell said Detroit will designate Alim McNeill (PUP/knee) to return this week.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bdd-deb6-a7fd-dbdf07820000</link>
      <description>McNeill’s Week 15 ACL tear is healing well and the Lions are reportedly targeting a Week 7 or Week 8 return for their star interior player. McNeill had 8.5 sacks over the past two seasons and carried PFF grades of 86.8 and 79.6. He’ll be a big help for Detroit when he comes off the PUP list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bdd-deb6-a7fd-dbdf07820000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots WR DeMario Douglas played just eight snaps in Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9be4-d95b-addb-fbe616f80000</link>
      <description>We didn’t blurb it over the weekend, but with Stefon Diggs being unchained early in the game, Douglas’ role in New England’s offense was all but kaput. This may be rock bottom and we’d anticipate Douglas being out there more in a game script where the Patriots are actually trying to pass, but Douglas is very droppable in most leagues if Diggs is going to be New England’s main slot receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9be4-d95b-addb-fbe616f80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphins signed WR Cedrick Wilson off the Saints practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bf9-d6e9-af9d-9bf96d750000</link>
      <description>Wilson is no target threat at this stage of his career, which is good news for Jaylen Waddle, Malik Washington, and Nick Westbrook-Ikhine. Those three appear to be a the top of the pecking order in a post-Tyreek Hill Dolphins offense. Westbrook-Ikhine played the majority of the outside snaps in Hill’s absence in Week 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9bf9-d6e9-af9d-9bf96d750000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns placed WR Cedric Tillman (hamstring) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c05-dca3-a9fb-bd9d9cfa0000</link>
      <description>They signed Malachi Corley and Gage Larvadain to the active roster to replace Tillman. Isaiah Bond out-targeted Tillman 10-5 the past two weeks and would seem to be the main beneficiary of a Tillman absence, though it’s hard to want to start him into the Vikings given how poorly Joe Flacco has played this year. Tillman will be out at least four weeks and might not return to a spot in Cleveland’s pecking order. He’s droppable in most leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c05-dca3-a9fb-bd9d9cfa0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders LT Kolton Miller (ankle) will be placed on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c09-deb6-a7fd-dfdfb40e0000</link>
      <description>It’s not just a high-ankle sprain, but additionally a hairline fracture per NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport. It sounds like this will knock Miller out for most, if not all of the season. Miller played through the injury in Week 4, but posted a disastrous 43.2 PFF grade while doing so. Third-round pick Charles Grant and veteran Stone Forsythe are the current depth options in the Raiders tackle room.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c09-deb6-a7fd-dfdfb40e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bills placed P Cameron Johnston (leg) on injured reserve.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c0e-d95b-addb-fc4e8a830000</link>
      <description>The punter will miss at least the next four weeks after replacing Brad Robbins as Buffalo punter in Week 1. Buffalo’s third punter of the season will be Mitch Wishnowsky. You can do what you will with that information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c0e-d95b-addb-fc4e8a830000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panthers coach Dave Canales said that Chuba Hubbard’s calf injury “wasn’t a factor” in how reps were divided in Week 4.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c13-d6e9-af9d-9e934d400000</link>
      <description>Canales told reporters that he believes “with the players we have in the backfield, if we can sustain drives, if we can play these games that way, then we have a full-speed runner, a violent runner in every time.” That’s a rough quote for Hubbard’s future workload — something that Athletic beat writer Joseph Person is advocating should grow. It doesn’t feel like the coaching staff feels the same way. Rico Dowdle probably doesn’t qualify as a bye week FLEX play just yet, but this quote certainly at least puts him into consideration in deeper leagues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c13-d6e9-af9d-9e934d400000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Athletic’s Joe Person reports David Moore (elbow) “likely will miss multiple weeks.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c16-d95b-addb-fc56851c0000</link>
      <description>Rookie sixth-rounder Jimmy Horn — you may remember him as Travis Hunter’s Colorado teammate — will get a chance to ply his trade in Moore’s absence, with Dave Canales saying he wants to “make sure he’s able to go out there and give us significant reps. We’ll carve out a role because there’s certainly things he can bring to our offense with his speed and ability to carry the ball and make yards.” Horn could make an interesting pickup in deeper leagues right now with Hunter Renfrow not exactly blossoming last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c16-d95b-addb-fc56851c0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers coach Matt LaFleur said Devonte Wyatt (knee) is “week to week.”</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c1d-dca3-a9fb-bd9d8a640000</link>
      <description>Wyatt’s injury appeared to be a big factor in Green Bay’s trouble stopping Dallas on Sunday night. Nazir Stackhouse and Karl Brooks filled in inside, but neither is as effective as the 2022 first-rounder had been in the first few games of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=00000199-9c1d-dca3-a9fb-bd9d8a640000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
