<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 18:02:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Giants declared OLB Kayvon Thibodeaux, QB Russell Wilson, WR Ryan Miller P Jamie Gillan, T James Hudson III, WR Gunner Olszewski and DL Rakeem Nuñez-Roches Sr. inactive for Week 15 against the Commanders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1db5-d1bc-a3fb-9db52d990000</link>
      <description>Thibodeaux remains out with his shoulder injury, and there’s a good chance he won’t return in 2025. Wilson will again be the emergency quarterback behind Jaxon Dart and Jameis Winston.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1db5-d1bc-a3fb-9db52d990000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears declared QB Tyson Bagent, RB Travis Homer, DE Dominique Robinson, DT Jonathan Ford, LB Ruben Hyppolite II, and WR Jahdae Walker inactive for Week 15 against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1db8-d77b-adfb-dfbbdff40000</link>
      <description>Bagent was sent home with an illness and Case Keenum will serve as Caleb Williams’ backup for Week 15 against the Browns. Otherwise, the Bears are fairly healthy with four games left in the regular season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1db8-d77b-adfb-dfbbdff40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengals declared WR Tee Higgins, QB Jake Browning, S JP Jules, and DT Jordan Jefferson inactive for Week 15 against the Ravens.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dba-d005-a9bf-ddbe578a0000</link>
      <description>Higgins was ruled out on Friday due to the concussion he suffered in Week 14’s loss to the Bills. His absence will create a bigger role for WR Mitchell Tinsley, who saw a season-high nine targets in Week 13 against the Ravens when Higgins was sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dba-d005-a9bf-ddbe578a0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared QB Geno Smith (shoulder/back), RB Zamir White, CB Greedy Vance, OL Jordan Meredith (foot), TE Ian Thomas (calf), WR Alex Bachman (thumb) and DL Leki Fotu inactive for Las Vegas’ Week 15 game against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dbc-d8cf-affb-bdbe50e80000</link>
      <description>Meredith and Thomas were on the questionable line while Smith and Bachman were ruled out on Friday. No major changes from expectations here; Kenny Pickett will start against the Eagles in a #RevengeGame and figures to be one of the weaker superflex options on the slate today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dbc-d8cf-affb-bdbe50e80000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs declared WR Hollywood Brown, OT Jawaan Taylor, OG Trey Smith, TE Jared Wiley, CB Trent McDuffie, DT Zacch Pickens, and RB Elijah Mitchell inactive for Week 15 against the Chargers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1db8-d005-a9bf-ddbcf4f30000</link>
      <description>Brown will sit out Kansas City’s crucial Week 15 tilt against the Chargers for personal reasons. His absence could open up more routes and targets for JuJu Smith-Schuster. The Chiefs will also be without McDuffie, making Justin Herbert’s matchup a little better. Herbert is a borderline option in one-QB leagues even with McDuffie out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1db8-d005-a9bf-ddbcf4f30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Browns declared RG Wyatt Teller (calf), DT Adin Huntington (quad), RT Jack Conklin (concussion), CB Denzel Ward (calf), RB Dylan Sampson (calf), TE David Njoku (knee) and G Zak Zinter (back) inactive for Week 15 against the Bears.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dbc-d8cf-affb-bdbe9c410000</link>
      <description>No surprises on the Browns inactives as Dylan Sampson was ruled out earlier in the week. His absence is a boost for Quinshon Judkins, who should see more receiving work with Sampson sidelined. LG Joel Bitonio (knee, back), WR Cedric Tillman (concussion, rib), DT Mason Graham (rib), and WR Malachi Corley (concussion) are active after being listed as questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dbc-d8cf-affb-bdbe9c410000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Christian Benford is inactive for Week 15 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dd3-d77b-adfb-dfd30cff0000</link>
      <description>The Bills’ top cornerback picked up a toe injury in practice towards the end of the week, and is unfortunately unable to go on Sunday. This is a huge loss for Buffalo, as Benford has been near elite over the last few weeks since overcoming an early season injury. The bills will start Tre’Davious White and Maxwell Hairston at corners and their depth will be severely tested, which is probably why they tried to sign Darius Slay a couple of weeks ago. The Bills also declared WR Gabe Davis, OT Tylan Grable, OT Chase Lundt. DT Phidarian Mathis, LB Terrel Bernard, and S Darnell Savage inactive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dd3-d77b-adfb-dfd30cff0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joshua Palmer is active for the Bills in Week 15 against the Patriots.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ddd-d8cf-affb-bdffb9660000</link>
      <description>Palmer had missed the last few weeks with an ankle injury, but was able to get in a few limited practices this week and appears good to go. It wouldn’t be a surprise if he is not quite at 100%, but the Bills need his athleticism and downfield capability in their receiving corps. Surprisingly, Gabe Davis was made in inactive for this game, which might signal a more pass heavy approach for the Bills since Davis is arguably their best run blocking wide receiver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1ddd-d8cf-affb-bdffb9660000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patriots declared WR/KR Efton Chism III, OLB Bradyn Swinson, TE C.J. Dippre, OT Marcus Bryant, DT Eric Gregory, and QB Tommy DeVito inactive for Week 15 against the Bills.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1de2-d77b-adfb-dfe3f74e0000</link>
      <description>No real surprises here. The Patriots come into this game relatively healthy, except for defensive tackle Milton Williams being on the IR.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1de2-d77b-adfb-dfe3f74e0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Bears WR Rome Odunze (foot) was ruled out after re-aggravating his foot injury before Week 15’s game against the Browns.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dc0-d005-a9bf-ddf4da560000</link>
      <description>Odunze is officially active, but Rapoport’s report that he’s been ruled out after re-aggravating his foot injury pregame came just minutes before kickoff. It’s disastrous news for anyone that was counting on Odunze in the first round of the fantasy playoffs. Luther Burden should see a boost in value with Odunze sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019b-1dc0-d005-a9bf-ddf4da560000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
