<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lions declared C Graham Glasgow, S Kerby Joseph, EDGE Joshua Paschal, WR Kalif Raymond, TE Brock Wright, OL Miles Frazier, DL Mekhi Wingo, and DL Tyler Lacy inactive for Week 13 against the Packers.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c624-d90e-a9da-df2f32cb0000</link>
      <description>Key players like Glasgow, Joseph, Paschal, and Wright were all ruled out before Thursday’s game, so this doesn’t come as much of a surprise. The Lions will hope to get most of these players back after some extended rest. The good news, however, is that Terrion Arnold and Penei Sewell will both be active after entering the day as questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c624-d90e-a9da-df2f32cb0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packers declared WR Matthew Golden (wrist) inactive for Week 13 against the Lions</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c62e-d82c-a79a-f7be04da0000</link>
      <description>Despite being limited in practice throughout the week and listed as questionable on Wednesday, Golden will be sidelined for Thursday’s Thanksgiving Day tilt. The rookie receiver has caught 24 passes for 286 scoreless yards this season. In addition to Golden the Packers also declared LB Quay Walker, DE Lukas Van Ness, DT Karl Brooks, WR Savion Williams, CB Nate Hobbs, and OL Donovan Jennings inactive for Week 13.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c62e-d82c-a79a-f7be04da0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vikings signed QB Desmond Ridder to the practice squad.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c64c-d6c4-abfb-d64fbed70000</link>
      <description>Ridder will likely be activated before Week 13’s game against the Seahawks as J.J. McCarthy continues to work his way through concussion protocol. Ridder spent time with the Vikings earlier this season but has not appeared in a game this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c64c-d6c4-abfb-d64fbed70000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Cowboys are likely to use the franchise tag on George Pickens this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c652-d82c-a79a-f7d6fc2f0000</link>
      <description>The offseason trade for Pickens has paid off in a big way for the Cowboys this season. The fourth-year receiver is already in the midst of a career year through 11 games this season, and will fetch a heavy payday, whether it’s from the Cowboys or someone else. Team owner Jerry Jones said earlier this week that the Cowboys have “two number one receivers,” adding further credence to the belief that the team will look to retain its top playmaker this offseason.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c652-d82c-a79a-f7d6fc2f0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports the Lions are expected to sign Jahmyr Gibbs to a contract extension this offseason.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c657-d6c4-abfb-d65769330000</link>
      <description>Gibbs is in just his third year with the Lions and will undoubtedly have his fifth-year rookie for the 2027 season exercised this offseason, but the Lions would be smart to secure the 23-year-old back for the long term. Arguably the best dual-threat back in the league, Gibbs has rushed 155 times for 951 yards and 10 touchdowns this season and has caught 48 passes for 379 yards and another three scores. He ripped off a 49-yard touchdown run in Week 12 to put the Lions within three points of the Giants, and secured the win for them in overtime on a 69-yard touchdown run. Gibbs won’t turn 24 until next offseason and is already among the best backs in the league. It would be wise for the Lions to get him under contract sooner rather than later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c657-d6c4-abfb-d65769330000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Network’s Ian Rapoport reports Daniel Jones will attempt to play through a fractured fibula in Week 13 against the Texans.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c661-d6c4-abfb-d663df960000</link>
      <description>Jones was a full participant in Thursday’s practice and “looked good,” according to a source familiar with the situation who spoke with Rapoport. This isn’t an injury that’s going to heal in one week, so Jones could try to play through it for multiple weeks. Jones has enjoyed a career revival in Indianapolis this season, throwing for 2,840-17-7 while completing a career-high 69.1 percent of his passes. He gets a tough matchup in Week 13 against the Texans, and shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a mid-QB2 if active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c661-d6c4-abfb-d663df960000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Monangai (knee) will play in Week 13 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c668-d82c-a79a-f7fca9860000</link>
      <description>Monangai was listed as a full participant on Tuesday’s injury report and continued to be listed as a full participant throughout the week. The rookie was removed from the injury report on Thursday, meaning he’ll be good to go against a matchup between 8-3 teams hoping to keep pace with the Rams for the top spot in the NFC. Monangai enters Week 13 with a three-game touchdown streak, but shouldn’t be viewed as anything more than a boom-or-bust RB3 given his low receiving totals and rushing outputs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c668-d82c-a79a-f7fca9860000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bears ruled out LB T.J. Edwards (hand/hamstring) for Week 13 against the Eagles.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c66d-d6c4-abfb-d66f5d8b0000</link>
      <description>The Bears also ruled out LBs Ruben Hyppolite (shoulder) and Noah Sewell (elbow) ahead of Friday’s game. Hyppolite is a lightly used backup who has totaled just six tackles this season, while D’Marco Jackson will take over for Edwards and Sewell, who have both been key contributors for the defense when active.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c66d-d6c4-abfb-d66f5d8b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lions WR Amon-Ra St. Brown is questionable to return in Week 13 against the Packers after suffering an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c693-d82c-a79a-f797dd6b0000</link>
      <description>St. Brown was embracing the Lions’ “no block, no rock” philosophy by attempting to help RB Jahmyr Gibbs pick up yards on a run play. The Packers’ defender stood St. Brown up just before fill-in starting C Trystan Colon and LG Kayode Awosika hit the ground behind him, simultaneously rolling in the back of St. Brown’s legs. Lions trainers were seemingly assessing St. Brown’s right ankle before the broadcast cut to commercial. He headed straight to the locker room once he was on his feet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c693-d82c-a79a-f797dd6b0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals RB Trey Benson (knee) was not seen practicing on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c67d-d82c-a79a-f7fd8fe30000</link>
      <description>Benson could still get limited work in later on, but Benson appears to be heading toward a DNP today. The Cardinals’ running back logged four straight limited sessions dating back to last week. We were hoping to see him upgrade to full participation today or tomorrow. We will provide an update if the official injury report reveals that Benson did indeed manage to participate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-c67d-d82c-a79a-f7fd8fe30000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
