<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NBC Sports Fantasy Football News</title>
    <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news</link>
    <description>Latest player news and analysis for fantasy football from NBC Sports.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 03:20:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ESPN’s Jeremy Fowler reports that the Buccaneers are “thinking” WR Chris Godwin (fibula) could return in late November or in December.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b76-d713-ad9e-7f7649940000</link>
      <description>Godwin has not yet returned to practice, so missing Week 10 against the Patriots makes sense. Fowler adds that RB Bucky Irving (foot/shoulder) could sit out in Week 10 as well. The Buccaneers face the Saints on December 7th, at which point, Godwin should apparently be back. Unfortunately, that is five games away, which could prove costly for fantasy managers who continue to stash him. He does not need to be rostered at this time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b76-d713-ad9e-7f7649940000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broncos declared WR Marvin Mims Jr., CB Pat Surtain II, TE Nate Adkins, RB Jaleel McLaughlin, OLB Que Robinson, DL Sav’ion Jones and DL Jordan Jackson inactive for Week 10 against the Raiders.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b8d-d1e7-a1fa-5bef6ad40000</link>
      <description>Mims (concussion) and Surtain (pectoral) both missed the Broncos’ Week 9 game against the Texans as well. The Broncos’ top-tier defense should be okay in this one, but it is an unfortunate missed opportunity for Mims’ fantasy managers. The speedy wide receiver would have had decent odds of producing an explosive gain or two against the Raiders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b8d-d1e7-a1fa-5bef6ad40000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raiders declared RB Zamir White, TE Carter Runyon, G Caleb Rogers, DT JJ Pegues and DL Leki Fotu inactive in Week 10 against the Broncos.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b94-d45b-affe-5f96eca90000</link>
      <description>The Raiders get back S Lonnie Johnson, who broke his leg in training camp. Rookies, DT Tonka Hemingway and WR Dont’e Thornton, are active tonight as well. The Raiders will ostensibly use the next few weeks to see if one or more of their rookie wide receivers, including Jack Bech, can unseat one of head coach Pete Carroll’s favorites, WR Tyler Lockett.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b94-d45b-affe-5f96eca90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49ers WR Ricky Pearsall (knee) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b9b-d45b-affe-5f9fd7cf0000</link>
      <description>Even if Pearsall miraculously practices in a limited capacity, he would be unlikely to suit up. The 49ers’ perimeter wide receiver has not practiced since spraining his PCL in Week 4. He remains difficult to drop, given his early-season successes, but the situation is agonizing nonetheless. Check back tomorrow to see if Pearsall’s fortunes have changed overnight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5b9b-d45b-affe-5f9fd7cf0000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Cooper Kupp (heel/hamstring) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ba1-d1e7-a1fa-5beb6e350000</link>
      <description>Kupp’s return is a big deal, though he is not yet out of the woods. Seahawks rookie WR Tory Horton practiced in full yesterday while listed with a groin injury. He was unable to practice today and is now also listed with a shin injury. Seahawks TE AJ Barner (calf) remains limited through two practices as well, and rotational WR Jake Bobo (calf) remains sidelined. New Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed is seemingly headed toward a significant role in his first game with his new team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ba1-d1e7-a1fa-5beb6e350000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks WR Tory Horton (groin/shin) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ba1-d673-a39e-ffb167b30000</link>
      <description>Horton practiced in full yesterday while listed with a groin injury and was seemingly on track to play in Week 10 against the Cardinals. He was unable to practice today and is now also listed with a shin injury. His injury comes at a poor time. Veteran WR Cooper Kupp (heel/hamstring) was limited today, as was TE AJ Barner (calf). Fellow WR Jake Bobo (calf) remains sidelined. New Seahawks WR Rashid Shaheed is looking like a high-upside WR3 this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5ba1-d673-a39e-ffb167b30000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seahawks TE AJ Barner (calf) was limited on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5bb4-d713-ad9e-7ff47fe20000</link>
      <description>Barner is tentatively on track to play, but it would be nice to see him practice in full tomorrow. The Seahawks’ 23-year-old tight end has four TE1 finishes on his 2025 resume, but he must be treated as a touchdown-dependent fantasy starter. Seahawks rookie TE Elijah Arroyo could warrant TE1 consideration if Barner sits out against the Cardinals this weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5bb4-d713-ad9e-7ff47fe20000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinals CB Will Johnson (back/hip) did not practice on Thursday.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5bb8-d45b-affe-5fbe64c90000</link>
      <description>The Cardinals’ stud rookie cornerback was a limited participant yesterday. Mid-week downgrades are never good. Johnson has been playing through a groin injury intermittently this season. Perhaps a week off would do him some good. Unfortunately, the Cardinals face the division-rival Seahawks in Week 10.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5bb8-d45b-affe-5fbe64c90000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antonio Brown was apprehended by authorities in Dubai and arrested on attempted murder charges.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5bbd-d1e7-a1fa-5bffb2080000</link>
      <description>The arrest relates to a shooting at a celebrity boxing event in Miami, back in May. Brown is reportedly being held in New Jersey and will be transported to Florida at an as-yet-unreleased date. It is unknown why he was taken to New Jersey first, and it is also reportedly unclear as to whether Brown has an attorney.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5bbd-d1e7-a1fa-5bffb2080000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jackson Powers-Johnson is questionable to return in Week 10 against the Raiders with an ankle injury.</title>
      <link>https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c08-d673-a39e-fc99536f0000</link>
      <description>Powers-Johnson got rolled up on a third-down sack, and after a quick look in the injury tent, the 22-year-old offensive lineman was carted off the field. Alex Cappa has taken Powers-Johnson’s spot at guard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.nbcsports.com/fantasy/football/player-news?playerNewsId=0000019a-5c08-d673-a39e-fc99536f0000</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
